<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ban Disputes  — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>Ban Disputes  — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/ban-disputes/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>Profile</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44921/profile</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Private Tom Halbroth</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44921@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello there. Unfortunatly i am no longer active in this community and would like for my profile to be deleted due to Private reasons. Thank you.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Server</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42194/server</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Rec. Bithell</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42194@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Good Evening all, Ive tried to search the server for my training tonight but, it says its non existent. Does anyone here want to give me a quick hand ?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Name Change</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42182/name-change</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Rec. Bithell</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42182@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi all, just wondering where to change my name, my IGN is PVT.Cal but on here its Rec.Bithell. wondering if anyone is able to help me out, new to this. TIA</p>

<p>wrong thread again</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Name Change</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42181/name-change</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 12:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Rec. Bithell</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42181@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Good afternoon all, so ive seen that their will be a name change for all Trainees, just wondering how to do it. My IGN Is PVT.CAL but on here its Rec.Bithell. Any help would be great.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Pending - Peace</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/34240/pending-peace</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 01:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Peace 21</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">34240@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID (How to get your ROID):idk<br />
Which Game were you banned on? (Arma 3, RO2/RS, RS2, Squad):RO2<br />
Date and Time of Ban: 9/27/19 (around 800 hours to 900 hours)<br />
Name you used when banned:Peace<br />
Admin who banned you:(Unknown)<br />
Why were you banned?:Spamming ( Unknown what type)<br />
Why should your ban be overturned?: Yeah... I just want to know the ban time and how long... also It was first time and it wasn't for a group of people...I mean I was in the zone man..  and the last time I said that was 10 - 15 min ago ( which was late ban after I stop) so</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Big Daddy</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/33111/unbanned-big-daddy</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 03:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>BigD121</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">33111@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID (How to get your ROID): 76561198001569710<br />
Which Game were you banned on? (Arma 3, RO2/RS, RS2, Squad): RS2<br />
Date and Time of Ban 9:55 PM CST 7/24/2019<br />
Name you used when banned: Big daddy<br />
Admin who banned you: Don't know<br />
Why were you banned?: Admin states I used the N word, never did in the match before and early match in which I was banned. Now if the admin states I was being rude and offensive then that was true.  Match before called all the SLs they sucked for the match on voice and text. One person also for not going into the cap point in the last few seconds. New match starts commander calls in spooky, AA goes up. I type in chat AA up, commander calls in scout and that is when I tell him "did you not pay attention to AA?" Then banned for using the N word.  Video leading to ban - <span data-youtube="youtube-aOKKZiqNHZ0?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aOKKZiqNHZ0"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/aOKKZiqNHZ0/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span><br />
Why should your ban be overturned?: I did not say the N word, if the ban is for foul language then let it be that.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Individuo Enlatado</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/29816/unbanned-individuo-enlatado</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Individuo_Enlatado</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">29816@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Name is Individuo Enlatado, admin claimed that I changed my squad name too much or something, which I didn't really do at all, I never even change my squad name on this game, its always the default settings. I don't know who is the admin, and I don't understand the reason for me being banned. I'm not a troll, this is one of my favorite games, and your server is one of the few where I get playable ping.</p>

<p>The ban happened yesterday (01/18/2019), and since I'm from Brazil I  have no idea what time it was in the US. I was playing the campaing for at least 3 maps I think,  I don't team kill at all and when I do I ask for forgiveness immediatly. I really don't understand why I was banned tbh.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Denied - Tea Bag Therapist</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/29821/denied-tea-bag-therapist</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 22:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>LovelessWolf221</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">29821@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>ROID (How to get your ROID):</strong> 76561198015759515<br />
<strong>Which Game were you banned on? (Arma 3, RO2/RS, RS2, Squad):</strong> Rising Storm 2 Vietnam<br />
<strong>Date and Time of Ban:</strong> Friday 18th January 05:18 GMT (UTC)<br />
<strong>Name you used when banned:</strong> "Tea Bag Therapist"<br />
<strong>Admin who banned you:</strong> Unknown<br />
<strong>Why were you banned?:</strong> "Insulting the Admin (Calling the Admin out on his BS)"<br />
<strong>Why should your ban be overturned?:</strong> "Because the Admin was being an abusive D***. My name was originally Tea Bag The Rapist. A joke between me and my friends. I was asked to change it in which I replied to the admin I would prefer to do it after the game had ended due to having to quit RS2 Vietnam. Me and my friends were joking around in the chat about the name and about being british at which point the admin kicked me.</p>

<p>I decided to acknowledge this and change my name to the above. (The name is a reference to the fact that I am indeed british and with the tea being dumped into boston harbour during the revolutionary war. Hence Tea Bag.) Which was Tea Bag Therapist. The second joke being I am a therapist.</p>

<p>During the time that I was changing my name my friends decided to confront the Admin (Hexagon and TurboDoms) Yes some harsh language may have been exchanged but both were banned. THEN another friend of mine was banned (Gingervitus) for using the word Gook. (Which is completely ridiculous. As it is Vietnam that is a historically accurate to use at that time) after this I rejoined and called the admin out on his BS. Yes I insulted him. However he had just banned 3 people and kicked me after I had requested that he wait until the end of the match as I would have to quit the game.</p>

<p>I think this is wholly unfair and a complete abuse of admin powers. Banning 4 people based on some words exchanged over a name which is a play on my british heritage and my profession."<br />
This happened on 29th Infantry Division New York Campaign 1 I think it was called</p>

<p><a href="https://vanilla.29th.org/profile/MSgt.%20Conrad" rel="nofollow">@MSgt. Conrad</a> said:</p>

<pre><code>Whoever Hexagon and TurboDoms are, I can assure you they aren't admins. All 29th ID admins would be wearing a 29th ID tag.

The other three people were banned for having the n-word as their squad name, so there's that.

Our server rules are listed on our website, when you join the server, and are constantly messaged through the admin console in the chat.

Any and all foul language, especially racial slurs, are not permitted on our server and we enforce that rule strongly. Before you say it, we absolutely don't care what would be acceptable in an actual war or that slurs are historically accurate. Your friend wasn't banned by the way, but I probably would have if I were there. Our server rules have been our server rules for 13 years. I don't see us changing them because someone wants to be toxic and try to justify it.

Excessive arguing with an admin is grounds for at least a temporary ban, but we typically lift those on first offenses.

Except you don't seem remorseful and you just seem to want to continue your behavior after I unban you and you seem to think its our fault for "abusing our power" to police the server that we pay for out of our own pockets. So I'm not particularly inclined to unban you.

Sell me on the idea.
</code></pre>

<p>Clearly you have skim read my post else you would understand Hexagon and Turbodoms are my friends who were banned for arguing in my defense over being kicked after asking the admin to wait until the end of the game for me to change my name.</p>

<p>My friends Turbodoms and Hexagon confronted the admin on kicking after asking the admin to wait until the end of the match. Secondly. They were not barred for their name. They were barred for arguing with the admin.</p>

<p>As far as I am aware my other friend Gingervitus didnt even get a warning for using the slur gook and was banned pretty much instantly.</p>

<p>Justify being toxic? elaborate upon where I have tried to justify being toxic? I simply said that using the term gook was historically accurate and it seems strange to ban someone based on the usage of such a word especially when its referring to an ingame character model and not an actual person? Admittedly I was kicked so I don't know how many times it was used. There was very little toxic behaviour. My name was originally Tea Bag The Rapist. I was asked to change it. I asked the admin to wait until the end of the match and then I would. We were joking around in chat with the Admin about me being english and our twisted sense of humour. I got kicked. My friends argued with the admin and we got banned. I joined again after changing my name and called the admin out and got banned.</p>

<p>The only thing you can remotely consider toxic are my friends and I insulting the admin AFTER what would be considered unfair treatment.</p>

<p>I didnt even get a response from the admin after I had asked him to wait until the end of the game. He just kicked me with no response.</p>

<p>We did not have the N-Word in our squad name. Our squad name was Gook. However what our squad was called is irrelevant because that is not the reason why they were banned.</p>

<p>Im not remorseful I have received a kicking after asking politely to wait until the end of the match. Why would I be remorseful for that? I also would not be remorseful for calling the admin out for banning 3 people. I should NOT have used foul language but I think I am at least a little bit justified considering the escalation of the scenario.</p>

<p>Quite frankly. Your attitude stinks also. You haven't tried to look at this completely objectively you don't seem to have fully read the post you have come here with the mindset that you and the admin are correct and that we were being toxic without looking at it objectively. I have never been a member of the 29th Infantry Division but I have played on your servers a few times across Arma 3 and Rising storm. Quite frankly this is disappointing.</p>

<p>Also you talk about policing the server. its more of a totalitarian regime than policing.</p>

<p>I was asked to change my name. I asked if the admin could wait until the end of the match. No response from the admin I was then kicked because I didnt comply.</p>

<p>My friends exchanged some harsh words with the admin upon why I was kicked. They were banned instantly.</p>

<p>I count 2 errors there. Firstly the admin did not state he wanted me to change my name straight away nor did he respond to me after I had asked him to wait until the end of the match. I was just kicked with no response from the Admin. As explained previously I have to completely shut down the entire game for the name to update.</p>

<p>My friends did insult the admin whilst asking why I was kicked which I don't think is wholly unfair considering that a member of their squad just got kicked for essentially trying to ask the admin to wait until the end of the match.</p>

<p>Yes I did rejoin and call the admin out. I did use abusive language towards the admin for banning an entire squad after one member got kicked.</p>

<p>I have not tried to hide the fact that me and my friends committed some wrongs. However if the admin had replied to me and told me "No you need to change your name now" or if he had explained to my friends the REASON why I got kicked there would not have been a need to ban 4 people from a server. Instead your admin chose not to explain himself and instead decided to ban everyone.</p>

<p>Yes you pay for the server however people play on the server with the thought that the admins will be fair in judgement and be willing to explain themselves. You have a right to police the server however you choose to police that has not been questioned. What has been questioned is the conduct of your admin on this occasion and the way he has acted not towards one but four individuals with no warnings or explanations.</p>

<p>Let me ask you a question. If you and your squad were performing rather well after some very abhorrent games and then one of your squad members got kicked for not receiving a reply to an admin about a name change in which he had asked the admin to wait. Would you not be a little irate? Would you not choose to question the admin on WHY the individual had been kicked after specifically asking the admin "Can I do it at the end of the match as I will have to restart Rising Storm 2"</p>

<p>I see the issue. You see, your sentence read "During the time that I was changing my name my friends decided to confront the Admin (Hexagon and TurboDoms)". Had you wanted to say that they were your friends, it should have read "During the time that I was changing my name my friends (Hexagon and TurboDoms) decided to confront the Admin".</p>

<p>I've got no ban records for your friends, just you. They probably got session banned for arguing with an admin.</p>

<p>I happen to trust my admins to do the right thing and you've not done much to convince me they didn't.</p>

<p>Your ban will stand. You are welcome to appeal at a later date if you choose to do so, but we understand if you would like to play on other servers in the future.</p>

<p><strong>Follow on</strong></p>

<p>Based on the above information I do not believe my case have been handled fairly or justly. I do not believe Msgt.Conrad has handled this case fairly or Justly. He has not been an independent third party and seems to have been biased against me.</p>

<p>I would like for someone else to look into the above and tell me if the perm ban for insulting an admin after being kicked for a name after asking for said admin to wait until the end of the match as mentioned above is fair or just.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Denied - Tea Bag Therapist</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/29811/denied-tea-bag-therapist</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 05:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>LovelessWolf221</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">29811@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Which Game were you banned on? Rising Storm 2 Vietnam<br />
Date and Time of Ban: Friday 18th January 05:18<br />
Name you used when banned: Tea Bag Therapist <br />
Admin who banned you: Dunno<br />
Why were you banned?: Insulting the Admin (Calling the Admin out on his BS)<br />
Why should your ban be overturned?: Because the Admin was being an abusive D***. My name was originally Tea Bag The Rapist. A joke between me and my friends. I was asked to change it in which I replied to the admin I would prefer to do it after the game had ended due to having to quit RS2 Vietnam. Me and my friends were joking around in the chat about the name and about being british at which point the admin kicked me.</p>

<p>I decided to acknowledge this and change my name to the above. (The name is a reference to the fact that I am indeed british and with the tea being dumped into boston harbour during the revolutionary war. Hence Tea Bag.) Which was  Tea Bag Therapist. The second joke being I am a therapist.</p>

<p>During the time that I was changing my name my friends decided to confront the Admin (Hexagon and TurboDoms) Yes some harsh language may have been exchanged but both were banned. THEN another friend of mine was banned (Gingervitus) for using the word Gook. (Which is completely ridiculous. As it is Vietnam that is a historically accurate to use at that time) after this I rejoined and called the admin out on his BS. Yes I insulted him. However he had just banned 3 people and kicked me after I had requested that he wait until the end of the match as I would have to quit the game.</p>

<p>I think this is wholly unfair and a complete abuse of admin powers. Banning 4 people based on some words exchanged over a name which is a play on my british heritage and my profession.</p>

<p>Kind Regards, <br />
LovelessWolf</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - The Shlonginator</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/29810/unbanned-the-shlonginator</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 04:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>The Shlonginator</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">29810@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I was banned on RS2: Vietnam on 1/17/2019 at around 11pm. The reason for the ban was unspecified and it did not specify by who I was banned by. My name at the time was "The Shlonginator". I really have no idea why I was banned. The only possible reason might have been because I was behind enemy lines when the line moved up and killed a few people as a result</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Zeppen</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/27731/unbanned-zeppen</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Zeppen</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">27731@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello, could someone answer me because I was banned from the server 29th Infantry ivision [Battalion Server] 66.150.121.150:7777 ???</p>

<p>I always played on this server, I do not understand.</p>

<p>Game -  Rising Storm 2 Viet.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Permanently Banned - L0C0</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/27258/permanently-banned-l0c0</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 16:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>L0C0</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">27258@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID : 76561198076592812<br />
Which Game were you banned on? RS2 <br />
Date and Time of Ban: Not sure <br />
Name you used when banned: L0C0<br />
Admin who banned you: Not sure<br />
Why were you banned?: Aim Hacking I guess lmao<br />
Why should your ban be overturned?: I don't hack I just use free cam a lot thats why I know where everyone is at.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned -  calcool007</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/26521/unbanned-calcool007</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 02:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>calcool007</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">26521@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Which Game were you banned on?  RS2<br />
 Date and Time of Ban: 5/18/2018 2pm-4pm<br />
 Name you used when banned: calcool007<br />
 Admin who banned you: Not sure<br />
 Why were you banned?: I didn't have the right packet<br />
 Why should your ban be overturned?: I continuously play on that one server because I like the environment and it is a great server to be apart of. If I over step my bounds by saying how someone in my squad isn't doing their job I don't mean to be rude especially to SLs and the reason why I particularly am not one myself is because I wouldn't be a very good one. I think the server and the admins are great and so are the people one it. I hope you guys get back to me soon. If this sounds like a rant I don't mean for it to be. I am not mad at anyone because it may of been by accident too</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Cramer</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/25814/unbanned-cramer</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 23:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Mark A. Cramer</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">25814@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I just enlisted through PFC Bren and he mentioned I had two past bans.. This was from 2010  when the 29th  was on Darkest Hour.  One ban was for saying I didn't like a map and I did use the word shit, which I didn't know was not allowed.<br />
The second ban I did deserve for cussing an admin for kicking me off the server to let someone else in after play 6o min of a 90 min map(the old Berlin map)<br />
I did not at the time realize how strict  the server rules were and was new to the game, but since then I have become familiar with the 29th community and rules, and have also been an admin for the 475 Ranger on RS.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>HOW TO DISPUTE YOUR BAN</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/25818/how-to-dispute-your-ban</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 04:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Hill [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">25818@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>To dispute your ban, you must first <a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/entry/register?Target=categories">register</a> on these forums.</p>

<p>Please go to the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/categories/ban-disputes">Ban Disputes Forum</a> and click "<i>New Discussion</i>" to create your own post.  And use the following form by copying and pasting it into your post.</p>

<hr />

<p>ROID (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://29th.org/roid">How to get your ROID</a>):<br />
Which Game were you banned on? (Arma 3, RO2/RS, RS2, Squad):<br />
Date and Time of Ban: <br />
Name you used when banned: <br />
Admin who banned you: <br />
Why were you banned?: <br />
Why should your ban be overturned?:</p>

<hr />

<p><strong>Note:</strong> If you were Session Banned (which only bans you for the duration of the map) then do not post a dispute it. If you're not sure, wait until the server changes maps.</p>

<p><strong>Note:</strong> If you are not very good at English, post in your language as well. One of us probably speaks your language.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Pvt Leomchuh</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/24009/unbanned-pvt-leomchuh</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Professor TBag</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">24009@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561198090519774<br />
Which Game were you banned on? RO2/RS<br />
Date/Time of Ban: 2014 <br />
Name you used when banned: pvt leomchuh<br />
Admin who banned you: no idea<br />
Why were you banned: I think it's because I played on other servers<br />
Why should you be unbanned: Because its been 4 years</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - GingerCrusader</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/23222/unbanned-gingercrusader</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 21:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>GingerCrusader</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">23222@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561198038212766<br />
Which Game were you banned on? (DH, RS, ArmA3) Rising Storm 2: Vietnam<br />
Date/Time of Ban: 01/02/2018 4:50 pm<br />
Name you used when banned: GingerCrusader<br />
Admin who banned you: unknown<br />
Why were you banned: no reason given. Just received message of "violation" when kicked<br />
Why should you be unbanned: Had just joined the public server and spawned in a squad and was subsequently banned without reason</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Dunkirk[Fjr2]</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/20111/unbanned-dunkirk-fjr2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Carsten M. Bievenour</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">20111@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561198049598695<br />
Which Game were you banned on? (DH, RS, ArmA3): your Ts<br />
Date/Time of Ban: a week or two after Halloween (2016)<br />
Name you used when banned: Dunkirk[Fjr2]<br />
Admin who banned you: none given<br />
Why were you banned: racism<br />
Why should you be unbanned: they day i got banned i was invited into the Ts by PFC. Schruurman (at the time) to do an interview about the Halloween event that took place Halloween night between the FJR2 and the 29th in Darkest Hour (2016). I did my interview and that was it. I latter was going to go back on to see if anyone wanted to play Men of War with me and some fellow Fjr's and it said i was banned for Racism. i do not know who or exactly why i was banned.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Pvt.</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19677/unbanned-pvt</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 10:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Oliver Campbell</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19677@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561198022360434<br />
Which Game were you banned on? DH<br />
Date/Time of Ban: 2017-02-01, don't know the exact time<br />
Name you used when banned: Pvt.<br />
Admin who banned you: PFC. Verbruggen<br />
Why were you banned: Reason: Didnt change his name when i told him to, warned him multiple times, kicked, returned, warned and kicked again.<br />
Why should you be unbanned: I was playing the game and got really into the action as it was the best part of the match. Suddenly, I got notified by the admin to change my name. I believe at this point I responded and said that I'd change it as soon as the game was over. To this, I got no reply only a kick. Once that had happened I tried changing my name to what it needed to be however, for some reason it only showed the name "Pvt.", basically, I messed up the tags. Unaware of my name still not being correct, if I recall correctly I was warned once again to which I once more responded by saying that I'll get it done later as I couldn't hop off at that moment, I was lacking in time as it was already late. After that, no response was given and I got banned.</p>

<p>I don't want to come off as negative, all I wish is to be unbanned so that I may enjoy playing on the server once more.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - MountinousMontenegrin</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19423/unbanned-mountinousmontenegrin</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Mickonziyeh</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19423@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: DH<br />
Date/Time of Ban: 01.08.2017 I dont remember how much time was it.<br />
Name you used when banned: MountinousMontenegrin<br />
Admin who banned you: I cant remember<br />
Why were you banned: For telling a dark humor joke wich was appereantly racist<br />
Why should you be unbanned: I wasnt aware of that rule and also admin didnt gave me any warnings and gave me perm ban wich I think isnt right. Also it was really harmless joke and no one was offended and everyone continued joking in chat.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Ban - &quot;Rec.Anderson&quot;</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19477/ban-rec-anderson</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>meosam2</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19477@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561198402122354<br />
Which Game were you banned on? (DH, RS, ArmA3) Forums<br />
Date/Time of Ban: Sometime last night was when I noticed I was banned from <br />
Name you used when banned: In game name is Vanilla, forum name was Rec.Anderson<br />
Admin who banned you: I am not sure, I think I was banned automatically.<br />
Why were you banned: I was banned for silly use of proxies on the forum<br />
Why should you be unbanned: As I've been talking to Melodrama and he told me about the proxy policy for the 29th. I like to switch proxies on teamspeak for flags and /int/ if you know it (4ch pass ofc) and other general joking around. I was not aware of the proxy policy (Although on hindsight I should've expected it) and if I knew this I of course would not have used my proxies. I'm very sorry for the inconvenience I've caused today and I'll of course stop using them when I am on the forums and on the 29th teamspeak. I just hope you can forgive me for my ignorance. I really do want to join with my friend and I hope my silliness wont hurt his chances either.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Aryan</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19444/unbanned-aryan</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>KeitelRJ</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19444@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561198034450295<br />
Which Game were you banned on? Darkest Hour<br />
Date/Time of Ban: a couple of months ago<br />
Name you used when banned: Aryan<br />
Admin who banned you: I don't really remember<br />
Why were you banned: was talking shit<br />
Why should you be unbanned: I was childish and I apologize, I really love this game ... I hope u understand guys</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>NameCopier-Legionario</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19204/namecopier-legionario</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 18:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Player</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19204@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This guy copies peoples names. His original name is legionario and he is from spain.</p>

<p>He is under the name of "Alf"<br />
<img src="https://s18.postimg.org/klk3z8ffd/20170718145943_1.jpg" alt="https://s18.postimg.org/klk3z8ffd/20170718145943_1.jpg" title="enter image title here" /><br />
Here is posing under my name on the allied team. Note Flag of spain.<br />
<img src="https://s18.postimg.org/j92exchzt/20170718150138_1.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
Switched name back to legionario<br />
<img src="https://s18.postimg.org/6vpkqfsbd/20170718151947_1.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p>complaints from others<br />
<a href="http://steamcommunity.com/app/1280/discussions/0/1457328927838408441/" rel="nofollow">http://steamcommunity.com/app/1280/discussions/0/1457328927838408441/</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Mass Tker-Ihavenofriends</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19171/mass-tker-ihavenofriends</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 15:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Player</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19171@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This guy was shooting friendlies left and right out of spawn. We all told him to stop, didn't listen.<br />
<img src="https://s11.postimg.org/m4zh6x4bn/20170717105614_1.jpg" alt="![![enter image description here](https://postimg.org/image/66qrgsa3j/ &quot;enter image title here&quot;)](https://postimg.org/image/66qrgsa3j/ &quot;enter image title here&quot;)" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="https://s4.postimg.org/wac8nfwfx/20170717105800_1.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="https://s17.postimg.org/4dq269kdr/20170717105804_1.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Deth</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19044/unbanned-deth</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 03:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Player</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19044@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561197988292604<br />
Which Game were you banned on? (DH)<br />
Date/Time of Ban: 7/9/2017<br />
Name you used when banned: Deth<br />
Admin who banned you: Cpt.Patty<br />
Why were you banned: Making fun of a screenshot on cpt pattys profile and insulting the 29th<br />
Why should you be unbanned: sorry</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Gen.Reverberi</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19045/unbanned-gen-reverberi</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 08:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Francesco Reverberi</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19045@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi all, sorry if i write in italian, but my english is horrible :S</p>

<p>Ciao a tutti, spero ci sia qualche giocatore italiano che possa aiutarmi. Scrivo perché sono stato bannato permanentemente da una stanza di gioco del vostro clan, ma non ne capisco il motivo. Non ho fatto fuoco amico né altro, a dire il vero non ho proprio giocato: sono entrato nella stanza, vedendo che tutti giocavano come semplici fucilieri (e tutte le altre opzioni erano vuote), ho intuito che in quella partita si potesse giocare solo in quel ruolo e allora mi sono adeguato scegliendo un fuciliere. Al che mi è stato scritto un messaggio tipo "only private", quindi mi sono visto bannare subito dopo. Ho riprovato a connettermi e ho scoperto che mi era impossibile connettermi perché al mio ost è negato l'accesso a quel server.<br />
Ora, siccome non c'erano solo giocatori della 29th, anzi, erano quasi tutti con nik non del vostro clan (e peraltro era l'unico server con un po' di gente, mi pare o 33 o 44 giocatori, non ricordo bene), potrei sapere perché sono stato bannato? <br />
E soprattutto, potrei essere nuovamente ammesso al vostro server, visto che ho sempre giocato correttamente, senza offendere nessuno e senza mai fare volontariamente fuoco amico?<br />
Grazie mille a tutti</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Aleczandr_Heimst</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18923/unbanned-aleczandr-heimst</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 02:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Aleczandr_Heimst</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18923@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edit 8:02pm PST-Forgot Steam ID: 76561198078789120<br />
Date/Time of Ban: 7:21 PST<br />
Game: RO: Darkest Hour '44<br />
Name you used when banned: SlovakianJewHunter<br />
Admin who banned you: Unknown-Edit 8:10pm PST- Only admin on was Dethfield.<br />
Why were you banned: Name wasnt under guidlines.<br />
Why should you be unbanned: Because i was preemtively banned without any warning or previous kicks.<br />
As stated above i was banned at aprox 7:21 PST while playing on the 29th Battalion server, when I was banned immediately with no Warning, preemptive kick or anything of the likes, for seemingly nothing more than the contents of my username (and that of my friends, although ironically enough, he was not banned.) and as it is now 7:38 my friend is still under the name of UkrainianCrippleHunter and has not been given a warning, a Kick or a ban of any kind. even though his name follows the exact same guidelines of mine, which (as the skins in game are S.S.(Dot 44, Oakleaf and black/Oakleaf Tanker Uniforms)) we followed a historical aspect for snipers and or other veterans of the time, which abides by nicknames of the sort. if given the chance you can contact me at Spidzer@Hotmail.com, and if need be i can hop onto the TeamSpeak to discuss this further. i tend to be under the username of Aleczandr, or Aleczandr_Heimst</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Unbanned - Malakai</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18841/unbanned-malakai</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 00:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Malakai J. Reinhard</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18841@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>game: I was banned from DH<br />
time: Roughly a year and a half ago<br />
Name: Believe it was Eugene or Malakai<br />
Banner: no idea<br />
Reason: No Reason Given<br />
why should you unban me: your server is the only one any one plays on the AI don't seem to work and I need a game that was fun, Thank you for taking your time to look at this post</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>I deeply regret what I did</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18875/i-deeply-regret-what-i-did</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 05:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>Yuoans</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18875@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I did wrong behavior,<br />
When i Played omaha, and win.<br />
I typed the "Sieg Heil"<br />
It was bad speech, Im so sorry about that<br />
I will never do that wrong behavior<br />
Please unlock my ban</p>

<p>my steam id : 76561198048221599<br />
IP address : 211.232.195.229</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Permanently Banned - Wehrmacht=WarCriminals</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18840/permanently-banned-wehrmacht-warcriminals</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 00:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Ban Disputes</category>
        <dc:creator>WWC</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18840@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>ROID: 76561198037356785<br />
Date/Time of Ban: 23 June 2017 circa 23:50 GMT<br />
Name you used when banned: Wehrmacht=WarCriminals<br />
Admin who banned you: No idea<br />
Why were you banned:</p>

<p>I presume by the defence of my username against right wing &amp; german fanatics who seem to have an issue with my username over the chat and my subsequent response to them.</p>

<p>Why should you be unbanned:</p>

<p>I do not believe I should have been banned in the first place.</p>

<p>My response to people having an issue with my name has been to google and then pick up a history book, to then ignore them and continue playing the game.</p>

<p>If you believe that I have been engaging in political discussion on the chat then please look at the chat transcript where I have not answered or engaged with even the most vile bigoted filth being written via the chat.</p>

<p>If you believe that my name is provocative and should be changed then I would suggest you also ban all the people with SS and other Wehrmacht unit names as well as those glorifying the III Reich, since there was almost no wehrmacht unit without involvement in major warm crimes, millions of rapes etc. and the <strong>open glorification</strong> of these units (which is quite common place on your server) I find to be a sickening disgrace which should also not be allowed. Although I have never openly disapproved of this on the server or via chat (and this should also be the same for soviet troops although I have found no one glorifying them), I have never protested against anyone in chat with usernames such as SS Totenkopf or Grossdeutschland Div etc. but I appear to have my fans regarding my username.</p>

<p>If you believe my name must be changed on this server I invite you to educate yourself on what is fact and should not even be challenged or discussed, i.e. the myth that is the clean wehrmacht.</p>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clean_Wehrmacht">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clean_Wehrmacht</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/War_crimes_of_the_Wehrmacht">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/War_crimes_of_the_Wehrmacht</a></p>

<p>There are several references of books and studies that can be followed from these two articles.</p>

<p>If you believe my ban should be upheld, you should then also ban the fellow who was throwing the most appalling anti-semitic filth at me in random intervals (I am not Jewish but it is still irrelevant), most of which I did not reply to, I'm sure he did not get banned - I forget his name please see the transcript.</p>

<p>Should the ban be upheld I will be fairly disgusted that while open glorification and pride in an army that committed some of the most appalling filth known to a modern army in history is not only accepted, openly displayed and indulged in on your server, but that to signal sympathy for their victims - the millions of women raped and/or forced into sexual slavery not to mention the thousands of deliberate murders and pillaging to name a few would be so outlandish a thing to have as a username that it would result in instant banning.</p>

<p>People have no right to not be offended by my username if it dispels their myth of a criminal army, and I should have every right to use it as a username since it is based in fact and not fantasy, unlike those used by people pretending to be Wehrmacht units with pride.</p>

<p>At most I could agree to not engage in discussion with people on your server who have a problem with my username, I did my best to answer simply google + history book when such people attacked me. However if this is the case I should have been warned and not just banned in an instant and while someone was ranting anti-semitic filth at me I might add. Would people complain if my username was Stalin=Bad? Or Hitler=Murderer?</p>

<p>The only other thing I can think of for the ban is where a few minutes before I by mistake killed quite a few team mates over a bridge firing HE from a tank, they were in fact mixed with German infantry on the Lutremange map (the flags had just changed position) and I also hit an allied supply truck killing all inside which from my angle and with the infantry looked like an Axis opel truck, judging by my score about 6th on the leader board with around 40 points at the time one can see I am not and have never been a deliberate team killer.</p>

<p>The result of this ban dispute is really a reflection of you as a server as opposed to any infarction on my part.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
