<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Public Discussion — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>Public Discussion — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/public-discussion/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>E-Day Event during the  winter break.</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/41734/e-day-event-during-the-winter-break</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 02:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpl. Burlock</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">41734@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello,</p>

<p>I am going to be running a unofficial event on my own server. It will be a D-Day style drill where the Americans assault a fortified beach head. Details are as follows!</p>

<p>E-Day<br />
Operation Endgame</p>

<p>Mission Brief:<br />
The United States Army has been assigned a spearhead mission to liberate Skorpo, a Norwegian town which has been captured by the Russian Army. In a daring amphibious landing, the Americans will hope to root out the defenders and establish a beachhead. <br />
The game itself will be a multi-objective, multi-life game mode. A rule booklet will be compiled in future and distributed to each member. Objectives will range in placement and there will be seven total. To secure a victory, the US must take ALL objectives. <br />
The mission is slated to commence on Friday, December 18th at 0:800 pm est.<br />
More information will be sent at a later date.</p>

<p>Registration is done through messaging T/5 Burlock of EP2S1.</p>

<p>See the example below. Please fill out and PM the format:</p>

<p>Name: T/5 Burlock<br />
Squad: EP2S1<br />
Team Preference: US<br />
Prefered Roll: Squad Leader<br />
Current AIT: Automatic Rifleman</p>

<p>Name: <br />
Squad: <br />
Team Preference: <br />
Prefered Roll: <br />
Current AIT:</p>

<p>*** A list of all available Rolls are listed below ***<br />
Available rolls United States Army (55 Slots): <br />
2x Team Leader and Assistant<br />
3x Pilots (1 MH-6 and 2 UH-60)<br />
4x Crewman<br />
2x Marksman<br />
1x Airborne Squad Leaders<br />
5x Airborne Soldiers<br />
7x Infantry Squad Leaders<br />
31x Infantry Soldiers</p>

<p>United States Army Available Assets:<br />
3x MH-6<br />
3x UH-60<br />
2x Bradley IFV<br />
4x Strykers <br />
6x MATV w CROWS M240B</p>

<p>Available rolls Russian Army (44 Slots):<br />
2x Team Leader and Assistant<br />
4x crewman<br />
2x Marksman<br />
6x Infantry Squad Leaders<br />
30 Infantry Soldiers</p>

<p>Russian Army Available Assets:<br />
2x BMP-2<br />
4x BTR-82<br />
5x Tigr CROWS<br />
8x Technical Trucks</p>

<p>Hope to see you guys out there! It will be lots of fun!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Tips For Playing  a medic in squad</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/41927/tips-for-playing-a-medic-in-squad</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 11:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Charlesworth</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">41927@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The following tips may be more use on the public servers but I sure some can help you in the 29th drill &amp; Scrim environments.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Playing the medic<br />
•   Stick close to your squad leader and slightly behind the fight. Tell the other members of the squad that you will not trek miles to heal them no matter how loud they scream! Firstly, this allows squad leader to do a lot of his duties, placing a rally etc and secondly it will hopefully let you manage the wounded quickly and get them back up and fighting. You can earn a lot of points as a medic.<br />
•   If you are not doing medical duties, get your shovel out and help your squad build. <br />
•   Get to the cap points with your squad.<br />
•   If you are incapacitated and no chance of revival, ask your squad leader for permission to give up. The medic needs to get back into the fight as soon as possible.<br />
•   If there are no medical duties and nothing to build or cap. Get your gun out but be prepared to put it away as soon as squad takes casualties.</p></li>
<li><p>Healing tips<br />
•   Staying alive is the most important, do not enter a “hot area” if you think you are unlikely to survive. <br />
•   If casualties are making a lot of noise, either calling for medic in whatever language or talking loudly in chat. Tell them to “Shut up”. You need to be able to hear the enemy if they are near and there calls also alert the opposition that there may be more of your squad alive in the area.<br />
•   When using field bandages, always try to be in prone position and position the casualty between you and any contact fire. (use him as a sandbag). Get in with dead and heal them. The number of times enemy have run past me thinking I dead is unbelievable.<br />
•   As you treat the casualty, quietly tell him where the enemy are, and any safe locations nearby, (and if has to run or crawl). Or get him to smoke.<br />
•   If you have a lot of casualties, concentrate on using field dressings. Only when everybody in reach is up, start using the medical kit.</p></li>
<li><p>When using the medical kit<br />
•   Always be a level lower than your patient. If he is standing, you crouch. If he is crouching, you lie prone. This allows him to secure the area for both of you. If he is prone again us him as a sandbag. <br />
•   Always leave the patient a safe place to move into if you come under fire.</p></li>
<li><p>General Tips<br />
•   Only use smoke if the opposition know you are active. If they think you are dead, move quietly and do not throw smoke, talk or fire your weapon.<br />
•   A medic should move fast and as quietly is possible. Leaping of blind walls is risky, but if the opposition are not alert you can get away with it.<br />
•   If travelling by logistical truck, get to the truck early and sit in the f5 or f6 position. The opposite side to where you expect the enemy “might be”. So if travelling North and the opposition is expected from the East, Sit in West side of the truck (f5). The f5 and f6 get protection from cab, load area and other personnel. It is no guarantee of survival, but you have the best chance of survival of anybody in the vehicle.<br />
•   If any vehicle traveling is hit, leave the vehicle as soon as you can and again take a prone position near the vehicle until you know what you intend to do.<br />
•   Healing non-squad members. I heal everybody if your short of bandages don’t be afraid to ask a rifleman of another squad to rummage in his pack and resupply your medical equipment. Very often riflemen will offer it up without being asked.</p></li>
</ol>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>A Tribute to Captain Fritz</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/40370/a-tribute-to-captain-fritz</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 08:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Bull</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">40370@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gentlemen, some of you have heard of the fascination I have with history, and in keeping with my fascination, I decided to create some dress uniform sets of members within the Blue and Gray.</p>

<p><img src="https://ibb.co/xzkV7Kj" alt="Front Chest" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ibb.co/xzkV7Kj">FC Link</a><br />
<img src="https://ibb.co/qp5cs0h" alt="Left Breast Pocket" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ibb.co/qp5cs0h">LB Link</a><br />
<img src="https://ibb.co/44fxy81" alt="High View Initial" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ibb.co/44fxy81">HVI Link</a><br />
<img src="https://ibb.co/0JdHwQy" alt="Shoulder Patch" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ibb.co/0JdHwQy">SP Link</a><br />
<img src="https://ibb.co/Wcj3D2n" alt="Name Tape" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ibb.co/Wcj3D2n">NT Link</a><br />
<img src="https://ibb.co/q12r0Tj" alt="High View Final" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://ibb.co/q12r0Tj">HVF Link</a></p>

<p>First on the list is Captain Fritz, due to the original WWII uniform set I acquired having original WWII sewn-in bullion Captains' ranks, (which I would never butcher), it was fairly clear who I would "choose" first. Captain Fritz, your uniform was a joy to create. I learned many things about the rarities of each award, and how this unit conducts its uniform versus the real life counterpart. I will not bore you gentlemen with the details in this post, but rest assured, if you would ever let me talk your ears off in the TeamSpeak about it, lord knows I would. Thank you for letting me put together this uniform for you sir, as I said, it was a pleasure.</p>

<p>(If anyone would want me to create their uniform, ribbon rack, or shadow box, or even nominate someone for their uniform creation, please feel free to contact me. Rah and Kill!)</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>[A3] Updates, News &amp;amp; Changelogs</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/3074/a3-updates-news-amp-changelogs</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 22:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Tuomainen</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">3074@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This thread compiles and updates our forums with the latest news and changelogs in Arma 3. If you catch or see any updates or news about the game, anywhere, feel free to post below with the information and the links!</p>

<h3>Table of Contents</h3>

<ol>
<li><a rel="nofollow" href="#April21">SITREP #00103 (April 21st, 2015)</a></li>
<li><a rel="nofollow" href="#April16">SPOTREP #00041 (April 16th, 2015)</a></li>
</ol>

<hr />

<h3><a>SITREP #00103</a></h3>

<p>(<a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/post/sitrep-00103">Source</a>)</p>

<p>FROM: Project Lead<br />
TO: Arma 3 Users<br />
INFO: 1.44 Plans, Content Licensing, Game Capture Artist, Array Sorting<br />
PRECEDENCE: Flash</p>

<h4>SITUATION</h4>

<p>In the short-term we are looking towards the 1.44 update, which will focus on bringing the new <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.battleye.com/">BattlEye</a> anti-cheat version to main branch. We've tried to implement it in an unobtrusive manner, as you can preview on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/dev-branch">Dev-Branch</a>. Your help with testing it under all circumstances is going to be very useful. Specific feedback and suggestions can be shared on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.bistudio.com/showthread.php?190426-BattlEye-service-implementation&amp;p=2910511#post2910511">our forums</a>. The rest of the update consists of miscellaneous fixes and tweaks. Meanwhile, we are solidifying our road map for the Expansion. The various departments are generating asset wishlists, analyses and concept art, beginning feature feasibility studies, creating prototypes, and of course, supporting production of the new terrain. After this planning stage has concluded, we'll be sharing what we can in a blog. Most details and specifics on the Expansion will not be discussed until the second half of the year however. We can tell you there is plenty to look forward to!</p>

<h4>INTELLIGENCE</h4>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/bohemiainteract">Bohemia Interactive</a>'s publishing team is looking for a <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.bistudio.com/company/careers/game-capture-artist">Game Capture Artist</a> in one of our Prague offices. You'd be supporting our various games with captured gameplay footage, produce cool videos and show off the games on pretty screenshots. If you like the sound of that, please <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.bistudio.com/company/careers/game-capture-artist">apply directly on our website</a> for this or one of the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.bistudio.com/company/careers">other available positions</a>.</p>

<p>We've begun <a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/Arma3official/status/589010864281358337">highlighting</a> the game's <a rel="nofollow" href="http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements">Steam Achievements</a> on a regular basis. These meta-challenges can provide a fun extra motivation to explore parts of the game you don't normally visit. Or they can make you aware of features you did not even know exist. In the end though, it's all about bragging rights!</p>



<p>The first achievement is also the easiest one: "This is War". You unlock this by simply starting any scenario, mission, showcase, challenge or other form of playable content in the game. We added it to get a sense of the portion of people who've bought the game, and have actually tried it. However, the numbers are a little skewed. Steam's global statistics tell us that 58.2% of all Arma 3 players have currently unlocked it. Keep in mind that this achievement was introduced with version 1.20 (<a rel="nofollow" href="https://store.bistudio.com/products/arma3-karts">Karts DLC</a>); no Alpha, no Beta, and not even the first period after release. The percentage also includes people who have played the game during a Steam Free Weekend. So, from the percentage alone, we can mainly get a very rough approximation of unlocks and how achievements compare to each other.</p>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/Dslyecxi">Andrew "Dslyecxi" Gluck</a> has published <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tWjKx2wlgKs">an informative video</a> about <a rel="nofollow" href="https://store.bistudio.com/products/arma3-marksmen#.VTbQuSHtmko">Marksmen</a>'s <strong>ASP-1 Kir</strong> Special Purpose Rifle. It's certainly not a weapon designed for every situation, but it does have unique strengths. The video does a good job of visualizing these, and explaining some of the basics of supersonic and subsonic projectile properties.</p>

<p><span data-youtube="youtube-tWjKx2wlgKs?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tWjKx2wlgKs"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/tWjKx2wlgKs/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>The same videographer has worked with us on a series of official <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLfUcrRpCM_fLrk4KKLkQKrlTBh7txPaO3"><strong>Community Guide videos</strong></a>. We feel they do a great job of introducing various aspects of the combined arms experience, and looking awesome while doing so. If you've never watched them, go through this playlist, or watch them in-game from the LEARN menu.</p>

<h4>OPERATIONS</h4>

<p>Having released our third DLC for Arma 3, we wanted to take another look at our DLC strategy. Senior Designer <a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/Gekonn">Jiří Zlatohlávek</a> has taken the time to write the latest OPREP on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/post/oprep-content-licensing">"Content Licensing"</a>. That is the name we've given to the technology at the heart of the strategy. Our approach to post-release support is often discussed on various Internet channels, and we've followed the debate with great interest. Read the full report for a brief re-introduction of our goals, a motivation for the business model, and an overview of changes and improvements introduced in update <a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/post/spotrep-00040">1.42</a>.</p>

<p>A <a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/post/spotrep-00041">hotfix for 1.42</a> was released on the main branches last week. It fixed a few Weapon Deployment issues, a problem related to encrypted server passwords, and controller hypersensitivity. We are still looking for more useful data on a reported server crash. At the moment our programmers cannot reproduce nor isolate the problem.</p>

<p>Scripters will <a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/Killzone_Kid/status/588752610020196352">soon have access</a> to another common operation directly in the engine. Having to previously resort to slower scripted solutions, a future update will let you <a rel="nofollow" href="https://community.bistudio.com/wiki/sort">sort</a> <strong>arrays</strong> much quicker.</p>

<h4>LOGISTICS</h4>

<p>Launcher programmer <a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/jiripolasekcom/status/589906299200090112">Jiří Polášek</a> reports on a crash that is connected to the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.radeonpro.info/">RadeonPro</a> graphics card utility. Avoid the crash by disabling the utility, or by adding <em>arma3launcher.exe</em> to the compatibility list and setting <em>"Disable API detection"</em>.</p>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/post/oprep-content-licensing">OPREPer</a> Jiří has also <a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/Gekonn/status/587992904678907904">done a clean-up pass</a> of the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://steamcommunity.com/app/107410/workshop/">Steam Workshop</a>. The "Addon" tag is deprecated now that mods are supported, so most entries have it removed. He also removed the "Mod" tag for many scenarios which should not have it. We're investigating means of keeping the Workshop clean in the future, and letting it be a place where you can comfortably discover great new content. Jiří seems to have popped up all over the place this week. <a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/Arma3official/status/589060043045261314">Here</a> he is giving a presentation on Advanced Game Design at the Masaryk University (Faculty of Informatics).</p>

<p>As announced <a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/post/sitrep-00102">last week</a>, we have now disabled and <strong>removed</strong> the remaining <a rel="nofollow" href="http://makearmanotwar.com/">Make Arma Not War</a> Steam branches. If you had them selected, you'll have been switched to main branch.</p>

<hr />

<h3><a>SPOTREP #00041</a></h3>

<p>(<a rel="nofollow" href="http://dev.arma3.com/post/spotrep-00041">Source</a>)</p>

<p>FROM: Project Lead<br />
TO: Arma 3 Users<br />
UNIT: Main Branch<br />
ACTIVITY: Hotfix: 1.42 (Server Passwords, Weapon Deployment Glitches, Controller Sensitivity)<br />
SIZE: ~72 MB / ~10 MB</p>

<h4>NOTES</h4>

<ul>
<li>Connecting to a passworded hotfixed server using a pre-hotfix client, may result in a crash (please be patient while everyone updates their data).</li>
<li>Consider using the Steam client option to verify the integrity of the local game cache to avoid corrupted data after downloading this update.</li>
<li>Consider defragmenting your HDD after downloading large updates.</li>
<li>A Legacy Build Steam branch is available for advanced users. It contains the previous significant main branch version (1.40). It can be used to compare specific changes between major releases. The access code for this branch is: Arma3Legacy140</li>
<li>You can find the servers in the Steam library (switch the filter to "Tools") - "Arma 3 Server" (based on your OS, it will download the Windows or Linux version).
<ul>
<li>Administrators can also use the command-line SteamCMD utility. The app ID is to be 233780.</li>
<li>NVIDIA GameWorks™ Technology provided under license from NVIDIA Corporation. Copyright © 2002-2015 NVIDIA Corporation. All rights reserved.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>

<h4>CHANGELOG</h4>

<p><strong>DATA:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Fixed: End Game would not end on Dedicated Servers correctly</li>
<li>Added: Set up proper values for 'permanent recoil' in deployment</li>
<li>Fixed: Adjusted geometry of the lowest VR block</li>
<li>Fixed: Digital Deluxe Edition soundtrack file-name and meta-data of 1 Marksmen track</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>ENGINE:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Fixed: Dedicated Servers would not accept some passwords as valid for #login and serverCommand</li>
<li>Fixed: Xbox controller - digital to analog sensitivity</li>
<li>Fixed: Recoil applied incorrectly when deploy (camera was being pushed out of the FOV after many shots)</li>
<li>Fixed: Persistent effect for recoil when deployed</li>
<li>Fixed: Weapon Deployment - if players use a UAV terminal when they have deployed a weapon, they get stuck and cannot undeploy</li>
<li>Fixed: Weapon Deployment - if players are on the higher part of a building in prone deployment, and the building is destroyed, they would stay deployed in mid-air (and similarly on a vehicle that is moved away)</li>
<li>Fixed: Weapon Deployment - players were able to 'rappel' down buildings by deploying their weapon</li>
<li>Fixed: Deploying on low rocky walls caused weapon to sometimes not be able to aim right</li>
<li>Fixed: Problem with remotely controlling a laser designator and disassembling</li>
<li>Tweaked: Smoother leg transform for prone deployment</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>SERVER:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Updated: Stand-alone Windows Dedicated Server (hotfix 1.42)</li>
<li>Updated: Stand-alone Linux Dedicated Server (hotfix 1.42)
<ul>
<li>Known issue: Steam client modifies the steam_appid.txt file incorrectly. In case of issues, verify its content is: 107410
</li><li>Known issue: Sometimes the add-ons are loaded from the wrong installation (e.g. main game)</li>
<li>Try adding -mod=curator;kart;heli;mark;dlcbundle to your arma3server.exe shortcut</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>

<hr />
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Squad Hipfire Accuracy</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/36413/squad-hipfire-accuracy</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 01:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpl. Mendoza</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">36413@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>As it turns out, every weapon in the game has a <strong>PRESET</strong> <strong>CONSISTENT</strong> point on the screen, usually below the point of aim by a fair bit, where the first bullet from hipfire will basically <strong>ALWAYS</strong> go.</p>

<p>The accuracy is essentially just a bit worse than iron sight accuracy to around 150 meters.</p>

<p>Below is a video with initial tests.</p>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://youtu.be/7feZnytNJBY">Squad Hipfire Shot Placement initial tests</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>WWII VE Day Recognition Fly Over</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/36245/wwii-ve-day-recognition-fly-over</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 16:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Sanzotera</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">36245@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>A WWII Fly Over marking VE Day will occur on May 8.<br />
The fly over will consist of 100 Vintage warplanes.  P-40, P-39, P-38, P-51, P-47, F4U, B-25 and B-17<br />
The aircraft will fly along the Potomac and across the National Mall, Washington, DC<br />
for more info visit www.WWIIflyover.org</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>How do I join?</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/25843/how-do-i-join</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 19:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Private Edward S. Ruslanovich</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">25843@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So is there an interview system or do I just log in and join the training. I can't find server/mod info for this, can someone help me out here? Much apreciated.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Squad</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/3703/squad</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 17:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>T3 Veld [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">3703@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>If anyone ever played Project Reality for BF2 it was a great mod, its basically made the game more realistic, the creators of the mod have been working on a standalone successor for some while on the Unreal Engine 4, the game has been voted one of the most popular Greenlight games until now in Steam's Greenlight service! At the moment the game is in pre-alpha state but from footage what i have seen is already looking great, basic stuff is in, but vehicles are still being developed. At the moment it's current state pretty is like Insurgency but on huge maps!</p>

<p>Official website:<br />
<a href="http://joinsquad.com" rel="nofollow">http://joinsquad.com</a></p>

<p>Official Youtube channel with development diaries: <br />
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/JoinSquad" rel="nofollow">https://www.youtube.com/user/JoinSquad</a></p>

<p>Greenlight Page:<br />
<a href="http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=402654862" rel="nofollow">http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=402654862</a></p>

<p>Half hour long of well known youtuber DevilDogGamer playing the game with a developer:<br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-yF_5XdhBhRc?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yF_5XdhBhRc"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/yF_5XdhBhRc/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p><strong>EDIT:</strong><br />
A Kickstarter campaign will start at the end of the week:<br />
<a href="http://joinsquad.com/readArticle?articleId=24" rel="nofollow">http://joinsquad.com/readArticle?articleId=24</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Discord</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/33095/discord</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Private Colt T. Hopkins</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">33095@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Is there a Discord for the 29th, or a specific reason we don't have one? I've found they tend to help with recruiting, as you can lock channels to enlistments, promote comraderie, as you lock channels to each soldiers unit. They're quick, and easy to maintain, as well. I could easily maintain a discord server for a group of this size.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Rising Storm 2: Vietnam</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/4453/rising-storm-2-vietnam</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 02:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>T3 Veld [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">4453@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Seems the next DLC/standalone will be taking place in the Vietnam era!</p>

<p><span data-youtube="youtube-yBYMluk3R4s?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yBYMluk3R4s"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/yBYMluk3R4s/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Hey 29th!</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/20466/hey-29th</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 02:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Pak</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">20466@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>29th, I just want to say hello.   I'm amazed with the progress this unit has made. I've been logging on DH the past week and it blows my mind how organized and active our players are to this day.  I just want to drop by and give major props to Wilson for the success he gave to the 29th. If it wasn't for Wilson, none of this would be here and that's a fact.  I've been married now for 5 years, with a good career in Geotechnical Engineering.  If there's anything I can do for the 29th, I will be here to support you all.  Much Love to my brethren, Tony Pak</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>ZeuSaturday Public Event WARNOs</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/20847/zeusaturday-public-event-warnos</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 20:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>CSM Conrad</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">20847@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="http://i.imgur.com/hxbWVBN.png" alt="" title="" /></div><br />
<br />

<blockquote><div>
  <p><strong>What <u>IS</u> ZeuSaturday?</strong><br />
  ZeuSaturday is a new, non-mandatory event housing time slot designed to create an opportunity for all members of the 29th community to engage in a variety of ZEUS Co-Op and PvP missions in ARMA3, curated by members of the 29th community. It is a constructive creative space where members can participate in a variety of well constructed scenarios and enjoy running missions with and for their friends.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p>ZeuSaturday will start at 4PM EST/9PM GMT on Saturdays in the 29th A3 Battalion Server. It is our intent to hold a ZeuSaturday event at the same time and day each week, though availability of Zeuses and unit interest will determine our final schedule consistency.</p>

<p>While the exact content of each ZeuSaturday will vary from week to week, you will be able to consistently expect an approved mission being conducted by a Zeus from within the unit. Things like mission location, faction, weapon restrictions, and mod requirements may vary from week to week depending on the Zeus in control or the server being used.</p>

<p><em>Mid Post TL;DR<br />
Who: Anyone - 29th Members or Non Members<br />
What: ARMA3 Zeus Missions by 29th Members<br />
When: Saturdays at 4 EST/9 GMT<br />
Where: 29th A3 Battalion Server<br />
Why: Because Zeus is fun for me and so is playing games with 29thers.</em></p>

<p>The flagship campaign for ZeuSaturday is Operation Typhon, a Cooperative campaign on Altis run by yours truly and PFC Vogel of CP1. (And also probably other people as the campaign progresses). More details to follow on Operation Typhon as the situation with Russian forces develops.</p>

<p>While this event is NOT restricted to only 29th members! It is our hope that you will invite public players to expand our community presence and participate in these events.</p>

<p><strong>If you are interested in curating a session of ZeuSaturday, please contact me directly so your mission can be vetted prior to making it an official ZeuSaturday mission of the week.</strong></p>

<p>I'm looking forward to seeing a large turnout from all companies to make this event a consistent success. If you've never had the pleasure of taking part in a large scale, coordinated Co-Op or PvP mission, I can assure you it is something mighty to behold and a ton of fun too.</p>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/PF94BEk.png" alt="" title="" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Rising Storm 2 tunnel maps [WIP]</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/25270/rising-storm-2-tunnel-maps-wip</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 23:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC S. Cooper [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">25270@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Here are maps of the tunnels in Cu Chi and other maps [WIP]</p>

<p>These maps are for all players.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>I applied for &quot;Member ship&quot; how will I know if I get in or not.</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/25075/i-applied-for-member-ship-how-will-i-know-if-i-get-in-or-not</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 02:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Bryce Q. Howard</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">25075@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Also is there any mods I should install or nah.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Problem with Darkest Hours</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/22631/problem-with-darkest-hours</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 22:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Argent</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">22631@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello people!! when i try to enter the game, i only see one server!! why??? someone can help me please??? thx boys!!!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Darkest Hour 8.0</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/21521/darkest-hour-8-0</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 13:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Morra [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">21521@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Just wondering what others thing of this new release. I played the Beta version yesterday, mixed feelings. I guess that is I am so use to the older versions whereas this one no doubt has changed the game play look and feel. <br />
I watched the vids on the different changes.</p>

<p><strong>The Squad</strong>: I can see things like the "squad" being a plus to keep people interested in the game for a spell in a open server. But it needs to be limited to whom can use in "open" game play to bring the look and feel of a realistic battle. Also it should be linked to someone on the field who is in charge, otherwise you just have  abuch of players in different squads popping in and out on the field. Communication is key and a better system of communicating is needed. I know there is TS and the others, but some sort of better in game system needs to be established to allow everyone on the one side to know what the hell is going on. lol Which leads me to where it can be fun and effective in both changing the game play and course of a battle. 29th realism scrims. From assigning players to a squad to controlling your squad on the battlefield to establishing strongholds, this no doubt can be a major plus to the realism scrimmages. During such a scrim, both sides have a more organized "communications" during the battle. Big plus.</p>

<p><strong>The ability to turn off kill message on right side</strong>:<br />
Always was a hot debate over the years. If your going to turn it off, some sort of "hit" or"flashing red light" should happen as you shoot a target. I found myself going back to the score board to see if I even killed the person. Now some will say you can see them die, well not all the time. I have taken out targets where you can only see a speck. That spec remains for a few seconds till the server removes it.</p>

<p>Well I will go now. Would love to hear what others think about the differences in the new release. What works, what doesn't and what can/should be fixed. BTW these thoughts above may be correct or wrong, I have not really played enough of 8.0 to totally get it.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Custom maps in RS2.</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/21257/custom-maps-in-rs2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 06:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Lemonater47</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">21257@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So by the looks of things the 29th is coming to RS2 properly. With all the recruitment threads and one of your servers ranks going from around 60th all the way to 5th in a month.</p>

<p>I was thinking if you'd maybe like to host custom maps. As the 29th have always been accepting of custom content. If so contact me and I will link the necessary admins to a discord server where they can get notified of custom content updates. The modding community is much more organised than what it was in RO2.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Need Help/Info on game server type stuff</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19788/need-help-info-on-game-server-type-stuff</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 18:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Player</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19788@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So i'm trying to add some custom sounds on my small 16 player sound testing server.</p>

<p>Can someone give me useful info how to do this and where to add the fast download links in the correct .ini file?</p>

<p>Thank you for any help.</p>

<p>Do I replace the stock file weapon "Dhweaponsounds" pack with my modified custom pack?<br />
<img src="https://s2.postimg.org/ok55q4feh/Screenshot_1.png" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p>Is the correct .ini file where I go to add the fast download link?<br />
<img src="https://s2.postimg.org/cwb3vkq9l/Screenshot_2.png" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p>Is the fast download?<br />
<img src="https://s2.postimg.org/5hls374e1/Screenshot_3.png" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Can't run Darkest Hour Crash on Launch</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19739/cant-run-darkest-hour-crash-on-launch</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 23:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>taxidriver</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19739@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sorry if i am violating some sort of rule with this post but i really dont know where else to go. I've been trying to run the game for months now with no luck. Used to be a very active player but now whenever i attempt to run the game i get this message:<br />
 Build RedOrchestra_Build_[2005-11-27_10.48]</p>

<p>OS: Windows NT 6.1 (Build: 7601)<br />
CPU: GenuineIntel PentiumPro-class processor @ 2395 MHz with 4095MB RAM<br />
Video: No Video</p>

<p>Can't find 'ini:Engine.Engine.GameEngine' in configuration file</p>

<p>History: UObject::SafeLoadError &lt;- UObject::StaticLoadClass &lt;- InitEngine &lt;- FMallocWindows::Free &lt;- FMallocWindows::Free</p>

<p>I have tried deleting and uninstalling, verifying the game cache, and whatever else i knew how to do. I really want to get back on DH so if anyone knows a solution i'd really appreciate it.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Weird Glitch SUPERMAN  :) Hill 400 (witnessed by Rafterman)[DH]</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19649/weird-glitch-superman-hill-400-witnessed-by-rafterman-dh</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>SirMax007</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19649@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Battalion Server Hill 400  Wednesday 16th August 00:20 hours GMT<br />
Hi 29th buddies, I thought you would want to know that I experienced a weird glitch whilst playing the Hill 400 map. I was in the role of sniper on the Allied side and, after watching your Youtube Tutorials, I followed your advice and took cover behind trees. I took multiple shots from one player without any damage and then another player (Rafterman) reported he had walked up to me and fired 2 shots at point blank range. I stayed alive and did not hear the shots at all. Hopefully you will remember I was an ADMIN for JR for years and would never cheat (hey I'm a tanker - just notice my terrible scores as infantry <img src="https://vanilla.29th.org/resources/emoji/smile.png" title=":)" alt=":)" height="20" />. This glitch only happened for about a minute or so and not prior to this occasion. Anyway, after this I avoided taking cover behind trees and of course then got shot a lot. Just wanted to raise this in the interests of transparency. Many thanks for the server, SirMax007 (previously [JR]SirMax007-MP ).</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Film</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19180/film</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 04:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Quinton J. Dai</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19180@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I would like to request something unique from the 29th Division. I heard this group has the most austere discipline out of any I heard of, so I was wondering, with your permission to use several of your players as well as some who have decent editing skills to create a film for Rising Storm 2. If you have a channel, you can use the video. Thank you very much for your time reading this message, if you have any requests or suggestions you would like to make, please respond back!</p>

<p>Very Respectfully,</p>

<p>Dai</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Friend had an accident</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19163/friend-had-an-accident</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 21:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Carlson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19163@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey everybody, My buddy Jake was recently involved in a car accident and suffered a traumatic brain injury, due to his living situation money is gonna be tight so we started up a gofundme to help his mother out with expenses, anything you can donate would be really appreciated.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Need a map put up for testing on battalion server for darkest hour</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18934/need-a-map-put-up-for-testing-on-battalion-server-for-darkest-hour</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 00:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Player</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18934@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This is deth btw.</p>

<p>Its been playtested, all the caps and spawns work.</p>

<p>Axis<br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-JmJ4SF4EFsA?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JmJ4SF4EFsA"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/JmJ4SF4EFsA/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>Allies<br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-CEPXxqqwKO8?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CEPXxqqwKO8"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/CEPXxqqwKO8/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>I have it zipped in a 4 mb file on my google drive.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The 29th in Rising Storm 2</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18615/the-29th-in-rising-storm-2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 10:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>Lemonater47</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18615@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So what is the 29th IDs stance on said game? Haven't really seen anything about it.</p>

<p>The Reason why I ask is because 32v32 scrims are possible. There are a number of groups capable of doing it particularly in North America. It's something I'd very much like to see happen.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>73rd Anniversary of D-Day</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18537/73rd-anniversary-of-d-day</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 15:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Laird [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18537@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Today, June 6th, marks the 73rd anniversary of the Normandy landings during World War Two, a very important landing operation part of the Allied invasion of Normandy, also being the largest seaborne invasion in history. This operation began the liberation of northwestern Europe which was currently under Nazi control. This ultimately contributed hugely to the Allied victory on the Western front. Today we remember the efforts of those involved in protecting our democracy and freedom, and the real-life 29th Infantry Division who were involved in the landing on Omaha Beach.</p>

<p>If you'd like to learn more about D-Day, I suggest you visit the <a rel="nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Normandy_landings">Wikipedia page</a> or <a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/discussion/18522/the-memorial-of-d-day">this recent article</a> written by our very own Pvt. Valitutto.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>MS Fundraiser</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18443/ms-fundraiser</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 20:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC McDonough</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18443@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello everyone, Myself and a few of my friends have entered into a fundraising event for multiple sclerosis. If you know anyone who has suffered through this terrible affliction or even know some side effects, you know a cure should be found ASAP. My current goal is 60 dollars(mandatory to participate in the actual event), but I will cover the cost if I don't reach that goal. All donations help, so if you got some loose change to spare I would appreciate every penny.</p>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://mssoc.convio.net/site/TR/MiscEvents/General?px=2724265&amp;pg=personal&amp;fr_id=5789">Here is the link to my donation page</a></p>

<p>In case you are curious about MS and looking for more info here is Multiple Sclerosis Society of Canada's website: <a href="https://mssociety.ca/about-ms/what-is-ms" rel="nofollow">https://mssociety.ca/about-ms/what-is-ms</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Memorial Day</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18403/memorial-day</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 16:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Plumbley [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18403@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Memorial Day is a day to remember those who lost their lives while serving in the armed forces of the United States. It is important to remember the sacrifices of those brave men and women.</p>

<p>Lest we forget.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Would there some MG-2 class (ammo guy) in RO1/DH reasonable?</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/13953/would-there-some-mg-2-class-ammo-guy-in-ro1-dh-reasonable</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 08:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>K98_Schuetze</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">13953@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello guys,</p>

<p>since the great update DH got this year, I'm seeing a more realistic, but not game-changing class possible.<br />
The MG-2 ammo guy (as the position for the MG was in a german squad named as MG-1).</p>

<p>Possible equipment: <br />
K98 with 8 clips, 2 nades, binacular and the possiblity to give 3x ammo for a MG and after resupply on some supply spot only 2x ammo giving for MG.</p>

<p>The often heared call "no ammo left/I need ammo!" could decrease and teamplay cound be honored by such an implementation.<br />
In ideal games I see mortar-spotter and mortar-operator, officer and radio-man, vehicle crews and squads working together.<br />
Why not a MG?</p>

<p>What do you think guys?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>ANZAC Day</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/17896/anzac-day</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 18:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC de Crom [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">17896@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>For those of you that don't know ANZAC stand for Australian and New Zealand Army Corps the ANZAC which if they are known at all are mostly remembered for the battle of gallipoli yet the ANZAC served in the First World War in many more places like west-flanders,palestine and france.<br />
In the Second World War they fought in Ethiopië,Egypt,North-Africa,italy and dont forget the South West Pacific.<br />
During the 60s they where deployed in vietnam along side of the americans.<br />
basically wherever the environment wants to kill you as mutch as the enemy you will find the officers and men of the ANZAC</p>

<p>ANZAC day is a remembrance of the ANZAC soldiers who served and died in all wars, for they are so easily forgotten (25th of April)<br />
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/pWO35GF.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>29TH DUI WW2</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/17888/29th-dui-ww2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 13:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Public Discussion</category>
        <dc:creator>CHRIS1976</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">17888@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello everybody , i am new on this forum , i recently find 2 duis , one with the capitol and bottom line yellow green so 29th mp the over one is capitol + bottom line blue and white , i have never seen it before , i don't find it on boock , it's written 29 mp on the back ???? Somebody could help me ???  i have picture but i don't manage to put it in my message</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
