<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/29th-id-dh-baker-company-deployments-and-operations/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>SUCCESSFULL - Baker Company Operation - Operation Cobra (St-Lo)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/13337/successfull-baker-company-operation-operation-cobra-st-lo</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 22:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Patty</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">13337@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><em>29TH INFANTRY DIVISION<br />
116TH REGIMENT, 1ST BN<br />
BAKER COMPANY HEADQUARTERS<br />
CPT. PATTERSON'S DESK</em></p>

<h3><strong>Campaign - Baker Company - Operation Cobra (St Lo)</strong></h3>

<hr />

<p><code>July 10th 1944 </code></p>

<p><code>Saint-Lô serves a strategic crossroads. American bombardments have caused heavy damage (up to 95% of the city is destroyed) and a high number of casualties, resulting in the city being called "The Capital of Ruins". </code></p>

<p><code>Serving as an important control point on the western area of German defences in Normandy, it has fell into the American area of operations. With the fall of St. Lo will come the opening in the lines of the German army around Caen and Falaise, which are bitterly deadlocked with the Commonwealth forces. </code></p>

<p><code>Once St. Lo is secured we can quickly exploit this opening and move South-East, linking up with the Commonwealth forces and surrounding the German Army, this will effectively end all solid resistance in France. This operation has been named 'Cobra'. </code></p>

<p><code>Baker Company are tasked with securing St. Lo. Attacking from the South-West, Baker will move it's way through the five main sectors and push the Axis out of the area, capturing the main control points and their command compound and eliminating any residual resistance.</code></p>

<hr />

<p><strong>Campaign Map:</strong> <br />
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/vRDH28o.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<hr />
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>General Discussion Thread</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/13341/general-discussion-thread</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 23:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Patty</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">13341@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Informal discussions and chat about the campaign including wishes of good luck and congratulations can go here.</p>

<p>Any opposing units can also view this thread and post here.</p>

<p>Ill start by wishing BP3 good luck in the upcoming round of the campaign!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Rules and Dates</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/13340/rules-and-dates</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 23:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Patty</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">13340@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<h3>Dates:</h3>

<p><strong>22nd August</strong><br />
<em>BP3 vs 2.FJ <br />
<a href="http://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/494653450005519474/385C8B4A10C9271EC315286F17F4B434B4DED0C4/" rel="nofollow">http://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/494653450005519474/385C8B4A10C9271EC315286F17F4B434B4DED0C4/</a><br />
(bp3 starts in the red area, 2FJ green)<br />
St-Lo Campaign <br />
8pm EST <br />
Caen <br />
Objectives: West, North and South Junctions.<br />
30 min round. <br />
BP3 will not recieve half-tracks. <br />
Standard scrim rules.</em><br />
A/A 2 rounds winner from 1st round defends in second.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><strong>Saturday 27th August</strong><br />
_BP2 vs 2.FJ <br />
St. Lo Campaign <br />
Falaise<br />
A/A<br />
Allies start in se spawn<br />
map limits<br />
8pm gmt</p>

<p><br /></p>

<hr />

<p><br /></p>

<h3>Scrim rules</h3>

<blockquote><div>
<pre><code>The same basic Rules will be applied:

No Trash-talking, No Ghosting, No Boosting, No Hacking, No Map exploits, No Dead talking, No Weapon Cloning.

Weapon / Vehicle restrictions, start locations and time limits must always be observed.

Each team can bring a maximum of 32 players to a battle, forces should be even by +/- 2 people. 

Date &amp; Times will always be in this thread.

Where: 29th ID Euro / Company Server

Maps, Objectives, Time-limits and Start locations will be announced in this thread. 
</code></pre>
  
  <p>Weaponry: Map limits.</p>
</div></blockquote>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>SUCCESSFUL - Baker Company Campaign - Operation Neptune (D-Day)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/1828/successful-baker-company-campaign-operation-neptune-d-day</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 17:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations</category>
        <dc:creator>Col. Wheatley</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">1828@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<h3><strong>Official Announcement: Campaign BP2 vs Grenadier Regiment 559 &amp; 2.SS Panzer Division 'Das Reich'</strong></h3>

<p><em>29TH INFANTRY DIVISION<br />
116TH REGIMENT, 1ST BN<br />
BAKER COMPANY HEADQUARTERS<br />
1LT. PATTERSON'S DESK</em></p>

<p>0900 Hours, 6th of June 1944.</p>

<p>Men of the 29th ID,</p>

<p>After the single largest amphibious landing in human history on the beaches of Normandy, the German forces have been caught off guard, expecting a landing at the Pas-de Calais. Unable to contain the Allied beachhead rapidly being established; the Regiments of the Wehrmacht and SS are all that stand between the 29th ID and other Allied divisions that are amassing on the beaches of northern France.</p>

<p>June the 6th, 1944, at 0630 Hours. The American 29th Infantry division, had landed at the section of beach codenamed ‘Omaha’ held by the German  Infanterie-Division.352.  By 9 o’clock  a small beachhead has been established at massive cost to the Allies. In the course of the fighting the 1st and 29th divisions suffered some 2,000 casualties.</p>

<p>‘Dog Green Sector’ is the name given to the small sub-section of the beach designated for the 1st Battalion, 116th regiment of the 29th ID to assault. Due to dispersal of the landings only Able Company managed to land in the intended area and suffered heavy casualties, almost resulting in the total loss of the Company… Trapped on the beach behind obstacles and heavy accurate MG fire, the company was decimated; losing two thirds of the companies strength. Of the 101 Able Co. men that set off from England, over 90 would become battlefield casualties.</p>

<p>By 9 o’clock the situation has improved and the other companies of the Battalion including B Company ‘Baker’,  who had initially landed off course had used this to their advantage to flank the German positions, assaulting the bluffs of the German 352nd ID from the sides, relieving the pressure on the units who were still pinned on the beach.</p>

<h3><strong>First Encounter: ‘Establishing the Beachhead’</strong></h3>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Now linked up with the survivors of Able Company at the sea wall, Baker Company, Second Platoon have been tasked with moving inland into the nearby village of Vierville Sur-Mer to repel a likely counter attack from the 352nd ID.</p>
  
  <p>BP2 must move to secure a key crossroads in the village overlooking the only road up the steep cliffs in the sector. Until  this crossroads is taken we can not move trucks and Armour up the road without fear of German ambushes from the buildings and bunkers overlooking it.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p><strong>1Lt. Patterson,</strong><br />
<strong>Commanding Officer,</strong><br />
<strong>Baker Company.</strong></p>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/MJ0KfcN.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/WdxGSXO.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/MvVUWdJ.jpg&quot;" alt="enter image description here" /><br />
<img src="https://public-sn3301.files.1drv.com/y2pk1M7rPCyIr3J_c6IDHvi0iJHbomR6jVRhSheb3yTR39EWoCvjTSzY-g62G5RyOeXm-YQmix2gq4pZzxE-KQajIZ4zfYRE2BfZFRjGH1O8lw/Campaign%20Map%20with%20Header.jpg?psid=1" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/VC3cfCF.png" alt="image" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Historical Information: Background Reading</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/1879/historical-information-background-reading</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 23:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Patty</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">1879@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Here is some information for the real Baker Company we portray (B Company 1st Bat, 116th Reg, 29th ID.): <a href="http://www.29infantrydivision.org/WWII-Documents/29th_Division-116th_Regiment-1st_Bn-B_Company-Group_Critique_Notes.html" rel="nofollow">http://www.29infantrydivision.org/WWII-Documents/29th_Division-116th_Regiment-1st_Bn-B_Company-Group_Critique_Notes.html</a></p>

<p>If anyone else has some interesting reads / info related to the Campaign feel free to post it up here.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>SUCCESSFUL - BP3 Deployment:  Vierville</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/6761/successful-bp3-deployment-vierville</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 20:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>29th ID DH Baker Company Deployments and Operations</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Patty</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">6761@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<h3><strong>Official Scrimmage BP3 vs [6Dyw]</strong></h3>

<p><em>29TH INFANTRY DIVISION<br />
116TH REGIMENT, 1ST BN<br />
BAKER COMPANY HEADQUARTERS<br />
CPT. PATTERSON'S DESK</em></p>

<p>Men of the 29th ID,</p>

<p>After a hard push in land we have managed to push back the Nazi invaders and establish ourselves a beachhead. We have fought hard and proven ourselves the premier fighting force in Normandy.</p>

<p>However a situation has been developing in our rear lines near the village of Vierville. A small platoon sized force of Germans has infiltrated the area and is holding up our supply lines.</p>

<p>Ordinarily we would send our own troops to deal with this minor threat, however Army HQ have decided to let a joint group of Free Polish and Canadian Airborne forces deal with the Axis.</p>

<p>This obvious meddling is as much of an iritation to us in Company HQ as I am sure it is to all of you. We find it unaceptable that this rag tag force is being sent to clear out an enemy in our own sector, especially after our own  impressive record.</p>

<p>I have recieved intel that the Axis force may be better equipped then previously expected, and this shabby force being sent to deal with them may not be enough to push them out the area entirely. When these airborne guys fail to clear out the Nazi's the 29th will most likely be called in to fix the issue ourselves, proving once more the dominance of our units and ending any future interference from the limeys.</p>

<p><img src="http://www.29th.org/sigs/76561198010731679.png" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
Cpt. Elliott L. Patterson<br />
Company Commander<br />
Baker Company HQ<br />
<br /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
