<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Server Feedback — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>Server Feedback — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/server-feedback/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>RS2 Queue Skip</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44068/rs2-queue-skip</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 21:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Agee</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44068@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I think it would be cool to allow 29th members a priority in joining 29th servers in which non-29th members would be kicked to make room for 29th members. Kind of like how Mr. Ded's servers work if you have seen it.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>RS2 Server Friendly Fire Kick Limit for commander Needs Addressing (unplayable)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/27285/rs2-server-friendly-fire-kick-limit-for-commander-needs-addressing-unplayable</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 21:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Donger Vision</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">27285@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Can I ask, how frustrating would it be to be in a match/round in your favourite mp game and having played for a long time the match is nearly coming to an end and perhaps your sides winning due to your smart decision making, you've netted yourself a lot of kills and exp and then suddenly your <strong>kicked</strong> from the game because one lvl 7 monkey runs into the big obvious red fire support marker and gets obliterated and he doesn't forgive you to be spiteful and asinine or doesn't even know said feature even exists, (which is ridiculously common) and he has done the same thing 3 other people have done before him. How is that fun or fair I ask you? it legitimately felt like the <strong>TK kick limit</strong> was from  <strong>3-5 TK's</strong> and as a <strong>commander</strong> even being extremely cautious in your use of fire support is near impossible to not reach thus making the role of commander unplayable. Why would you want to play as commander knowing your going to be kicked from the game because some new person doesn't know the F1 prompt is present in the bottom left corner until the end of the match or some stupid person chooses to run through the incoming fire support in the the enemy's lines.</p>

<p><strong>If anyone has the ability to increase the TK limit for the commander role on your servers I implore you to do it because this feels like a mistake and right now the role may as well be removed.</strong></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Enlistment problems</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/38859/enlistment-problems</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit John N. Danielson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">38859@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello! I was having trouble getting the website to load my enlistment form.  I was able to make an account, however, I am not able to find a form while signed in.  Without being signed in, I have tried to make a new account, and enlist; but I am still unable to get the form to load.  Is there anyway we can remedy this issue?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Arma 3 Battalion Server - Questions</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/27211/arma-3-battalion-server-questions</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Private, First Class Chase H. Pendleton</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">27211@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey everyone, long time no see <img src="https://vanilla.29th.org/resources/emoji/wink.png" title=";)" alt=";)" height="20" />. I had some quick questions regarding the A3 server, I've trolled about the forums with no solid answers.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Are you all still active on A3? If so, what times can I catch y'all on for some pub play?</p></li>
<li><p>Is there a masterlist of mods needed to play on the server?</p></li>
<li><p>Are the required mods all available on the steam workshop or do I have to venture elsewhere to get them in order to play on your servers?</p></li>
</ol>

<p>I'm finally able to run A3 pretty decently, and I figured this was the best place to start up again in Arma, hope to catch yall on!</p>

<p>EDIT: I'm also quite LOST with this game right now, I can do single player stuff but I'm in over my head as far as multi goes... Maybe some of yall can show me the ropes if you get the chance.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Got kicked for name?</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/27239/got-kicked-for-name</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 05:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>imautistic</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">27239@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Got kicked mid-match after over 5 rounds on your server for using the name "imautistic" because it's inappropriate on your RS2 Vietnam server meanwhile people run around with actual racist names and all and aren't kicked, it's actually offensive because I am actually autistic in real life and find nothing wrong with using that as my name because I'm actually diagnosed with high functioning PDD-NOS. Not playing on your servers again, fix your admins.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>**Problem Player Reporting Thread**</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/14503/problem-player-reporting-thread</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 22:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Hill [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">14503@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Report problem players here.<br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/discussion/14504/how-do-i-report-an-issue-in-the-darkest-hour-or-ro2-rs-servers#latest">Read this post first</a></p>

<ul>
<li>Which Game Server?</li>
<li>Post must include player name and ID</li>
<li>Approximate time of occurrence (Eastern Time)</li>
<li>Any other relevant details</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Posts missing actionable details may be deleted without warning.</strong><br />
<strong>This is not a place for conversation; only reporting.</strong></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>UNDERAGE limits</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/27046/underage-limits</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 23:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Landon P. Rudolph</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">27046@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I would like to report back a problem that really should be considered, as my enlistment form was denied because I'm 14 not 15 by which I'm very mature for my age and was personally recruited not for my age but for catching the eyes of the recruiter. I personally think that others should not be denied because of age requirments, They should be trialed as the overviewers who overlook the forms don't necessarly know what the enlistee is capable of, both physically, mentally, and their personal style of Maturity.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Got kicked for friendly fire in RS2 without killing anybody</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/25917/got-kicked-for-friendly-fire-in-rs2-without-killing-anybody</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>whatthe</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">25917@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I know how FF works.  You can get kicked just for doing damage to people without killing them.  However, how do I get kicked for exceeding that limit without killing a single person?  I was doing pretty damn well and all of a sudden I'm kicked so early our team even passing the first two points.  The FF limit is way too damn low.  It's unacceptable.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Rising Storm 2 Vietnam public server. Friendly fire issue.</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/25564/the-rising-storm-2-vietnam-public-server-friendly-fire-issue</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 02:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Truffleshuffle03</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">25564@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I understand the need for friendly fire limit and I love the idea but something is broken with the 29th limit. I was playing your public server killed two enemy then boom kicked from the server saying I had done to much friendly fire but I did not shoot friendly's at all there was no teammate in that area. I had killed 1 way earlier but that was it and that was probably 10 or 20 minutes before I was kicked and just after I got two enemy dead boom kicked for friendly fire limit.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Arma 3 EXILE Server</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/20439/arma-3-exile-server</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 02:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Hill [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">20439@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Discussion and feedback related to the 29th ID's Arma 3 Exile server.</p>

<p><strong>IP:</strong>  63.251.20.66<br />
<strong>Port:</strong>  2349</p>

<h3>Rules</h3>

<ul>
<li>Be kind to the Bambies -- 5 minute safe time</li>
<li>Highest ranking 29th ID member is the current administrator.  Report issues at:  this thread</li>
<li>No building across roads, or close to trader areas.  Do not block access to safezones or access to trader areas</li>
<li>No camping outside safezones, stealing vehicles inside savezones, harassing people inside safezones, or firing in the safezones</li>
<li>No racism, excessive swearing, arguing, harassment, or political or religious discussions</li>
<li>Do not recruit for your own unit/clan in our servers</li>
</ul>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>map explotes and teleporting players??</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/19480/map-explotes-and-teleporting-players</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 07:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>hawk1s1k</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">19480@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>remelle, cater tan causeway and several others have been exploited by several players.. I have watched players appear out of to my amazement land on top of roofs. magic no its and exploit in the maps and players are using it to kill other players. if a mp or higher wants the players names I will forward it to you but will not list them in public. in the past players took advantage of donner and would go behide the map and kill players many were banned for this. I watch one player appear from on top of a roof and go thru a building to appear behide the tiger on remmelle and kill the tank and laugh about his great skill I told him that was map explot<br />
remmele map is the map one but its a new problem more players are doing it as the weeks are going by. if its legal were is the ladder</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH Varaville</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/17632/dh-varaville</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Steve McGarrett</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">17632@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sorry if this should instead be posted on the DH Steam Community forum or Darklight's GitHub page, but Varaville is a "custom map" and I don't know who authored it and can never tell if issues are map related or server related, so since I experienced the issue on your guys' server, I'll let you decide how to handle it.</p>

<p>Playing Varaville yesterday evening as the Axis Combat Engineer, I was unable to switch from the MP40 to any other weapon.  According to the role screen, the CE was supposed to have an MP40, frag grenades, smoke grenade, and satchel.  I tried all sorts of things and nothing worked.  I tried switching weapons by both using the scroll wheel and hot key selection, tried dropping the MP40 and picking up a different primary weapon, re-spawning, and also changing classes and changing back.  It wouldn't let me pick up additional grenades and I did notice that when I died, all the weapons I was supposed to have did drop to the ground.  This continued even after the spawn points changed when the Allies advanced.  One of the other Axis players seemed to indicate this was something he'd experienced before on this map.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Addition of maps (Darkest Hour)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/9931/addition-of-maps-darkest-hour</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 18:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Pvt. Papp [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">9931@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello all,</p>

<p>I am curious if there are any plans to add maps to the roster on 29th servers. One such map that came to mind was Omaha Beach, and Pointe-du-Hoc i cannot remember if they have ever been on DH but i have noticed that ever since 6.0 many maps have come off of the roster. Thanks for looking.</p>

<p>Papp</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Problem With Stavelot (Post 7.2 update)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/16948/problem-with-stavelot-post-7-2-update</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 17:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Steve McGarrett</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">16948@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Looks like the Stavelot map may be slightly broken right now, unless it was a glitch.  Once the Axis captured Abbey Road and Lake Road, no more objectives became available and the map just played until time expired with no more cap zones.  This just finished minutes ago (March 23, 1145 CST).</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH Battalion Maps</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/16245/dh-battalion-maps</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Olaf Steiner</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">16245@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>There are two maps for Berlin, DH-Kriegstadt and DH-Moltke Bridge. Probably should remove Moltke Bridge. People vote for it not realizing it's Berlin.</p>

<p>On the topic of Bridge though, please bring back Bridgehead. It's the pinnacle of DH, good combined arms.</p>

<p>I also suggest removing Forest - it's a server killer.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>How do I report an Issue Involving Another Player in the Darkest Hour or RO2/RS Servers?</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/14504/how-do-i-report-an-issue-involving-another-player-in-the-darkest-hour-or-ro2-rs-servers</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 22:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Hill [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">14504@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes you may encounter some troublesome players while playing on the DH or RO2/RS server.  Here are some methods and the steps for reporting a problem player.</p>

<p>The methods below are the best way to expedite an investigation into your report. Individual threads created regarding issues on a server will be closed and may not be addressed.</p>

<h3>Most important First Step</h3>

<p>Whenever you encounter a problematic player, always make sure to use the <code>listplayers</code><sup>DH</sup> or <code>playerlist</code><sup>RO2/RS</sup> command in the console.</p>

<h5>Darkest Hour</h5>

<ol>
<li>Press the <code>~</code> key</li>
<li>type <code>LISTPLAYERS</code></li>
<li>Press Enter</li>
<li>Use Page up and Page Down to scroll through</li>
<li>Record their ROID and name<br /></li>
</ol>

<h5>Red Orchestra 2 / Rising Storm</h5>

<ol>
<li>Press the <code>~</code> key</li>
<li>type <code>PLAYERLIST</code></li>
<li>Press Enter</li>
<li>Use Page up and Page Down to scroll through</li>
<li>Record their ROID and name<br /></li>
</ol>

<p><strong>This helps us greatly when dealing with your report.</strong></p>

<hr />

<hr />

<h4>Contact a Server Admin (NCO or Officer) via Teamspeak</h4>

<p><strong>Contact any NCO (Cpl. and higher) and they can assist you.</strong></p>

<ul>
<li><p>Please have the player's name and ROID available when contacting a member via Teamspeak</p></li>
<li><p>IP:Port</p>

<ul>
<li>63.251.20.99:35750</li>
</ul></li>
<li><p>Password</p>

<ul>
<li>29th</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>

<hr />

<hr />

<h4>Post The Offender's Name and ID in the Problem Player Reporting Thread</h4>

<p>We have a <a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/discussion/14503/problem-player-reporting-thread">dedicated thread</a> to report problem players.  <strong>This method is not as fast as utilizing Teamspeak (above)</strong></p>

<ul>
<li><a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/discussion/14503/problem-player-reporting-thread">Problem Player Reporting Thread</a>

<ul>
<li>Which Game Server?</li>
<li>Post must include player name and ID</li>
<li>Approximate time of occurrence (Eastern Time)</li>
<li>Any other relevant details</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Posts missing actionable details may be deleted without warning.</strong></p>

<hr />

<hr />

<h4>Send a Private Message to a member of our MP Corps</h4>

<p>Failing action via one of the above methods or if an occurrence is involving a 29th member we encourage you to send a private message on these forums to any member of the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/MP">MP Corps</a>.</p>

<ul>
<li>Click on the name of the member you'd like to contact at the link above.</li>
<li>Click <code>View Profile</code></li>
<li>Click <code>Message</code> (next to the service jacket)</li>
</ul>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH: Battalion vs Euro Server</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/11733/dh-battalion-vs-euro-server</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>clochi</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">11733@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey guys,</p>

<p>first of all a big thanks for keeping Darkest Hour alive!</p>

<p>I was wondering if u could open up the euro server and use the battalion server for your private drills.</p>

<p>If battalion is full, everyone has a ping around 200ms. On euro server, the pings were always fine.<br />
This would increase the fun a lot.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH Technical problem-  issue with my HUD</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/11807/dh-technical-problem-issue-with-my-hud</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 21:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Krzysztof J. Caffie</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">11807@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello, I have been playing on this server for 19 hours and suddenly I have an issue, that my HUD is invisible, i cannot see in game chat (but i can hear voice chat). I cannot join any teams or choose any class (but there are people in server and i can spectate, watch them play). I have no idea what happened. When i join any different server, everything is fine. It is happening only in 29th id server. How could I fix it ? I really enjoyed this server and community to be honest and I miss playing in my free time with you mates.</p>

<p>(screenshots to visualize my issue):<br />
<a href="http://imgur.com/a/3R5Hi" rel="nofollow">http://imgur.com/a/3R5Hi</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH and Ticks</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/9248/dh-and-ticks</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 02:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Olaf Steiner</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">9248@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Great game impacted on certain maps by overpowered cpu.</p>

<p>If this is a 3.5 Ghz cpu, then even 56 max players is optimistic.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Map has crashed the Battalion Server [DH]</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/8749/map-has-crashed-the-battalion-server-dh</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Ewan R. Snook</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">8749@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The map Donner_beta2alt has crashed the server and won't let me connect and brings up an error message saying package "DH_GerPlayers" version mismatch. I'm not sure if its because of the new patch or simply the update</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH Battalion server not showing</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/8174/dh-battalion-server-not-showing</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 02:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Olaf Steiner</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">8174@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>It's still up (can join) but not showing in the server listing.</p>

<p>Thanks.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Can't join DH Battalion Server</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/7329/cant-join-dh-battalion-server</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 14:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Private Fernando V. Assis</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">7329@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello!</p>

<p>These last days I've been noticing that the Battalion Server has having some issues with the maps.</p>

<p>Seems that some new maps have been introduced and people can't download it (maybe a server problem or maybe just the maps simply don't work).<br />
For instance, right now "DH-Champs-d'agonie_JeepMG" is loaded and nobody can join the server.</p>

<p>So, the thing is because of these uncommon maps the Server is currently unplayable.<br />
Some of my DH friends said they having the same issue since last Monday (Oct/19).</p>

<p>Well, I don't know if a simple reset of the server would work or some deeper maintenance is needed.<br />
But it would be great to have the Battalion Server back on tracks again.</p>

<p>If some more information is needed just PM me and I'll do my best to help.</p>

<p>Thanks!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Batalion server empty</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/7332/batalion-server-empty</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 20:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>LG_Derrick</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">7332@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi !<br />
I see that there are very few players on the DH-Batalion server these last days .<br />
Why , please ?<br />
Is there a 6.0 server anywhere ?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH Server Download problem</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/7342/dh-server-download-problem</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 23:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Rhodos</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">7342@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I don't know if you already know it, but downloading on the batt-server is very slow, (by me take 2 min for 1%) since 2 days, and the server is empty. Look the last 2 days <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.gametracker.com/server_info/70.42.74.69:7757/">here</a>.<br />
<img src="http://cache.www.gametracker.com/images/graphs/server_players.php?GSID=1452945&amp;start=-1d&amp;request=09569311037193984" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH - Can't join because I cant download files fast enough</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/4806/dh-cant-join-because-i-cant-download-files-fast-enough</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 05:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>kainhall</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">4806@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>i live in montana and the fastest i can get is 6/1 megaBIT a second.</p>

<p>so i go to join the test version server ya guys have, and it starts downloading files....and it goes slow. <br />
so slow that sometimes the map is over before i can finish the download....it sucks.</p>

<p>i was able to play previously because i played regularly from the release of darkest hour. so it was only 1 or 2 files at a time.</p>

<p>ive also tired to move all the files from the "darkest hour" folder in my RO1 root folder, to the correct places in the "darkest hour dev" folder, but, it didnt seem to work, probably because everything got updated by you guys. so i would need to download the new file anyway, it seemed.....</p>

<p>anyway.... what im asking for is for you guys to zip/rar up all the extra files your server uses that players would need, and post a link to a download location.</p>

<p>i think it would help others who are making the movement from standard, to dev versions, and then to final release, and i know it would help my butt out a lot!</p>

<p>thanks</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>ARMA 3 Battalion Server - QUESTION and CHANGE have to be DONE</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/6059/arma-3-battalion-server-question-and-change-have-to-be-done</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 16:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Symptome</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">6059@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>HI ADMIN</p>

<p>First of all . I luv your server and game mod ! but I will like to have a place on your server or forum with all the rules and thing that we can control .. is there a Zeus module on this if Yes .. why we can control it to remake fresh mission like a server restart !!</p>

<p>Have question/interogation about the ARMA 3 SERVER ?</p>

<p>We need EARPLUG add .. as this game sound for vehicul is to loud we have big problem to command team on teamspeak when in a Chopper or Tank even ATV sound is so loud !! EARPLUG should be on all server !!</p>

<p>Is there Admin playing on this serve ... I saw no one !!</p>

<p>Does your server RESTART ... because I Play for 4 hours and no restart ! We need restart like every 2-3 hours to respawn map for ennemy (I play yesterday and barely all the map was Clear .. that make the game boring as their nothing to do because there no more ai)</p>

<p>Is there a way to spawn vehicul because (stupid player get in all vehicul and the put it somewhere on the map .. !! so ( No more Plane - Heli - And Tank) unless someone blow it (after walking 10 km)</p>

<p>We should have a Voting system for Night and Daytime ...because for now look like a 24hour server so if you play by night (reallife)  like me and my friends does we are stuck to play in Night ... that another boring thing .. Voting is simple and resolved this, like this we can choose with player on the server to turn to night or day went we want !</p>

<p>and other thing you should have info about the game mod on your server !!</p>

<p>Hope to have a reply from admin real soon .. as you look like a active group</p>

<p>All the change I ask are Easy to do and that gonna make the Arma3 server Very Enjoyable ... as I saw many people commin and quitting because of Static Nighttime ..(all player I saw try the /vote day... and quit after seeing that it not implemented !! <br />
Thx For ALL</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>It aint workin</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/1983/it-aint-workin</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 01:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>mal</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">1983@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi, so yeah, you need to start letting non-29thers be admins. There's plenty of trustworthy members that are there rather often that can responsibly ban.</p>

<p>Otherwise the only populated server for this game is going to crap. The dobadders know this and take full advantage of this fact. It's not 2014 anymore. The situation has changed. Give others banning power.</p>

<p>-Mal</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Putot-en-Bessin super cheap map exploit</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/5880/putot-en-bessin-super-cheap-map-exploit</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 22:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Easy_Trigger</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">5880@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi,</p>

<p>Around 17:30 Eastern Time today (August 11, 2015), I was playing as a German tanker on Putot-en-Bessin. My driver took me to a place where there was a turkey shoot of Canadian soldiers. I soon realised with horror that I was HE-ing the actual room where the Allies spawn! I stopped the spawn killing right there... but I think this version of the map must be deleted from the server, because players WILL spawn kill and exploit other defects in every map if there's no admin to stop them.</p>

<p>In general, this server can get very nasty when admins are absent...</p>

<p>-Easy Trigger</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>29th Battalion server on DH down?</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/4843/29th-battalion-server-on-dh-down</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 23:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Alan M. Ethridge</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">4843@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello, Ive been noticing lately when I get on that the 29th Battalion server and a lot of other servers will be down, but only at certain times. Can someone tell me whats going on?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH Map Problems</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/4094/dh-map-problems</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 00:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback</category>
        <dc:creator>Loosewire</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">4094@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello 29th admins,<br />
Since the new maps being introduced, the Darkest Hour Battalion server population has dramatically dropped, primarily due to maps:</p>

<p><strong>DH-Hill400DOE</strong>  -  once voted for this map cannot be loaded by <strong>ANYONE</strong>, the server population drops to 0 and everyone has to wait for the map time to run out. This effectively ends the gameplay for the entire day. This map <strong>MUST be removed</strong> from the list, it is voted regularly and has stopped the server twice this weekend and is as I am typing.</p>

<p><strong>'BloodyHell'</strong>  -   <em>1.</em> this map has a player class limit on riflemen forcing players into classes they may not know how to use (axis are meant to have fewer players than allies but this is not an issue) <br />
<em>2.</em> the map player limit is <strong>below</strong> the server player limit, this results in ~10 players being stuck in spectate for the entire map and several more unable to even spectate and being locked in the lobby.<br />
<em>3.</em> Furthermore the key satchel charge destroyable targets (the fence) are NOT destroyable, it causes players to waste time trying to blow them up and creates an inpenetrable bottleneck for the axis tank to guard, these need to be fixed or it need removing.</p>

<p>There are several other maps that either crash the server or have issues in their poor construction which I unfortunately cannot recall at this time.</p>

<p>I beg you to remove these (at least while bugs are fixed) from the map rotation or these problems will hamper the otherwise enjoyable gameplay on the server night after night.</p>

<p>Regards<br />
Long term player on your server - Loosewire</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
