<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>[Public Relations] Arma 3 — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>[Public Relations] Arma 3 — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/[public-relations]-arma-3/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>2nd Marine Raider Battalion</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/1203/2nd-marine-raider-battalion</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 22:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>Dreek</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">1203@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<blockquote><div>
  <p>TeamSpeak Information:<br />
  ts22.gameservers.com:9302</p>
  
  <p>Contact:<br />
  <a href="http://steamcommunity.com/id/Foxhole38/" rel="nofollow">http://steamcommunity.com/id/Foxhole38/</a></p>
  
  <p>Site:<br />
  <a href="http://2dmrb.enjin.com/home" rel="nofollow">http://2dmrb.enjin.com/home</a></p>
  
  <p>The 2nd Marine Special Operations Battalion has been conducting training in Arma 3 since February of 2014, and is also formerly known as the 5th Ranger Battalion from the Arma 2 Modification Invasion 1944 as well as Darkest Hour. We are performing joint operations as well as assisting with TvT/PvP scenarios.</p>
  
  <p>We've enjoyed the previous scenarios we've ran with the 29th and look forward to more in the future.</p>
  
  <p>Signed,<br />
  Master Sergeant David Anderson<br />
  Team Chief - 1MSOT<br />
  W Company<br />
  2nd Marine Special Operations Battalion</p>
</div></blockquote>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Greetings from Joint Strategic Defense Force [JSDF]</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/27671/greetings-from-joint-strategic-defense-force-jsdf</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 03:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>tub</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">27671@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello I am a rep from JSDF "Joint Strategic Defense Force" we would love to do events with you some time and am hosting a WWI event this Sat all are welcome!!!!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>242nd Nightstalkers Infantry Brigade Combat Team</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/1985/242nd-nightstalkers-infantry-brigade-combat-team</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 08:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>242nd  Nightstalkers</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">1985@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<h3>242nd Nightstalkers Infantry Brigate Combat Team</h3>

<p>Website: www.242nightstalkers.com<br />
Servers: <br />
72.5.195.222 <br />
242 Nightstalkers Operations Server<br />
Teamspeak III: 242nightstalkers.teamspeak3.com<br />
Leader: =242= CPT. Helios<br />
Contact Email(s): 242ndNightstalkers@gmail.com</p>

<p>The 242nd Nightstalkes is an infantry focused, no-nonsense ArmA 3 clan that builds a community around serious fun, skill, and interesting missions. No doubt many of you have seen us around your sever, or have participated in one of our public missions. We've found the 29th ID to be comrades in games of the highest order and hope to see many of you in future games. Here's what we play and where you'll find us.</p>

<p><strong>ArmA 3 Missions</strong><br />
-Pandora: The Insurgency<br />
-Tango Hunt (Modded)<br />
-Tango Hunt (Vanilla)<br />
-Monthly PVE Missions<br />
-DTAS<br />
-Wasteland<br />
-Benny's Capture The Island (Becti)</p>

<p><strong>Stuff that Just ain't ArmA (STAA)</strong><br />
-Mechwarrior: Online (Clan Cloud Cobra registered under Clan Wolf)<br />
-Company of Heroes II<br />
-Company of Heroes (Blitzkrieg Mod)<br />
-DotA 2<br />
-Homeworld: Remastered<br />
-Insurgency<br />
-Wargame: Red Dragon</p>

<p>We're planning on hosting more public missions and hope to see the 29th ID in game in the future.</p>

<p>-CPT. Helios, 242nd Nightstalkers.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Message from 1FROMST</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/16815/message-from-1fromst</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>USMC1stFROMST</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">16815@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello Major Whitby. This is Captain Nomad of the USMC 1st Force Reconnaissance. We are console based, specifically on Battlefield 4. We are planning on developing a second Battalion for ARMA III. We have been well aware of your team for quite some time. Our reasons for contacting you are for our own enlightenment of the more technical aspects of training on ARMA III.  We assume your command staff may be busy and possibly find it difficult to make time to teach us, however we were curious if you'd allow us to spectate and participate in one of your unit's functions, as we would like to take notes and perhaps take a little knowledge on how to run an Arma Milsim back with us. It would be great to hear back from you. Contact us through any of the links down below. We look forward to working with the 29th in the future. Thank you for your time.</p>

<p>Steam URLs:</p>

<p>2nd Lt Burns: <a href="http://steamcommunity.com/id/CallsignFury/" rel="nofollow">http://steamcommunity.com/id/CallsignFury/</a></p>

<p>Capt. Nomad: <a href="http://steamcommunity.com/id/TehWardell/" rel="nofollow">http://steamcommunity.com/id/TehWardell/</a></p>

<p>Discord: <a href="https://discordapp.com/invite/M8V9nPW" rel="nofollow">https://discordapp.com/invite/M8V9nPW</a></p>

<p>Email @ USMC1stFRbatt@hotmail.com</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Fight us in Arma 3!</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/16642/fight-us-in-arma-3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 20:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Peroni [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">16642@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/units/Sig.png" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><img src="http://i.imgur.com/txRHfmM.png" alt="poster29th" title="enter image title here" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/units/Civ.png" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></div>

<hr />

<p>Hey there! We are the <strong>29th Infantry Division: a realism based military simulation unit.</strong> We play a variety of games within our numerous companies, but ArmA 3 is what our Charlie company is based in.</p>

<p>Founded in 2005 and based on the real life 29th Infantry Division in the US Army, our unit has become immensely popular among a multitude of nations, age ranges, and player types. With over 300 dedicated, hard-working, conscientious players, ranging from Private to Lieutenant Colonel, we aim and strive to help each other achieve the greatest gaming experience they could have.</p>

<p>If you have a unit of your own or are part of one, we would be more than interested in organizing an event with you.  A scrimmage is, simply, an organised match where a certain unit battles other units under certain rules (E.g. a single life for each soldier per round). With the amount of effort each members puts into gaining experience and discipline each drill, we are certainly not a light, nor easy, fight.</p>

<p>We look forward to facing or fighting you on the battlefield.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="http://i.imgur.com/8vZgzZB.jpg" alt="poster29th" title="enter image title here" /></div>

<hr />

<p>If you would like to organize an event or require more information, please contact one of the members listed below.</p>

<blockquote><a rel="nofollow" href="http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197978319784">Sgt. Stray on Steam</a>.</blockquote>

<blockquote><a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/messages/add/Sgt.%20Stray">Message Sgt. Stray on this forum</a>.</blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<blockquote><a rel="nofollow" href="http://forums.29th.org/messages/add/Cpt.%20Hill">Message Cpt. Hill  on this forum</a>.</blockquote>

<p>Leave a message and we will get back to you as soon as is convenient.</p>

<p>Additionally, please feel free to join our Teamspeak channel if you have any questions or would like to chat with any of our staff.</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><strong>Teamspeak IP:</strong> 63.251.20.99:35750<br />
  <strong>Password:</strong> 29th</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<hr />

<p>We also have a <a rel="nofollow" href="http://steamcommunity.com/groups/29thID-A3">Steam group</a>, a <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.facebook.com/29thinfantrydivision/">Facebook page</a>, and a <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/user/29thid1/feed">Youtube channel</a> if you'd like to discover more about our division. Thank you!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Season's Greeting From 3 Commando Brigade</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/15864/seasons-greeting-from-3-commando-brigade</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 11:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>MeFirst</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">15864@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello everyone,</p>

<p>while Christmas and the coming of 2017 is still a few weeks away, we would already like to thank all units and clans that did joint operations with us. Especially regarding joint operations, 2016 was a very good year for us.</p>

<p><img src="https://abload.de/img/155j0l.png" alt="Seasons Greetings from the 3CB" title="Seasons Greetings From the 3CB" /></p>

<p>We are looking to see you again in 2017, but so far we wish you a nice Christmas, a happy holiday and all the best for 2017.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>3rd Combat Brigade</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/14407/3rd-combat-brigade</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 22:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>Selchu3CB</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">14407@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Guys here's the link to my imgur of tonight.  not many pics of us all together but hope you enjoyed yourselves.</p>

<p><a href="http://imgur.com/a/w6VJ2" rel="nofollow">http://imgur.com/a/w6VJ2</a></p>

<p>enjoy</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>MMB (Massive Milsim Battles)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/11911/mmb-massive-milsim-battles</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 18:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>MMB Frenky</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">11911@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi mates, i am here to invite you to the ARMA 3 TvT Project we are organising. So MMB is a project hosted by ARMA 3 Greek community, wich we started few weeks ago. Our main goal is to gather up as many quality english speaking squads for a good and quality TvT. Every squad wich joins gets its own squad in game, and the leader can be chosen to lead whole side if he wants. All the rest info wich you need you can get on our site ( <a href="http://www.arma3.gr/asctournaments/" rel="nofollow">http://www.arma3.gr/asctournaments/</a> ) or you can contact us directly trough our TS3 server (188.165.52.178).</p>

<p>I hope you are interested and you will join us! <img src="https://vanilla.29th.org/resources/emoji/smile.png" title=":)" alt=":)" height="20" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>8th Combat Squadron</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/10359/8th-combat-squadron</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 20:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>1LT Barthel 8CS</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">10359@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello gents!  Some of you i know, some of you i dont. Im 1LT Barthel of the 8th Combat Squadron. We are a fictionalized casual milsim unit that has no set time scheduling restraints and allows our members to come and go as they please as long as they check in under the current guidelines.</p>

<p>That being said, after some revamping lately, we have a few servers up and at the moment. We have our operations server, public server and a testing server.</p>

<p>158.69.226.18:2317  this is the ip for 8th CS Server #2 which is currently running public patrol ops. ACE 3, TFAR and CBA REQUIRED. all other mods are allowed. This is open to all and everyone is welcome. Please come in whenever u feel bored and shoot some pixels with us!</p>

<p>Voice.8thcs.org  &lt;----- our teamspeak<br />
forums.8thcs.org &lt;----- our forums</p>

<p>come check us out sometime!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>United States Air Force</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/7913/united-states-air-force</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 04:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>Pvt. Filkins [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">7913@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Air Force Realism Unit was started in October of 2015 with the intentions of creating the most realistic U.S. Air Force Simulation in ArmA bringing all aspects of the U.S. Air force into the game. The Units Started out with 5 Major Commands (Air Force Global Strike Command, Air Combat Command, Air Force Special Operations Command, Air Mobility Command, and Air Reserve Command), 8 Wings (5th Bomb Wing, 28th Bomb Wing, 91st Missile Wing, 53rd Fighter Wing, 24th Special Operations Wing, 22nd Air Refueling Wing, 436th Airlift Wing, and 403rd Reserve Wing), and 17 Groups including 7 Operation Groups which operate: B-1B Lancer, B-52 Stratofortress, F-16C Fighting Falcon, F/A-22 Raptor, F-35A Joint Strike Fighter,  A-10 Thunderbolt, F-15 Eagle, KC-135 StratoTanker, C-5 Galaxy, C-17 Globemaster III, CV-22 Osprey, C-130J Super Hercules, MC-130J Commando II, and Minuteman III ICBM(scud), 1 Security Forces Group, 7 Maintenance Groups, 1 Pararescue Group, and 1 CCT Group.</p>

<p>vs21.tserverhq.com:9225 our Teamspeak</p>

<p><a href="http://airforcerealism.enjin.com/home" rel="nofollow">http://airforcerealism.enjin.com/home</a> our website</p>

<p>SSgt E. Filkins<br />
USAF Realism Unit<br />
Unit Liaison NCOIC</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Black Widow Company</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/3702/the-black-widow-company</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 17:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>gwidion</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">3702@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello 29th! I am Gwidion from the Black Widow Company. I am actually a former 29th member from TP 304 back in the DH days. I retired as T/5 A. Davis. I just wanted to stop by and say hello and introduce you to BWC.</p>

<p>We are an organization loosely structured on the military. In regards to Arma 3, we play milsim on our server. During operations we average anywhere from 20-35 players. We are just about finished with a 5 month long campaign where we played as the U.S. 1st Cavalry Division. Our next campaign will be as NATO (most likely) in Afghanistan.</p>

<p>Anyway, you can check us out at www.the-bwc.com. We also play a host of other games.</p>

<p>Thanks!</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>25th ARAIG</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/3991/25th-araig</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 22:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>FSgt. Balzer [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">3991@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>29th Members have been invited to the join the 25th ARAIG on their Arma3 Wasteland Server!<br />
(25TH ARAIG): 198.27.67.209 port 2376</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Hello from the 7th Cav!</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/3307/hello-from-the-7th-cav</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 01:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>Nadz.S</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">3307@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello my Name is SPC Nadz.S from the 7th Cavalry<br />
I'm from S5 Public Relations section and I would love to meet up and have a chat about setting up some matches of various kinds between our groups.<br />
My personal role in the Cav is a tanker, and thus I find anything not with treads and a large gun to be deeply worthy of suspicion.</p>

<p>Unit Name: 7th Cavalry Gaming<br />
Website: <a href="http://www.7thcavalry.us/" rel="nofollow">http://www.7thcavalry.us/</a><br />
Teamspeak: IP: ts3.7thcavalry.us<br />
Password: 7thCavalry<br />
Unit Type: We are a large mixed unit but we have a bias towards infantry of various flavors (We have lots of members from US and EU timezones so we can cater for most timezones)<br />
Objective: To find and establish a network of experianced players and cement lots of good natured matches<br />
Mission: We would like to do anything from a series of OP's to one off TvT's. We have a large selection of maps and map/mod makers on hand so we can facilite most desires and certain clan wants, some clans have their own must haves and quirks some don't.</p>

<p>Throughout the year we have a number of events and would like to diversify and enhance our collective experiances, with the recent take off Kunduz, Afghanistan map within the modding fraternity and buzz of excitment for when its ready for use for groups, I would imagine mud walls will be shaking once again and would be an ideal time for joint ops of some kind.</p>

<p>Some Videos (less than offical)<br />
Operation Fenrir: Infantry SL POV Wolf <br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-F-xCxdxu9qw?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F-xCxdxu9qw"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/F-xCxdxu9qw/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>Patrol Ops: Pioneer Patrol<br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-Px852PaicMU?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Px852PaicMU"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/Px852PaicMU/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>If you want to contact myself:<br />
<a href="http://www.7thcavalry.us/user/7360-7cavspcnadzs/" rel="nofollow">http://www.7thcavalry.us/user/7360-7cavspcnadzs/</a><br />
or drop a post on the forum</p>

<p>SPC.Nadz.S</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>From Ironside International [Ix2]</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/1161/from-ironside-international-ix2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 14:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>RC Harper</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">1161@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>First and foremost, thank you very much for the invite to your Fight Night.  I know I'm speaking for everyone when I say we had a blast and will be attending again!  As mentioned after the operation, we'd like to extend an invite to the members of the 29th ID to take part in our planned operations and fun ops as well which are conducted every Saturday @ 2000CST.  Visit www.ironsideint.com and mention you're from the 29th to get Friends Of Ironside [FoI] status to get access to operations and other events.  Thanks again and we hope to see you around.</p>

<ul>
<li>Sincerely,</li>
</ul>

<p>RC "Blackburn" Harper</p>

<p>Contractor Grade 2/C-2</p>

<p>Ironside International</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Greetings from Septem Pro Vita</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/607/greetings-from-septem-pro-vita</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 21:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>[Public Relations] Arma 3</category>
        <dc:creator>SPV_Fearxmanmyth</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">607@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Just wanted to introduce myself and get in touch with the leadership of the 29th. It is nice to see other militaristic teams in arma.</p>

<p>SPV consists of only adults where roughly half of us are veterans operating in a number of FPS games. Our arma section is always looking for other teams that share our passion for milsim environments while gaming.</p>

<p>If any of the officers could contact me I would very much like to speak to you about possible future interactions between our teams.</p>

<p>We typically operate 8pm eastern and later on weekends. PM me here or send me a message on our forums at www.syndicate7.us</p>

<p>Appreciate your time thanks gents.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
