<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Promotions and Awards — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>Promotions and Awards — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/promotions-and-awards/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>Recurring Donations Awards (January-April)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44839/recurring-donations-awards-january-april</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Burg</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44839@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div>

<h3>The following list includes only those currently missing their medals/cords.</h3>

<hr />

<p>In recognition of their dedication to the unit through providing a recurring donation of $3 or more. The following members will receive the <strong>Meritorious Public Service Medal</strong>. This medal will remain on their jackets while they continue to provide contributions to the unit.</p>

<hr />

<p><strong>Charlie Co.</strong><br />
T/4 Jon C. Erb</p>

<p><strong>Dog Co.</strong><br />
PFC Luke M. Scovel<br />
PFC Mike N. McCarta<br />
Pvt. John P. Wolfe</p>

<p><strong>Easy Co.</strong><br />
PFC Jordan R. Reid<br />
PFC Jergul A. Jergulson<br />
Pvt. Sid H. Evers</p>

<p><strong>Fox Co.</strong><br />
PFC Max O. Officer<br />
Pvt. Casey Robinson</p>

<p><strong>Retired</strong><br />
Martin G. Castaneda</p>

<hr />

<p>In recognition of their dedication to the unit through providing recurring donation of 10$ or more. The following members will receive the <strong>Blue Infantry Cord</strong>. This cord is in addition to the Meritorious Public Service Medal and will remain on their jackets while they continue to provide contributions to the unit.</p>

<hr />

<p><strong>Dog Co.</strong><br />
Pvt. John P. Wolfe</p>

<p><strong>Easy Co.</strong><br />
PFC Jergul A. Jergulson<br />
Pvt. Sid H. Evers</p>

<hr />

<p><strong>The entire unit as well as the Lt. Col. thank you for your generosity. These donations help pay for the expensive forum and server costs. Every donation is without a doubt greatly appreciated.</strong><br />
<img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/bicord.png" alt="" title="Blue Infantry Cord" /> <img src="https://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/mpsm.gif" alt="" title="Meritorious Public Service Medal" /></p>

<hr />

<p></p></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Six Years and Six Months of Service (Jamie N. Stray)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44601/six-years-and-six-months-of-service-jamie-n-stray</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 20:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Ozturan</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44601@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>SSgt. Vandewalle said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>After 6 years and 6 months of active service within the 29th, it’s hard to come up with an original writing for the Army Of Occupation Medal. I wanted to go back and take a look at Lieutenant Stray's very first award, which dates back to 2010. However, this man is this old that he outlived our previous forums and thus the administration services lost these papers. It was in the year 2010 that I very first met Private Stray, in Able Company. He made a name for himself with his trusted Zook or Panzerschreck throughout the Company, before he took the route of Squad Leadership. Soon after, he moved over as a Platoon Sergeant of Able Second Platoon. And that is where we met again. Staff Sergeant Stray became Lieutenant Stray, with me running all sorts of errands for him in the HQ. We both have a big passion for World War history and the 29th ID. We both can’t live without it. It shows in the records of Lieutenant Stray, as he couldn’t resist coming back to us after a hiatus, starting off from scratch again, moving from rifleman up to Platoon Leader again. He’s always looking for ways to improve the squads or platoons he is in. Eager to learn, and eager to pass on his knowledge. And therefore it is with great honor that I present Lieutenant Stray with his thirteenth Army of Occupation Medal for his six years and six months of active service within our unit.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="Thirteenth Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Badge (George Bork)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44738/badge-george-bork</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 01:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T3 Chandonnet</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44738@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/88426">Cpl. Hanley</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/90163">PFC Bork</a> has been a fine machine gunner and an integral part of DP2S1 for a long time now. Ever since I took command of DP2S1 I have seen PFC Bork consistently develop his machine gun skills to the point where he can accomplish any task given to him, whether it is to help with suppressing fire during an assault or preventing hostile forces from flanking around an objective. PFC Bork has clearly demonstrated that he is dedicated enough to his AIT that he practices outside of drills, and as such, it is appropriate to award him his Machine Gun Marksman Badge at this time. Congratulations, PFC Bork, and I look forward to seeing even further AIT develop in the future.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/badges/marksman/machinegun.gif" alt="" title="Machine Gun Marksman Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Award (Olaf A. Baron) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44439/award-olaf-a-baron</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 21:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T3 Grimes [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44439@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/12780">SSgt. Bagge</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>During the third round of the Company drill on 03/29/2021 EP6S3 was tasked with defending the eastern part of the defensive area. <a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/86392">Cpl. Baron</a> placed his squad in the surrounding hamlet and farmland in wait for the enemy assault. The squad's position turned out to be vital to the defending team’s ultimate victory. The Russian main effort was focused right in Cpl. Barons squad’s position.<br />
  During the Russian assault EP6S3 managed to take out roughly 1/3 of the enemy team with Cpl. Baron taking out 12 Russians himself. The Cpl. Had placed himself on his squad’s easternmost flank and were right in the path of advancing infantry and picked them off one by one. During his engagement with the enemy, he constantly reported the enemy's movements and spotted the enemy BMP 2, which later got hunted down and destroyed. He, unfortunately, fell to enemy fire but was the last man in his squad to go down. Only after his death could the attackers push past his position and enter the eastern area of the objective village.<br />
  His heroic defence slowed down the Russian advance so the rest of the team could move in and finish the now battered attackers.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/bstar.gif" alt="" title="Bronze Star" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Three Years of Service (Erwan Pirou)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42867/three-years-of-service-erwan-pirou</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Valiūnas</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42867@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/88645">PFC Suárez</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Three years! Easier said than done, I can't remember the time where he was not in the center of something. He has made up to master some of the most difficult classes in game including flying a helicopter, because flying is not done with magic and a lot to effort has to be put in it. That doesn't mean <a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/87704">PFC Pirou</a> makes it seem as if was a piece of cake. Although he wants to be humble about his abilities on a ground, I'm sure most of us agree that they are not overshadowed by his flying skills. He is not just a good pilot or a good bunker cleaner, he is one of the best members to share some time and have a conversation with. Keep the skies safe and the enemy pinned down for many more to come!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><br />
<img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="6th Army of Occupation Medal" />
</div>]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Award (Furkan Akbulut) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44870/award-furkan-akbulut</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 20:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Lans</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44870@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/12780">SSgt. Bagge</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>During S1s attack round in the match against S3, <a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/87805">PFC Akbulut</a> was sent on a special mission north while the rest of the squad maneuvered south and west. While PFC Akbulut moved to his assigned position he got spotted by PFC Strickland and PFC Smith and they started engaging him to no avail. They eventually had to shift their focus south when the rest of S1 started attacking and got pinned by Strickland's MG fire. At this point Akbulut had positioned himself on a rock and expertly landed a frag rocket on top of Strickland and Smiths position killing them instantly. After this PFC Akbulut started advancing once again and eventually linked up with PFC Fletcher at the former MG nest. From this position he helped spot enemies and also killed and wounded 2 more soldiers with his remaining frag rocket. With the help of PFC Fletchers covering fire PFC Akbulut moved in and secured the objective building and dug down the objective unhindered. With his actions PFC Akbulut secured a victory for s1 and their advancement in EBOTs. <br />
  For these actions I am pleased to award PFC Akbulut an Army Commendation Medal. Congrats!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/arcom.gif" alt="" title="Army Commendation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Six Months of Service (Aksel Heidi) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44768/six-months-of-service-aksel-heidi</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 03:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Regan</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44768@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/88887">Cpl. Knight</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/90552">Heidi</a> is still relatively new to our unit but has already proved himself a skilled warrior and loyal squad member. He is quickly becoming critical to squad operations and is taking up his new AIT with a passion. In due time I will be writing Heidi yet another AOCC and I really look forward to that in the near future. I see much potential going forward, congrats on your first 6 months!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="1st Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Two Years of Service (Nathan W. Wells)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44787/two-years-of-service-nathan-w-wells</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 18:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Bae</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44787@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89734">PFC Nielsen</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Two years is a milestone in your 29th career and a time to pause and reflect. Glancing over <a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/87270">PFC Wells</a>' service record you can find many, many things - triumphs of battles won, service to the unit, and an undying spirit to JUST KEEP PUSHING. However, this is just a pit stop on the road ahead with the unit - congratulations PFC on your 4th AOCC and 1st WWI Victory Medal. We all can't wait to see what comes next for you.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<hr />

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="4th Army of Occupation Medal" /> <img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/ww1v.gif" alt="" title="1st World War I Victory Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Badge (Nathan W. Wells)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44878/badge-nathan-w-wells</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Bae</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44878@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89734">PFC Nielsen</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>POV: You are charging into a town and you hear an odd chatter of gunfire ahead of you. Not deep enough for a MG, too fast for a Pistol, but still definitely not a rifle. Confused you keep pushing forward into the town, turn the first corner and bam - there it is again right in your face and you are down. "What the heck just happened?" you think to yourself. After sprinting over to the spectator box to find out, you see PFC Wells standing over top of you SMG drawn continuing to punish your teammates with his SMG-ing skillz. I'm sure many of us in the platoon have had this experience.<br />
  For acquired dexterity with his SMG, we award PFC Wells his SMG Marksman badge.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<hr />

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/badges/marksman/smg.gif" alt="" title="Submachine Gun Marksman Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Promotion and Badges (Joey V. Tall) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44879/promotion-and-badges-joey-v-tall</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Gillespie</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44879@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/88151">Sgt. Mellinger</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>I'll be honest here, <a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/91064">Pvt. Tall</a> starting out wasn't someone who exactly stood out in terms of in-game performance. This isn't a bad thing per se, but, Tall had a lot of room for improvement like any new member of the 29th. Looking back at his performance then and now has been a complete and total change. Literally, just this past week I have seen him grow so much as a member of the 29th. He has become much more active, vocal, and motivated to be the best he can be. The highlight of his "29th career" so far is definitely his BBOTS debut. He helped us a lot with our prep and contributed a lot to our victory. He has never been in a Battle of the Squads match before and he made it look like this was just another drill. He managed to get multiple kills that night and communicated like someone who has been here for a while. I honestly can't believe how much he has grown and I have been ecstatic with that growth. I no longer think that he is fit with his current rank so, Cpl. Maestas, SSgt. Crane and I believe that he is finally ready to be awarded his first chevron and as well his Rifle Marksman Badge and Expert Infantry Badge. Congratulations PFC Tall and seriously, your growth these past few weeks has been one of the better growth periods I have seen out of any 29ther. Keep up the great work.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<hr />

<p></p><div>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/forums/29thsealheaderblack.png" alt="" title="" /></p>

<p>CERTIFICATION OF PROMOTION</p>

<p><b>TO ALL WHO SHALL SEE THESE PRESENTS, GREETING:</b></p>

<p>Know Ye, that reposing special trust and<br /> confidence in the fidelity and abilities of</p>

<p><code><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91064">Joey V. Tall</a> &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 048883185&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;FP2S2 </code></p>

<p>I do promote him to <u>Private, First Class</u> in the </p>

<p>UNITED STATES ARMY</p>

<p>to rank as such from the <u> 29th </u> day of <u> April 2021 </u>.</p>

<p>You are charged to discharge carefully and diligently the duties of the grade to which promoted and to uphold the traditions and standards of the Army.</p>

<p>Effective with this promotion you are charged to execute diligently your special skills with a high degree of technical proficiency and to maintain standards of performance, moral courage and dedication to the Army which will serve as outstanding examples to your fellow soldiers. You are charged to observe and follow the orders and directions given by superiors acting according to the law, articles and rules governing the discipline of the Army. Your unfailing trust in superiors and loyalty to your peers will significantly contribute to the readiness and honor of the United States Army.</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/forums/29thsealfooter.png" alt="" /></p>

<p></p></div>

<p><img src="http://www.29th.org/sigs/76561198004825138.png" alt="Alex W. Crane" title="Alex W. Crane" /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<hr />

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/eib.gif" alt="" title="Expert Infantry Badge" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/badges/marksman/rifle.gif" alt="" title="Rifle Marksman Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>1522nd Training Platoon</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44811/1522nd-training-platoon</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 17:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>CW4 Slomczynski</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44811@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="http://i.imgur.com/os6ArJc.png" alt="image" /></div>

<p>Congratulations to the <strong>1522nd Training Platoon</strong>.</p>

<p>You have successfully completed the Lighthouse Corps Basic Combat Training Program. You've come this far, so remember to stay active.</p>

<p>Your squad leader will contact you all shortly via PM. Best of luck to you and we hope to see you around!</p>

<p>Learn how things work in the 29th by reading the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://29th.org/wiki">29th Wiki</a></p>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91516">Private Ivan Will L. Ching</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Charlie Company, First Platoon, Second Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/CP1S2">CP1S2</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Arma 3 Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/a3.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91515">Private Frank Harper</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Charlie Company, First Platoon, First Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/CP1S1">CP1S1</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Arma 3 Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/a3.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>1527th Training Platoon</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44884/1527th-training-platoon</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>CW4 Slomczynski</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44884@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="http://i.imgur.com/os6ArJc.png" alt="image" /></div>

<p>Congratulations to the <strong>1527th Training Platoon</strong>.</p>

<p>You have successfully completed the Lighthouse Corps Basic Combat Training Program. You've come this far, so remember to stay active.</p>

<p>Your squad leader will contact you all shortly via PM. Best of luck to you and we hope to see you around!</p>

<p>Learn how things work in the 29th by reading the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://29th.org/wiki">29th Wiki</a></p>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91565">Private Tom Green</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Easy Company, Fourth Platoon, Second Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/EP4S2">EP4S2</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Squad Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/sq.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91578">Private Titus Hawkson</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Easy Company, First Platoon, First Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/EP1S1">EP1S1</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Squad Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/sq.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91554">Private Moses W. Robertson</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Easy Company, First Platoon, First Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/EP1S1">EP1S1</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Squad Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/sq.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Nine Years of Service (Didier Vandewalle)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44845/nine-years-of-service-didier-vandewalle</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 20:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Ozturan</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44845@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/4368">2Lt. Stray</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Here’s an interesting fact about the fine SSgt. Vandewalle in front of you all, and myself. He is the person to whom I have awarded the most Army of Occupation Medals to in the 29th. That is because SSgt. Vandewalle has dedicated an enormous amount of time over the past 13 years to the 29th, 9 of them in fact. It is impossible to cover the vast distance of time that he has been active in the unit, so I will speak about the last few months. During times when I had to focus on important elements of my life, the fine and capable SSgt. Vandewalle was there to fill the void without a moment's hesitation, performing his and my duties despite demands on his own time. There are rarely people in life that you know have got your back and I know without a doubt that SSgt. Vandewalle will have mine, and I, his. It is my immense pleasure to award you your 18th Army of Occupation Medal for 9 years of service, congratulations!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="18th Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Two Years of Service (Ilja Stutz)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44872/two-years-of-service-ilja-stutz</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Valiūnas</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44872@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/85251">Sgt. Miochevich</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/89051">PFC Stutz</a> has been an excellent companion, and a person who is well known to all of us in our platoon. Willing and able to take up a huge variety of duties and tasks upon himself, PFC Stutz invests a lot of time in improving himself, as well as finding ways to help the squad become better. His comments and suggestions are always of great value, and his unofficial role as "third in command" is of great importance to us all. PFC Stutz has been here with us for two years now, so it is time to award him his fourth Army of Occupation Medal, as well as his very first WWI Victory Medal. Congratulations, PFC!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><br />
<img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="4th Army of Occupation Medal" /> <img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/ww1v.gif" alt="" title="1st World War I Victory Medal" />
</div>]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Award (Samuel L. Metz)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44867/award-samuel-l-metz</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Furie</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44867@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/89978">PFC Metz</a>, during EP2S2's BBOTS match against EP2S3, made sure his contributions were noticed throughout the match. However, it was during the first round that his actions really shined through. While the rest of EP2S2 manouvered into their attacking position PFC Metz found his way to an elevated position that allowed him to cover his squad effectively. It was in this position that PFC Metz managed to pick off two defenders that had eyes on EP2S2's approach. Once the squad began its push on the objective compound PFC Metz joined the push and upon clearing a building PFC Metz was able to spy a defender working his way back to the objective and quickly took him out. At this point the leadership of EP2S2 went down and PFC Metz quickly stepped up and took leadership of the remaining attackers. While the attackers made their way to the objective an overlooking defender managed to take out one of the attackers and started firing at PFC Metz. Under fire and being one of the last 2 left for the attackers PFC Metz swiftly turned his MG to the incoming fire and eliminated the defender. By this point there was less than a minute left on the round timer and only 2 attackers left to complete the objective. PFC Metz coordinated the attackers and managed to complete the objective with less than 30 seconds on the clock. An absolutely stellar round for PFC Metz and one deserving of this Army Commendation Medal. Congrats PFC Metz!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/5173">Sgt. Minor</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>PFC Metz was the key factor for EP2S2's first victory in E/BBOTS. His callouts were on point along with predictions of possible enemy movement and locations giving the squad a chance to put effective suppression upon enemy forces. He killed 9 people over the two rounds, the exact size of EP2S3 during the fight, hampering the defensive and offensive efforts of the squad's opponents. Finally, PFC Metz managed to push through after all the squad was dead except for Pvt. Chuprina and himself on the attack round to the objective building while eliminating more hostiles, and tearing down the objective while the clock showed less than a minute of time left. Had the squad lack PFC Metz's combat and leadership skills during the fight, the victory for EP2S2 would have been uncertain.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/arcom.gif" alt="" title="Army Commendation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>1528th Training Platoon</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44883/1528th-training-platoon</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 08:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>CW4 Slomczynski</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44883@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="http://i.imgur.com/os6ArJc.png" alt="image" /></div>

<p>Congratulations to the <strong>1528th Training Platoon</strong>.</p>

<p>You have successfully completed the Lighthouse Corps Basic Combat Training Program. You've come this far, so remember to stay active.</p>

<p>Your squad leader will contact you all shortly via PM. Best of luck to you and we hope to see you around!</p>

<p>Learn how things work in the 29th by reading the <a rel="nofollow" href="http://29th.org/wiki">29th Wiki</a></p>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91574">Private Joel A. Campbell</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Easy Company, Second Platoon, Third Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/EP2S3">EP2S3</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Squad Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/sq.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/3263">Private Jareck A. Hollens</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Fox Company, Second Platoon, Third Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/FP2S3">FP2S3</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Squad Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/sq.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91557">Private Mitch C. Malone</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Fox Company, Second Platoon, First Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/FP2S1">FP2S1</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Squad Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/sq.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h3><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91560">Private Robert W. Mason</a></h3>

<ul>
<li>Assignment: Fox Company, Second Platoon, Second Squad (<a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#units/FP2S2">FP2S2</a>)</li>
<li><p>Awards: 29th ID Shoulder Patch, American Defense Service Medal, Squad Unit Participation Ribbon</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/patch.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/adef.gif" alt="image" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/small/sq.png" alt="image" /></p></li>
</ul>

<hr />
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Eleven Years and Six Months of Service (Jon C. Erb)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44877/eleven-years-and-six-months-of-service-jon-c-erb</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Bae</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44877@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/4397">Sgt. Dott</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>If there's one thing life can guarantee it’s the continual passage of time and the long-enduring cycles we all know: The sun rises and sets, the seasons breath new life into the landscape and then bring bitter cold, and T/4 Erb receives another AOCC. Much like a solstice, we can expect that in six months T/4 Erb will be here for an AOCC. You could even build a calendar based on his time here. For those curious, it is now 23 AE, which means this is his 23rd AOCC. That's eleven and a half years here in the 29th. Congratulations, T/4, and I'll see you in 24 AE.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<hr />

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="23rd Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>One Year of Service (Mitch Argerham) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44880/one-year-of-service-mitch-argerham</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Gillespie</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44880@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89105">Cpl. Guyette</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>I first met <a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/90049">PFC Argerham</a> when FP2 was just created and he was just another PFC in our squad. This quickly changed after the first couple of drills and having him lead a bit. Being ASL-less and SLT popping up, he was the perfect candidate to take up the position. Now he is taking a load off of my back and I am truly grateful to have an awesome ASL. One year down and to many more. Congrats PFC Argerham!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="2nd Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Two Years and Six Months of Service (Brendan A. Williams)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44876/two-years-and-six-months-of-service-brendan-a-williams</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 02:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Bae</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44876@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89953">PFC Montgomery</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>PFC Williams has been with the unit for about 912 days. In that time, he has honed his skills as a rifleman. His aim is true, his callouts are clear and concise, he steps up when leadership goes down, and he even volunteers to help out the new privates during drills. He is an asset to the Dirty First and a joy to work with. Congratulations on your 5th AOCC PFC, we hope to see many more to come!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<hr />

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="5th AoCC Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Badge (Julio P. Barazal)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44852/badge-julio-p-barazal</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Murray</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44852@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/89448">Cpl. Voth</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/90138">PFC Barazal</a> has been a hallmark of DP3S3 since I was assigned to the squad late last year. Punctual, capable, and always positive, he is one of the finest members of the 29th I’ve had the privilege to serve with. As the squad’s MG, he knows his role and weapons, using both to maximum efficiency to safeguard the squad and tear holes through enemy lines. When given an order, I can rely on PFC Barazal to see the job through and communicate pertinent information to squad leadership. Not only this, but he is clever enough to act on his own initiative with the absence of leadership, wreaking havoc upon anyone who dares stand in his way. As such, it is time he is given proper recognition of his skills, congratulations on your Machine Gun Marksman badge!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/badges/marksman/machinegun.gif" alt="" title="Machine Gun Marksman Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Promotion and Badge (Jacob M. Murray)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44853/promotion-and-badge-jacob-m-murray</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Murray</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44853@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/88114">Sgt. Lord</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>I guess it is that time again. <a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/91159">Private J. Murray</a> has done it again. It looks like he has proven himself yet again. I have to say in the short time that this private has been here he has left quite the impression on people and fit in like he was always here in the first place. J. Murray has been a shining star here in DP3S2 and DP3 as a whole. He is someone that all PFC should strive to be. He has been a great morale boost to the squad and a decent shot on top of all that. He has made his mark here on the platoon whether good or bad he's here to stay. Congratulations on your EIB and PFC.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<hr />

<p></p><div>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/forums/29thsealheaderblack.png" alt="" title="" /></p>

<p>CERTIFICATION OF PROMOTION</p>

<p><b>TO ALL WHO SHALL SEE THESE PRESENTS, GREETING:</b></p>

<p>Know Ye, that reposing special trust and<br /> confidence in the fidelity and abilities of</p>

<p><code><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/91159">Jacob M. Murray</a> &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;836151529&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; DP3S2</code></p>

<p>I do promote him to <u>Private, First Class</u> in the </p>

<p>UNITED STATES ARMY</p>

<p>to rank as such from the <u> 27th </u> day of <u> April 2021 </u>.</p>

<p>You are charged to discharge carefully and diligently the duties of the grade to which promoted and to uphold the traditions and standards of the Army.</p>

<p>Effective with this promotion you are charged to execute diligently your special skills with a high degree of technical proficiency and to maintain standards of performance, moral courage and dedication to the Army which will serve as outstanding examples to your fellow soldiers. You are charged to observe and follow the orders and directions given by superiors acting according to the law, articles and rules governing the discipline of the Army. Your unfailing trust in superiors and loyalty to your peers will significantly contribute to the readiness and honor of the United States Army.</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/forums/29thsealfooter.png" alt="" /></p>

<p></p></div>

<p><img src="https://www.29th.org/sigs/76561197977260351.png" alt="Matthew J. Brenholen" title="Matthew J. Brenholen" /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<hr />

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/eib.gif" alt="" title="Expert Infantry Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Badge (Ludio G. de Freitas)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44864/badge-ludio-g-de-freitas</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 01:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T3 Chandonnet</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44864@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/88426">Cpl. Hanley</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/84557">PFC de Freitas</a> is an excellent member of DP2S1. PFC de Freitas has always had a great attitude, helpful and professional, and is a brother-in-arms and friend to all. PFC de Freitas' excellence as a squad member is only matched by his effectiveness as a submachine gunner. Since I joined DP2S1 I have witness PFC de Freitas go from an average AIT user to an integral part of his squad and his platoon. PFC de Freitas can consistently eliminate groups of targets, clear buildings, and use the other equipment at a Light AIT User's disposal to make decisive and outcome-altering plays on a regular basis. PFC de Freitas' ability to go above and beyond the required level of skill expected of a Light AIT makes it necessary to award him his Submachine Gun Marksman Badge. Congratulations PFC de Freitas and I know that you will do nothing short of amazing things throughout the rest of your career in the 29th ID.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/badges/marksman/smg.gif" alt="" title="Submachine Gun Marksman Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Award (Alex S. Turner) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44856/award-alex-s-turner</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Albers</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44856@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/87263">SSgt. Gibson</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89326">PFC A. Turner</a> was part of the EP3S3 element providing covering fire for their attack in the EP3 BBOTS Championship. As the squad moved into a dangerous area on their approach, PFC Turner on their North flank began using his grenades and rifle to eliminate key enemies threatening the squad. PFC Turner killed 5 enemies in total, all of them threatening the primary squad. The biggest reason his contribution was essential to the victory is that 4 of 5 kills came within 4 minutes of the round ending when S3 was extremely behind on time. His most crucial kill came when he picked off the enemy that was charging up behind the squad and almost would have certainly ended S3's chances at victory. All in all he killed over half of the defenders when his squad was outnumbered by 2 from the beginning. For these actions I am pleased to award PFC Turner an Army Commendation Medal. Congrats!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/arcom.gif" alt="" title="Army Commendation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Six Months of Service (Robert L. Frank)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44855/six-months-of-service-robert-l-frank</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Murray</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44855@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/90108">Cpl. Wallison</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Those of you reading this who have had the pleasure of working with <a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/90564">PFC Frank</a> are probably thinking, “He’s really been around for only half a year?”. A guy like Frank fills his role as an exceptional rifleman to a T. His demeanor and skills place him in a much higher bracket than most guys with the same time put in. Frank files the spot of jack of all trades in DP3S1. Being only a rifleman and a crack shot one at that, he brings in all the things a fantastic 29ther has in tote. Confident, cool under fire, and great with communicating with the team. I can’t imagine what the squad would do without you Frank. We hope to get many more years to come. Keep being the cool, chill dude we know and love. Congratulations on your first AOCC.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="1st Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Badge (Gavin T. Wash)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44854/badge-gavin-t-wash</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Murray</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44854@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/88646">Jake Lee</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Declared on the day he joined DP3S3, <a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/91228">Pvt. Wash</a>'s bold and pressed intentions to become a platoon sniper was the first surprise. Created after witnessing some of DP3's finest in action, his promise to practice and attain that level through guesting was the second surprise. To this day, his continued commitment to that promise is the third, but hopefully not final, surprise. In every drill, Pvt. Wash showcases both his aggressive playstyle and his active communication habits. Many a round begins with Pvt. Wash leading the charge and organizing those near him. His tempo, callouts, and willingness to get into the nitty-gritty of action have been influential to victory after victory. Congratulations, Pvt. Wash! Keep up the great work!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/badges/marksman/rifle.gif" alt="" title="Rifle Marksman Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>One Year of Service (Eddie Lance) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44851/one-year-of-service-eddie-lance</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Albers</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44851@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/88596">Cpl. Hamilton</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>It's pretty crazy to think that <a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/90040">PFC Lance</a> is just now hitting his one year mark in the unit. Since he first joined, he had pretty much everything you can want in a private. He's always been skilled and gives excellent callouts but where he most impressed us was with his interest in doing more for the unit. PFC Lance took on a staff position in lighthouse and joined SLT and although it started a bit rough due to some scheduling issues, he did what he could to fix it and has been doing a great job ever since. With Lance just now reaching his one year and already making it as far as he has, I think he has a good future ahead of him in the 29th. Congrats on your second AoCC PFC Lance!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="2nd Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Six Months of Service (Reis N. Smith) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44850/six-months-of-service-reis-n-smith</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Albers</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44850@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89485">Cpl. Addante</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Oh boy <a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/90684">R. Smith</a>. The little grenadier that could, the second he grabbed his AIT I offered to give him some pointers that may help him in drills, and boy did he ask. Yet in the 3 months since he's been an AIT holder, he has certainly impressed me as well as Sgt. Mortem. He along with everyone in the squad is subject to listening to a vast line of random and questionable conversations that we get to hear, and smith may come off as one to seem shocked and questioning his existence within the squad, he's also the silent killer when it comes to adding on to said conversations always garnering a laugh from everyone. He is an absolute joy to have in the squad and cannot way to see him around for another 6 months!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="2nd Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>One Year of Service (Jarrett Lawson) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44849/one-year-of-service-jarrett-lawson</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Albers</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44849@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89485">Cpl. Addante</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>It seems like only yesterday that <a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89946">Lawson</a> had came into my squad, a light hearted and friendly guy who wanted nothing more than to dominate on the battlefield. Over the last year I feel that he has done an excellent job at achieving that. He has been no less than another great addition to the squad with his quick thinking and combat ready attitude that always stands out in and out of drills. Whenever you talk to Lawson you will instantly find yourself engaging in long conversations about the most random stuff that can be talked about. To which I can finally say we came to a conclusion that the veggie burger was in fact the worst tasting MRE after an hour long discussion. One year has passed and I am hopeful to see him for another. Congrats Lawson!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="2nd Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Promotion and Badges (Sid H. Evers) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44848/promotion-and-badges-sid-h-evers</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Albers</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44848@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/89485">Cpl. Addante</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91028">Evers</a> is one of many silent killers in the squad. Whether its his addition to the absurd humor or deadly combat skills, there is no doubt in my mind that he belongs to the squad. Its the best feeling seeing a private come into the squad and stay their first 3 months because that means they are sticking around for awhile. Especially after we've had a slew of... questionable privates come and go. He gets a long well with the rest of the guys as if he had been here longer and that cohesion alone aids in not only his performance but everyone else's. Congrats on your promotion PFC Evers, very well deserved!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<hr />

<p></p><div>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/forums/29thsealheaderblack.png" alt="" title="" /></p>

<p>CERTIFICATION OF PROMOTION</p>

<p><b>TO ALL WHO SHALL SEE THESE PRESENTS, GREETING:</b></p>

<p>Know Ye, that reposing special trust and<br /> confidence in the fidelity and abilities of</p>

<p><code><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/91028">Sid H. Evers</a> &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 017948312&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; EP3S1</code></p>

<p>I do promote him to <u>Private, First Class</u> in the </p>

<p>UNITED STATES ARMY</p>

<p>to rank as such from the <u> 27th </u> day of <u> April 2021 </u>.</p>

<p>You are charged to discharge carefully and diligently the duties of the grade to which promoted and to uphold the traditions and standards of the Army.</p>

<p>Effective with this promotion you are charged to execute diligently your special skills with a high degree of technical proficiency and to maintain standards of performance, moral courage and dedication to the Army which will serve as outstanding examples to your fellow soldiers. You are charged to observe and follow the orders and directions given by superiors acting according to the law, articles and rules governing the discipline of the Army. Your unfailing trust in superiors and loyalty to your peers will significantly contribute to the readiness and honor of the United States Army.</p>

<p><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/forums/29thsealfooter.png" alt="" /></p>

<p></p></div>

<p><img src="http://www.29th.org/sigs/76561198145404349.png" alt="Benjamin A. Gibson" title="Benjamin A. Gibson" /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><br /></p>

<hr />

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/badges/marksman/rifle.gif" alt="" title="Rifle Marksman Badge" /><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/eib.gif" alt="" title="Expert Infantry Badge" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Two Years and Six Months of Service (Joseph E. Gunn) </title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44835/two-years-and-six-months-of-service-joseph-e-gunn</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 01:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Promotions and Awards</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Logan</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44835@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="http://personnel.29th.org/#members/5173">Sgt. Minor</a> said:</p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://personnel.29th.org/#members/88000">Cpl. Gunn</a> has been an excellent addition to EP2S2 in his 2 and a half years of service. He has shown excellent leadership skills in combat, and in training the squad. His skills also extend to his weapons, via rifles, or armor. He is also a friend to the squad, being either humor or wisdom to the squad, whenever it is needed. I do not think that EP2S2 could be where it is today, without his presence. Congratulations on your 2 and a half years of service, I can not wait to see where you will be in your next 2 and a half!</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p></p><div><img src="http://personnel.29th.org/images/awards_boxes/large/aocc.gif" alt="" title="5th Army of Occupation Medal" /></div>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
