<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Other Games — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>Other Games — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/other-games/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>Wargame: Red Dragon</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/43921/wargame-red-dragon</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 14:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Hagedorn</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">43921@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey guys,</p>

<p>I have recently gotten back into Wargame and am looking for some people to play with and hopefully show me where i need improvement or help me improve my tactics</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Arma 3 Creator DLC: S.O.G. Prairie Fire</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44607/arma-3-creator-dlc-s-o-g-prairie-fire</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 02:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Kurnshaw</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44607@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey folks.</p>

<p>With the announcement from Bohemia, I am honestly hyped by this new DLC.</p>

<p>It features a 14 player coop campaign and it supports lots of popular multiplayer modes.</p>

<p>Now I am wondering if anyone would be interested to play and/or host some games and events with this DLC (vanilla is fine by me, it could attract more who don't have the time/space to download mods).</p>

<p>If there are, hopefully this thread could be of use as some means to organize it so that we could have fun together as fellow 29th members.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>LFG - The Division 2</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42963/lfg-the-division-2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 14:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>Private Alex J. Menendez</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42963@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi folks!</p>

<p><img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2019/articles/2019-01-30-15-02/-1548860567068.jpg/EG11/thumbnail/750x422/format/jpg/quality/60" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p>I have been looking for a group of people to play some missions in The Division 2! I've been playing this game and I'm hooked. However, playing as a lone wolf or with the occasional stranger ain't so fun, therefore I would enjoy the company of likeminded clansmen who would like the challenge to play the <strong>impossible</strong> Raids which can be done with a party of up to 8 people!</p>

<p>Not only the Raids, but also the manhunts, which in this season we're hunting a rogue agent - Faye Lau. There's also the Summit and Kenly College expeditions that came available.</p>

<p>Whoever has the game and is at least level 30, send me an invite through Ubisoft Connect (former Uplay) - my nick is "AlexMenendez". In these times of quarantine, it would be good to play a casual game, just for the fun of it, and enjoy the company of our fellow members. I intend to play tomorrow, and all members are welcome, from Charlie to Easy Company.</p>

<p>See ya there,</p>

<p><strong>Cheers</strong></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Winter Break Minecraft</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42398/winter-break-minecraft</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 13:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Agee</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42398@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>My squad was tasked to find stuff for us to do together during the break. Someone randomly said Minecraft, and I was like, yeah let's do that. So now I am going to be hosting a Minecraft server throughout the month.</p>

<p><strong>The server will first open up when Company drills would be this Sunday (4 p.m. EST). You should also join the TeamSpeak because Minecraft is cooler if you don't have to type.</strong></p>

<p>This server is for 29th members only, sorry if your friends wanted to join, just can't trust they have the 29th etiquette. Speaking of which, <strong>the rules for this:</strong><br />
1. Don't Grief. I don't expect it to happen, but for that one troll reading this, don't do it. It is bad for everyone.<br />
2. Have fun. This server is meant for all 29th members that enjoy Minecraft, or are looking into giving it another shot.</p>

<p><strong>Server Info:</strong><br />
This will be a vanilla survival world in 1.16.4 (latest release). I'm not going to be doing anything crazy to this one, just pure vanilla, plain and simple.<br />
If you are interested in doing this, please leave a "1" in chat so I can get a good scope of how many people are doing this. <em>You can still join even if you didn't put a "1"</em><br />
IP will be posted this Sunday as I have not bought the server yet.<br />
If you have any questions feel free to PM me or ask in this chat.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>War Thunder</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/32058/war-thunder</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 18:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Yukki</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">32058@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hai Gents,</p>

<p>i have reopend a 29th War thunder Squadron cause the old one was outated.</p>

<p>Fell free to join it.</p>

<p>Search 29ID in Community-Squadrons Tab and apply.</p>

<p>Greetings Yukki</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>D&amp;D 3.5 Play by Post</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/41537/d-d-3-5-play-by-post</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>T4 Hatfield</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">41537@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello my friends, I'll be running a D&amp;D 3.5 Play by Post (text only, running 24/7) game over Discord and I'd like to invite anyone interested in joining. Pretty much every published OGL content is legal for use.</p>

<p>Hit me up for more details or a link to the discord.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Crusader Kings 2 Multiplayer Game</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/37061/crusader-kings-2-multiplayer-game</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 13:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Regan</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">37061@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey gents,</p>

<p>I'm thinking about organizing a multiplayer CK2 campaign because of the CK3 hype with release later this year. That said, CK2 base game is free on steam and you don't need any DLC to play MP. As long as the host (me) has all the DLC, then you can enjoy the full game for free.</p>

<p>If anyone is interested we can discuss a rule set and date/time.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>VTOL VR</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/40162/vtol-vr</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 16:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Hagedorn</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">40162@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I am currently getting my Oculus repaired but should be back in a few weeks, i wanted to see if anyone else has VTOL VR and if when i get my headgear back, anyone would be up for some multiplayer games</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Hearts Of Iron 4</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/33735/hearts-of-iron-4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 21:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>Private Marko Cekić</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">33735@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Would anyone be interested in playing some Hearts of iron 4 i haven't played a multiplayer game in ages and would love to get a few people to play with.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Exo One: Prologue</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/39702/exo-one-prologue</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 20:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Bergstrom</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">39702@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><em>this is just a demo at the moment</em></p>

<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1375530/Exo_One_Prologue/" rel="nofollow">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1375530/Exo_One_Prologue/</a></p>

<p>A strange signal... an alien craft... an interplanetary, gravity-defying journey through space and time. This is the prologue for Exo One.</p>

<p><img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steam/apps/1375530/ss_e6ff3f007818485221558f082222476222b2bde6.jpg?t=1598012616" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p>Exo One: Prologue is the beginning of a surreal and otherworldly adventure into the unknown, serving as an introduction to the mechanics and mood of the main game, Exo One, coming later this year.</p>

<p>This is a short first taste of Exo One - approximately 10 mins playing time</p>

<p><img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steam/apps/1375530/ss_cc28067c259419550c731530215d625d753781b9.jpg?t=1598012616" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p>Master a truly alien traversal system and move through enigmatic and desolate alien landscapes in ways you've never experienced. Use gravity and momentum to reach colossal speeds and exhilarating heights. See amazing, high-sci-fi planets, float through boiling cloud formations, slide and roll down hill and mountain faces, and drift toward alien horizons.</p>

<p><img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steam/apps/1375530/ss_7d291ffe557cf84352de0ae900f2bce02118652d.jpg?t=1598012616" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p>Atmospheric, diffused visuals are merged with otherworldly sound effects and a hypnotic electric guitar soundtrack.</p>

<p>Open a wormhole and step through into mankind's first journey outside the solar system.</p>

<p>Exo One Prologue Gameplay MAX settings</p>

<p><span data-youtube="youtube-MO90OuBvK0Q?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MO90OuBvK0Q"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/MO90OuBvK0Q/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Post Scriptum: The Bloody Seventh</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/13309/post-scriptum-the-bloody-seventh</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 16:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Bergstrom</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">13309@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-W24njMwPkCM?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W24njMwPkCM"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/W24njMwPkCM/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span><br />
Post Scriptum: <a rel="nofollow" href="http://postscriptumgame.com/">Website Under Construction</a><br />
Post Scriptum is a WW2 modification for the acclaimed tactical shooter SQUAD. Players will relive the events of ‘Operation Market Garden’ across the fields and towns of Holland. This massive Allied assault consisted of a coordination of the British and American Airborne to capture key bridges while the British XXX Corps moved to reinforce them through Highway 69. However, consecutive delays in consolidating ground from the north of Belgium through Nijmegen forced the 1st British Airborne Division in Arnhem to make a stand much longer than anticipated. With no successful link between the XXX Corps and the Airborne in sight, the seventh and final bridge in Arnhem was considered lost.<br />
‘The Bloody Seventh’ is our name for the initial focus of the project as we feel it succinctly details the struggle that the British paratroopers had to endure while waiting for their army counterpart to establish a link through the Lower Rhine.</p>

<p>Players will be given the option to fight with the British Airborne Division, British XXX Corps or several branches of the German Army, such as the Wehrmacht or the Waffen SS. It’s a rare opportunity to experience the intense battlefield that was the Battle of Arnhem, which stretched across farms, woods, villages and city areas. Each area is being accurately recreated from archival references that range from street level to aerial images. Whether you’re jumping out of a plane, resupplying friendlies or operating a tank you will find multiple reasons to drop back into the battlefield in this grand scaled representation of a WW2 setting never explored in a large multiplayer environment.</p>

<p><img src="http://postscriptumgame.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/Screenshots/Screenshots_16.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="http://postscriptumgame.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/Screenshots/Screenshots_06.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="http://postscriptumgame.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/Screenshots/Screenshots_15.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="http://postscriptumgame.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/Assets/Weapons/Enfield_2_MkI_Studio_02.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="http://postscriptumgame.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/Assets/Weapons/K98k_Studio_02.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="http://postscriptumgame.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/Assets/Weapons/PIAT_Studio_03.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><img src="http://postscriptumgame.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/Assets/Weapons/Sten_MkV_Studio_02.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Aim Lab - Practice your FPS skills</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/39446/aim-lab-practice-your-fps-skills</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 16:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Regan</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">39446@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey all,</p>

<p>I found this on steam yesterday and its actually really cool. The "game" is free on the steam store, called Aim Lab. It uses a number of challenges and AI to make a profile on your FPS skills. It will then give your advice and tips on what you do good and bad with. Using the data it collects, it will recommend specific challenges to sharpen your skills.</p>

<p>Best part? It allows you to simulate game settings/sensitivity from a bunch of different FPS titles including Squad, Rising Storm 2, Post Scriptum, Escape from Tarkov and a bunch of others.</p>

<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/714010/Aim_Lab/" rel="nofollow">https://store.steampowered.com/app/714010/Aim_Lab/</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Red Dead Redemption 2 (PC)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/38158/red-dead-redemption-2-pc</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 22:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Kurnshaw</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">38158@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>It's probably belated but if anyone plays Red Dead Online on PC (I think I saw T5 Zim and 1Lt. Bergstorm with their RDR2 screenshots) and looking for casual company to walk hunt or whatever other casual things, come give me a game invitation.</p>

<p><a href="https://socialclub.rockstargames.com/member/Tjupps/" rel="nofollow">https://socialclub.rockstargames.com/member/Tjupps/</a></p>

<p>It'd be nice to play with you all. It'd be like the fathers/grandfathers of the first blues &amp; grays.<br />
And we probably can use some uniform and all. Since there are some military clothings in the game.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Deep Rock Galactic</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/37514/deep-rock-galactic</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 17:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Bergstrom</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">37514@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-k4m_5JYrAGM?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k4m_5JYrAGM"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/k4m_5JYrAGM/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>DEEP ROCK GALACTIC is a co-op-first sci-fi FPS featuring badass space Dwarves, 100% destructible environments, procedurally-generated caves, and endless hordes of alien monsters.</p>

<p>My friends and I have been playing it consistently for a few years now and it's gotten better and better. This is one of the shining examples of Early Access done right.</p>

<p>If you have 2-3 other friends (and you're in the 29th so there's really no excuse) then you could do far worse than get this game. It has a difficulty that ramps up as you get further into it. I STILL haven't played the higher hazard levels and have done a couple of handfuls of Deep Dives (end game content) and each one is incredibly challenging.</p>

<p>I've put 140 hours into this game and barely scratched the undersurface (little digging joke there). One of the gleeful things about it is the thoroughness they commit to the Dwarf motif. The home base (where you go between missions to spend your minerals and coin on upgrades and cosmetics) features a bar where you can drink and dance until you pass out - literally. You can wait for your consumerist comrades by kicking barrels into a hoop and making general mischief until the Admin yells at you to get back to work (we chose to name him Alan for no particular reason).</p>

<p>There are four classes:<br />
Digger: Equipped with two massive drills for tunneling, a flamethrower and a semiautomatic pistol as standard.<br />
Scout: An assault rifle, double barreled boomstick, flare gun and grappling hook launcher (Batman style - only scout can use it)<br />
Gunner: A giant gatling gun, hand cannon of a revolver and a grappling line launcher that can be used by other players. Also has a small shield bubble generator<br />
Engineer: A semi automatic shotgun, a 40mm grenade launcher and a placeable turret, plus a foam platform launcher to make jumping between (and jumping down onto) surfaces safe</p>

<p>You can see how these classes interplay together and there are so many opportunities for creative use in hostile combat environments.</p>

<p>Lastly and perhaps most importantly (for laughs) is the Salute button (V by default) which once you get it and start using it, you will want in every... other....game... forever. When you have a beer mug in your hand it even gives you an assortment of "cheers" voice lines.</p>

<p>Seriously for $35 CDN or whatever your regional currency, I don't think you can do better tbh.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Halo: Master Chief Collection</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/30589/halo-master-chief-collection</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 04:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>T5 Gillespie</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">30589@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So, as many of you have no doubt heard, the MCC is coming to PC, alongside Reach.</p>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/976730/Halo_The_Master_Chief_Collection/">Steam Store Page</a></p>

<p><span data-youtube="youtube-88VBun17AMI?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=88VBun17AMI"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/88VBun17AMI/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>It's coming to <strong>both</strong> Windows Store and Steam.</p>

<p>Who's hyped?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Hidden</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/37148/the-hidden</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 20:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>1Lt. Dawdy</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">37148@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>In light of a recent discussion and nostalgia of past source mods, wanted to bring up one of my favorites. The Hidden is set up where a team of highly trained PMC are tasked with killing subject 617 "The Hidden". The only problem is that the subject has a superhuman ability of being almost invisible. The subject can also jump long distances, developed concussion grenades, and with his insanity wants to kill the task force with a knife. However, the task force also has a wide array of tools to aid in killing the subject. This game mode doesn't require a lot of people, as only one person per round gets to play as the hidden while everyone else is the task force.</p>

<p>And best of all it is FREE.</p>

<p>If you are interested in getting together a group night were we play this game, leave a comment. Otherwise here is a few useful links.</p>

<p><span data-youtube="youtube-HJybbFPVTcc?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HJybbFPVTcc"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/HJybbFPVTcc/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>download link for windows<br />
<a href="https://www.moddb.com/downloads/hidden-source-beta-4b" rel="nofollow">https://www.moddb.com/downloads/hidden-source-beta-4b</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>ZOMBIE MASTER</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/36932/zombie-master</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 21:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Stear</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">36932@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So, as most know ive been around a awhile within the community. There was a game back around 2006-2007 a game called Zombie master.<br />
Alot of us old 29thers played this game alot, i found that they brought back the game and its called Zombie Master Beta 2. last update was October 2019. I have installed this mod for HL2, and it still works. It would be awesome to get more 29ther install this game, server can range from 6-24 people. 1 person is zombie master and controllers the map like a rts style spawning in zombies and doing different map abilities. The survivors try and complete objectives threw the map to win. at the end of round there will be a new zombie master.</p>

<p>I loved this game, its amazing. I would like to try and get a group back up playing this game. Check if it out. if interested download it add me on friends and lets try and get a few people together for a match and enjoy a good time of zombies and laid back game play.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.moddb.com/mods/zombie-master-reborn/downloads/zombie-master-reborn-beta-5-windows-installer" rel="nofollow">https://www.moddb.com/mods/zombie-master-reborn/downloads/zombie-master-reborn-beta-5-windows-installer</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Mordhau</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/31832/mordhau</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Butler [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">31832@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/629760/" rel="nofollow">https://store.steampowered.com/app/629760/</a></p>

<p>Basically a new version of Chivalry that's not garbage. I like it quite a lot and I know a fair amount of people here play it, so I went ahead and got a passworded server up for those who want to get away from the randomness and chaos of the public deathmatch servers.</p>

<p>The server name is <strong>Win Butler's Sesh Zone</strong> (yep)<br />
Password is <strong>29th</strong></p>

<p>Server costs about 1$ per slot and I've put in for 90 days as of today. Might keep it going after depending on the interest. Feel free to join and play as you like, it should be defaulted to a Deathmatch rotation.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bannerlord Multiplayer?</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/36793/bannerlord-multiplayer</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 21:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Regan</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">36793@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>If anyone wants to play Multiplayer together send me a message. I'm open to any game mode.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Escape From Tarkov</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/35226/escape-from-tarkov</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Brenholen</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">35226@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for interested members. I know a few people already play it but I am looking to join in. Most of my friends have dropped it or play casually. Message me if you are already grouped up or interested.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Battlefield V - WW2</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/26576/battlefield-v-ww2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 20:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Bergstrom</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">26576@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Co-op will be a thing (4 players). <br />
War Stories seem to be an ongoing thing starting with Fall of Europe (1939-1941?).<br />
Conquest is back in some form.</p>

<p>Operations ("Grand Operations") will be a multi-map game mode which seems to track a single battle over a few days.</p>

<p>Instead of gas masks it appears a "Tool Box" will be used to develop fortifications and weapon emplacements.</p>

<p>No Premium Pass and no pay2win.</p>

<p>From Concept Art it seems like Eastern Front, Africa, Norway, France, Netherlands/Belgium, Germany are all locations.</p>

<p><span data-youtube="youtube-Yg5AOmEv6tQ?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yg5AOmEv6tQ"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/Yg5AOmEv6tQ/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>Cricket bat melee weapon confirmed.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Destiny 2</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/34531/destiny-2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 14:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>CSM Conrad</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">34531@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Since I'd rather not necro an ancient thread, here's a new one.</p>

<p>With the release of Destiny 2: New Light on Steam (Making the game and its first two expansions free to play), a bunch of 29thers have picked up the game and have been playing it a lot. While we've had a fairly consistent team playing together, it became clear on Wednesday when we were building a group to do a raid that we actually had even more people interested in playing than we thought.</p>

<p>We have an "official" 29th clan set up that anyone is welcome to join. You'll just need to find someone with the ability to invite you (I know I can if that's easiest). We ran Leviathan twice this week and are on the lookout for people who are interested in doing more raids and other content. It's a ton of fun to play such a cooperative game with 29th members since we're already on the ball with coordination and communication, so I look forward to seeing more of you involved in the festivities.</p>

<p>Don't feel obligated to join the clan or play with us, but know that we're here if you decide to.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Hell Let Loose (realistic WW2 FPS)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/18452/hell-let-loose-realistic-ww2-fps</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 20:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Willis</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">18452@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Hell Let Loose</strong><br />
<a href="https://www.hellletloose.com/" rel="nofollow">https://www.hellletloose.com/</a></p>

<p><strong>PC Only</strong></p>

<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.hellletloose.com/f-a-q">View Frequently Asked Questions</a></p>

<p><strong>SOCIAL:</strong><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/hell_let_loose">Twitter</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.facebook.com/HellLetLoose/">Facebook</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqbQTnT8Wj3uzIc8TL9iKNg">Youtube<br />
</a></p>

<p><img src="https://cdn.pbrd.co/images/dpXkz7kAT.jpg" alt="https://cdn.pbrd.co/images/dpXkz7kAT.jpg" title="enter image title here" /></p>

<p><strong>About</strong></p>

<p>Developed for Unreal Engine 4 by a small independent team, Hell Let Loose places heavy emphasis on teamwork and communication as players work together as limited Roles in Platoons beneath the leadership of Officers and the force Commander. Using historically accurate weapons, logistics, armor and tactics, Hell Let Loose is a game that demands teamwork and communication not only to win, but to survive.</p>

<p>Featuring sweeping 4km2 maps, the battlefield is divided up into large cap sectors - allowing for emergent and constantly unique gameplay that pits two forces of fifty players in a fight to the death across fields, bridges, forests and towns. The first theater of war is the sleepy Norman town of St Marie Du Mont on<br />
D-Day 1944 in northern France during Operation Overlord. It features a stunning and detailed 1:1 scale battlefield recreated from archival reference material and satellite photography.</p>

<p>Players will organise and muster behind the front lines before carefully pushing forward into the French countryside towards the town. They will need to establish supply lines using logistics vehicles - enabling them to build Garrisons and other spawn locations in the field.</p>

<p>Armor and infantry must work together to smash through the front line and capture territory - pushing the enemy back and earning greater resources to sustain their fighting power.</p>

<p>Engineers will lay minefields and barbed wire to create choke points. Sunken lanes become killing zones while dense woodlands could mask the presence of a devastating PAK 43 - towed into position by a waiting unit of Wehrmacht infantry. Allied infantry call in strafing runs as hedgerows light up with the fire of a Panther tank and the scream of the Hitler's Buzz Saw - the MG42.</p>

<p>The battlefield is laid out - ready to be mastered by soldiers with the skill and strategic ability to wipe the enemy from the field.</p>

<p>A closed pre-Alpha of Hell Let Loose is expected to begin in October 2017, with a Kickstarter campaign launched prior to a Greenlight campaign.</p>

<p>We plan to release Hell Let Loose on Steam in early 2018.</p>

<p><strong>WHEN IS HELL LET LOOSE SET?</strong></p>

<p>Hell Let Loose is set throughout the duration of World War Two. The first theater of war will be based in Normandy, northern France. It will include several villages and the town of St Marie Du Mont. The map is based on archival reference photographs, satellite photography and height imagery. We are proud to present a 1:1 scale 4km-squared battlefield.</p>

<p><strong>HOW REALISTIC WILL IT BE?</strong></p>

<p>We're aiming to make a game that mixes the high-intensity carnage, weapon mechanics and brutality of Red Orchestra 2 with the operational, supply and construction mechanics of Project Reality beneath the meta strategy of a game similar to Company of Heroes.</p>

<p>We prefer intense, terrifying and intelligent instead of long, tedious and boring.</p>

<p><strong>WHICH FORCES CAN I PLAY AS?</strong></p>

<p>Initially, the first theater set in Normandy will pit the faded might of the German OKW against the relatively green forces of the United States Army.</p>

<p>We plan to make more factions available as we create different theaters. <br />
Our road map includes the addition of:</p>

<ul>
<li>British Forces</li>
<li>Ostheer Wehrmacht Forces</li>
<li>Russian Forces</li>
<li>Imperial Japanese Forces</li>
</ul>

<p>We plan to create many more theaters on full release - allowing players to fight in iconic conflicts such as the Battle of the Bulge, the Battle of Stalingrad and the Battle of Guadalcanal. We are also keen to include the community in our decision-making process when it comes to the creation of additional theaters.</p>

<p><strong>WILL THERE BE GORE?</strong></p>

<p>Yes. We already have appropriate decals, death animations and blood spray, but we'll be looking to drive the horror home with dismemberment.</p>

<p><strong>WILL WE BE ABLE TO BUILD?</strong></p>

<p>Yes. We're keen for players to be able to construct defences in order to capitalise on natural choke-points and fields of fire. The Engineer role will be able to erect barbed wire, tank traps, machine-gun nests and other emplacements. He'll also be able to lay anti-tank and anti-personnel mine fields, as well as detect and mark enemy minefields.</p>

<p>Obviously, an Engineer cannot carry a battlefields worth of defences on his back.<br />
To construct them, he will have to have supplies delivered to the front line. It will be crucial to have steady and protected supply lines should you want to maintain a strong defensive line.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/k3k4iii.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/CnyQnKj.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/ZqPfKmo.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/jx0L1Db.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/UEcutzz.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/BZOBBWz.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/AouwJOl.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/jxQuar1.jpg" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /><br />
<img src="https://scontent-sea1-1.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t31.0-8/18673162_1652203628141957_1761803069806842186_o.jpg?oh=221501b986b2ffad4fa9a66f4e84b8ef&amp;oe=59B099D8" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></p>


<span data-youtube="youtube-dFZmTaeM2g8?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dFZmTaeM2g8"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/dFZmTaeM2g8/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span>



<span data-youtube="youtube-oxNA2qSBMaw?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oxNA2qSBMaw"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/oxNA2qSBMaw/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span>

]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>World of Warcraft</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/10616/world-of-warcraft</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 04:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpl. Zenhenko [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">10616@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I know a few people that play WoW in the 29th, so why not make a thread. Right now I'm playing a WotLK private server and its really fun. The game was so much different back then. I'll probably resub to retail when Legion comes out.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DCS World</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/32939/dcs-world</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 16:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Sigal</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">32939@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Calling all pilots!!!! Whether a veteran of air combat or complete beginner we should band together to become the best we can be and learn our aircraft inside and out. Add me on steam if you are interested in flying a few sorties or just generally want to mess about.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Star Citizen</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/7156/star-citizen</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Dashwood [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">7156@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="http://irondagger.de/Images/Games/Star_Citizen.png" alt="enter image description here" title="enter image title here" /></div><br />
<br />

<hr />

<p>Chris Robert's spiritual successor to his Wing Commander series (And to a lesser extent Freelancer) is starting to gain some momentum once again. After a <strong>very</strong> successful kickstarter back in 2012/13 the dream of a fully immersive free-to-play online space RPG/FPS/Sim was born. It took a bloody long time for anything to come of it but finally we are seeing some interesting developments.</p>

<p>Aside from the hanger which you have been able to view some of your ships in for quite a while now, CIG (The developers) have released some interesting footage about what they hope their explosions will look like in-game:</p>

<p></p><div> <span data-youtube="youtube-4P4adTuZkMI?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4P4adTuZkMI"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/4P4adTuZkMI/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></div>

<p>On top of that they have released an interesting teaser for their FPS module, Squadron 42, starring Gary Oldman:</p>

<p></p><div> <span data-youtube="youtube-8EC4WHPxnrk?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8EC4WHPxnrk"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/8EC4WHPxnrk/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></div>

<p>At the moment the game is early pre-alpha internal testing. Backers have been able to "pledge" to the game by purchasing ship packages that include the ship concept, the game and a few other bits depending on what ship is purchased. Once the game goes live (Public alpha that is), backers will have immediate access. At the moment all there is is a hanger to walk around, a combat flight sim and the social module where you walk around a pretty set piece.</p>

<p>What we have seen so far indicates a project that, if delivered, will blow any other game of its type out of the water. Chris Roberts is claiming alot with this one, and aside from project delays, he has yet to disappoint.<br />
<br /></p>

<hr />

<p></p><div> <span data-youtube="youtube-lJJ9TcGxhNY?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lJJ9TcGxhNY"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/lJJ9TcGxhNY/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></div>

<hr />

<p>Right now if you set up an account on the RSI website (<a href="https://robertsspaceindustries.com/" rel="nofollow">https://robertsspaceindustries.com/</a>) and pledge your support you can get 5,000 UEC (In game currency) using a referral code (I am linking my one, if you have friends who already have the game, get them to send you one so they get nice things). There are already a few people in the 29th who have pledged to Star Citizen in preparation for its eventual launch. If it is all that it promises, having a large 29th presence on this game would be amazing.</p>

<hr />

<p>Referral code: STAR-WSLG-WXSP<br />
Website: <a href="https://robertsspaceindustries.com/" rel="nofollow">https://robertsspaceindustries.com/</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Starbase</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/32531/starbase</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Bergstrom</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">32531@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-zXLTFwoYM_s?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zXLTFwoYM_s"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/zXLTFwoYM_s/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<blockquote><div>
  <p>Starbase is a massively multiplayer online game with gameplay focused on building and designing spaceships and stations, exploration, resource gathering, crafting, trading, and combat. <br />
  Alternatively the game features a sandbox mode where players can explore the game alone or with selected friends in their own universe.</p>
  
  <p>Set in a universe of vast scale and detail, the fully-destructible environment and hybrid voxel/vertex-based game mechanics enable simulations in the game at immense depth; minor collisions may break a few outer plates from your spaceship, while fast-speed crashes can rip the ship apart.</p>
  
  <p>The scale and depth of the simulation in all aspects of the game gives players the ultimate freedom to exploit their innovativeness and creativity – the building blocks of success in Starbase. From constructing single spaceships with durable outer platings to creating massive automated factories and designing electricity and data networks, the players are free to do it their own way.</p>
</div></blockquote>

<p>The devs at Frozenbyte Games (of the Trine series fame) have been releasing feature videos and some of them have been quite fascinating.</p>

<p><strong>Destructible environment and weapons</strong><br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-Mm3hNcxVcWA?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mm3hNcxVcWA"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/Mm3hNcxVcWA/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p><strong>Detailed Destruction Feature Video</strong><br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-gYEuXrjnqm4?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gYEuXrjnqm4"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/gYEuXrjnqm4/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p><strong>In game code programming</strong><br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-7lXK6_bktUk?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7lXK6_bktUk"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/7lXK6_bktUk/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p><strong>Spaceships</strong><br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-qLIkz2IO5iA?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLIkz2IO5iA"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/qLIkz2IO5iA/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p><strong>Spaceship Warfare &amp; Weapons</strong><br />
<span data-youtube="youtube-HDaf2KCN95k?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HDaf2KCN95k"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/HDaf2KCN95k/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Division 2 (PC)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/30580/division-2-pc</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 00:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>2Lt. Furie</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">30580@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anyone looking to play the Division 2? I have started today and it is alright, feels like the first one but in a new setting. Feel free to add me on Uplay: Rushonfire22 and if you want join my clan: Filthy Casual</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Hunt: Showdown</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/32132/hunt-showdown</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 09:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Carogna [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">32132@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube--zuutgFNIhg?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-zuutgFNIhg"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/-zuutgFNIhg/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>

<p>Basically a two player team tactical FPS in wich you had to compete with four other teams to hunt down PVE monsters and pick their bounties up.<br />
Once you got the bounty you need to go to the extraction point, knowing that every other hunters can see you on the map and try to take you down to steal it.<br />
The permadeath system and the limited firepower (game is set in the early 1900 so it's a revolver/bolt action matter) is pretty hardcore and brings to really tense gunfights, in wich tactical choices, positioning and coordination with your teammate are of the upmost importance.<br />
It's a very good combination on PVP and PVE in my opinion, and the astonishing graphics and sounds from Crytek create a truly immersive experience.</p>

<p>Since there was no thread about it i thought to open one, feel free to add me on steam if you already play this.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Battalion 1944</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/9694/battalion-1944</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 23:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Other Games</category>
        <dc:creator>T3 Chandonnet</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">9694@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This is a new WW2 game coming out on Steam/XB1/PS4. It uses the Unreal Engine 4 and is slated for a May 2017 release. Bulkhead Interactive aims to revitalize the WW2 shooter genre. I'm excited for this, as I'm sick of the futuristic shooters/CoD games. You can check out the announcement trailer <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OwT7DJLHAKQ">here</a></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
