<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Server Feedback Archives — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>Server Feedback Archives — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/server-feedback-archives/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>server feedback at 10: 37 pm eastern us</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/17835/server-feedback-at-10-37-pm-eastern-us</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 02:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>LordTrollingham</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">17835@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>an admin banned me  without warning and i broke none of the 29th server rules. it would seem that one of youre guys is letting his ego get to him, or perhaps this is the way the 29th runs their servers, letting the highest ranking 29th member do as they wish without cause or reason, which is unfortunate, because I thought that the 29th battalion server on darkest hour was leget and that the 29th admins upheld the rules stated on the 29th.org website. i didnt get the name of the admin because i was banned without warning with no reason givin for remainder of match and on the server list none of the players show the 29th clan tag, it is so unfortunate that you are allowing your people to run the 29th battalion server like the good guys server where they ban you just because they wnt to even when you have not violated server rules. i just wanted others to know that this is unacceptable for people that are supposed to be active service and role models for the rest of society. Thank you for taking the time out of your long day to read this and give your honest thoughts on it.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>[DH] Unable to Mute Players Using Mics</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/17684/dh-unable-to-mute-players-using-mics</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 02:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>LordTrollingham</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">17684@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I have tried everything in my power to mute rafterman from my end, i went to communications, and hit ban player, speech, text, and mute voice, literally every option available but i cant stop hearing him, and i know a lot of people like him so thats cool with me i just paid my hard earned cash to be able to play this game to relax, and not to hear other peoples bs and insulting his team nonstop for not winning for him while being at the bottom himself, and even if he was the number one player that doesnt mean we should have to listen to that nonsense, i just want to be able to mute that single player is all, ive used every ingame option that is available to no avail.</p>

<p>I think the voice, speech mute option is not functioning on the 29th battalion server on darkest hour, and if you could look into this I and many others would be very thankful as i have seen after i spoke up to the 29th admin ingame about it that many other players were having the same issue.</p>

<p>Thank you for taking the time out of your day to address this issue that seems to be effecting many players other than just me, and as it states in the 29th rules that many players come here to relax and escape from the stresses of life, and that means in my honest opinion that we shouldnt have to listen to a guy on a mic hounding us all match every match. Thank very much for looking into this for us.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DH server needs more admins</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/14502/dh-server-needs-more-admins</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 22:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>cakeisgood</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">14502@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I frequent the server and I have noticed a major increase of griefing and intentional tk'ing.</p>

<p>Get some more admins on your server, or give some of the pvt. ranked members the privilege to kick these griefers. Too often do i report some griefer to a member of 29th to be told they have no power.</p>

<p>Joining TS to report works.....but more admins are needed</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Admin on DH Battalion?</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/13432/admin-on-dh-battalion</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Olaf Steiner</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">13432@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Never an admin around when you need one. No way that I know of to contact an admin while the tking is happening.</p>

<p>Roid 76561197998165482</p>

<p>I'm not sure what kind of server setup you have but it should be possible to install some monitoring to get alerts and record roids on excessive TKs, via the server log.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>report of a pub player</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/11966/report-of-a-pub-player</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 07:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Private Dias T. Nascimento</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">11966@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi I was playing one the server this morning and this dude was kinda rude, I remember a time back in the unit were people were more respectful. the past few days I have been playing one the server I see many pubbers been very unrespectful to others or in general to the 29th unit.</p>

<p><img src="http://s33.postimg.org/8qwkrqpn3/dh_jg_Wagner.png" alt="enter image description here" title="image1" /><br />
<img src="http://s33.postimg.org/f0k2wx1lb/dh_jg_Wagner2.png" alt="enter image description here" title="image2" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>more tking on DH Battalion</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/11679/more-tking-on-dh-battalion</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 02:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Olaf Steiner</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">11679@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>IHeartTking (and other aliases, kept rejoining and tking this evening, kid was fairly persistent in his antics) 7656119805738819</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>tking on DH battalion</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/11615/tking-on-dh-battalion</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Recruit Olaf Steiner</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">11615@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>2 tkers on 29th battalion DH server, at -9 and -15, respectively.</p>

<p>LeroyJenkins 7651198073565519<br />
Qualex 7651198033979916</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Moderator Abusing power</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/10361/moderator-abusing-power</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 05:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Player</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">10361@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This involves t/5 freisenhan</p>

<p>Few days ago, I accidentely run over him in a tank, and I get kicked.</p>

<p>About 20 minutes ago, I blow him up on an AT gun at maupertus (He is Axis) and then I drive the tank behind enemy lines, and I'm kicked....</p>

<p>Would you confront this try hard to stop this abuse of power?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Another griefer on the Darkest Hour server....</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/9163/another-griefer-on-the-darkest-hour-server</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 19:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Bahston</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">9163@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>He goes by the name Wulfgang, he takes a role of a tank crewman and starts killing many teammates on the beginning for the round. Now this wasn't the worst, he respawns in a Panzer IV and when the rest of the tank crewmen (including me) get in the tank, he kills all of us when we get out. I can't play with him anymore, can you please talk to him or ban him?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Player trolling, TKing constantly and marking it off as &quot;OOPS, KARMA!&quot; Nickname Pritz</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/8912/player-trolling-tking-constantly-and-marking-it-off-as-oops-karma-nickname-pritz</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 00:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Bahston</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">8912@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So what happened was that I was TK'd by Pritz in a bell tower in one of the maps, I forgot what it was called, all I know is that one of the objectives was Road N33. Close to the end of the game, when the reinforcements were depleted, I was camping in one of the corners of a building, and a soldier (who was friendly) just ran past the doorway, being on my toes, I shot immediately, it was Pritz. I tried to lightheartedly dismiss it by saying "Sorry" and "That was karma for shooting me back at the tower." Well Pritz goes on a rampage in Foy, the next map. I choose MG Squad, he chooses MG Squad and starts shooting me in the back when I'm close to enemy lines. He does this multiple times and always says "OOPS" and "KARMA!" I find this unacceptable so I type "Pritz is salty" and he does this even more times, always with the same excuses. I just quit because I can't deal with Pritz anymore, I see him eyeing me when I switch to Machine Gunner.</p>

<p>This just happened 20 minutes ago, please deal with this! I unfortunately have no proof</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Troling and bad language</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/7026/troling-and-bad-language</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 00:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>PFC Antoine [Ret.]</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">7026@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This player had trolling the public server. Me and PFC Patison [29th ret] , had given to him somes warnings and advices. I kicked him 4 times but he had changing his name and he do not stoping that for 30 mins .</p>

<p><strong>-Facts:</strong> MDV blocking, friendly kills, friendly tanks destroying and bad language against the others players.</p>

<p><strong>-Request:</strong> Permanent Ban.</p>

<p><strong>-His ROID:</strong> 76561198115469948</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Trolls on Lutremange map</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/6964/trolls-on-lutremange-map</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 21:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>LG_Derrick</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">6964@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi !<br />
I was on the Lutremange map a few minutes ago as a tanker on Axis team .<br />
A player named Todd was driving a Sdkfz 251 , using it to push our tanks . Then he changed named to Issac , as a tanker in a Panther, and shooted  on my tank , damaging it .<br />
On the previous maps, there were also some trolls .</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>A player trolling , nickname Gorilla</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/5871/a-player-trolling-nickname-gorilla</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>LG_Derrick</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">5871@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi !<br />
Last night on Bridgehead map , a player named Gorilla played as allied tanker .<br />
He went to Axis tank spawn and destroyed the Axis tanks in spawn .<br />
<a href="http://img11.hostingpics.net/pics/295954Gorilla1.jpg" rel="nofollow">http://img11.hostingpics.net/pics/295954Gorilla1.jpg</a></p>

<p>Then he went sitting at a distance from spawn :<br />
<a href="http://www.hostingpics.net/viewer.php?id=726349Gorilla2.jpg" rel="nofollow">http://www.hostingpics.net/viewer.php?id=726349Gorilla2.jpg</a></p>

<p>And shooting on new tanks when they respawned :<br />
<a href="http://www.hostingpics.net/viewer.php?id=310840Gorilla3.jpg" rel="nofollow">http://www.hostingpics.net/viewer.php?id=310840Gorilla3.jpg</a></p>

<p>This behavior is very similar to a player who has already be banned and unbanned 2 times...<br />
IMO trolls will kill Darkest Hour , because their only pleasure in life is to ruin the game experience of honest players.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>[DH] Player exploiting again</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/5844/dh-player-exploiting-again</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 02:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Matisse</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">5844@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi again 29th,</p>

<p>Same guy, same issue as before: wearing the uniform of the opposing force.</p>

<p>First as "Player" then as "Lon" and then "Turtle", ROID 76561198222486208 (<a href="http://i.imgur.com/Y7zEMaY.jpg" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/Y7zEMaY.jpg</a>) --&gt; <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198222486208" rel="nofollow">https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198222486208</a></p>

<p><a href="http://i.imgur.com/HEGKnw7.png" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/HEGKnw7.png</a><br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/lGItTQY.jpg" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/lGItTQY.jpg</a><br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/DbjdYks.jpg" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/DbjdYks.jpg</a><br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/DbjdYks.jpg" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/DbjdYks.jpg</a> (killed the Sherman, including death message)</p>

<p>It really ruins the game -- I know I won't be going back to the 29th server anytime soon with this happening. There aren't many active servers, and I know you guys were looking into this, can something please be done?</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>[DH] Player exploiting</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/5714/dh-player-exploiting</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 01:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>Matisse</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">5714@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi 29th,</p>

<p>I was on your Darkest Hour server just a little while ago, and there was a player by the name of 'Tina' (ROID: 76561198222486208 --&gt; <a href="http://i.imgur.com/CWupPuS.png" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/CWupPuS.png</a> --&gt; <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198222486208" rel="nofollow">https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198222486208</a>) who was playing as a German and yet had an American uniform/kit.</p>

<p>I hopped into Spectate to take a closer look..<br />
Screenshots:<br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/PweGTiY.png" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/PweGTiY.png</a> <br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/fyBSUwX.png" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/fyBSUwX.png</a> (Clearly playing German)<br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/yRMgWvM.png" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/yRMgWvM.png</a> (Same screenshot as above, just no scoreboard -- clearly in an American kit)<br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/pY79yQ7.png" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/pY79yQ7.png</a> (spawning at German spawn)<br />
<a href="http://i.imgur.com/xeV4bgr.png" rel="nofollow">http://i.imgur.com/xeV4bgr.png</a> (including a kill message)</p>

<p>Although I do not know how to replicate this bug, I do know that Theel is aware of it (and how it works) and says it will not be possible to do in DH 6.0. Still wanted to make you guys aware of it and hopefully encourage some more active admins during US evening hours <img src="https://vanilla.29th.org/resources/emoji/smile.png" title=":)" alt=":)" height="20" /></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Mistreatment of 29th battalion server players (DH)</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/3704/mistreatment-of-29th-battalion-server-players-dh</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 17:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>sumpftarn44</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">3704@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello all! Im here to report T/5 Kouters (29th ID). Today I was kicked once from the game and kicked another time for the entirety of a game for using foul language. 29th server rule #3 states keep the foul language to a "MINIMUM" which is a rule that i follow while playing on 29th servers. If foul language is to be forbidden, update the server rules. If it is still to be kept to a minimum then get your admins in check so they stop kicking good and honest players that abide by server rules and slowly kill DH which we all know and love.</p>

<p>PS. I was banned for the entirety of the game because i stated rule #3 and asked how i broke the rule. Therefore i was kicked for a game session for absolutely no reason besides the admin mistreating players. my username at the time was "Y2K"- thanks yall</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Further mis-treatment of 29th server players</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/4089/further-mis-treatment-of-29th-server-players</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 22:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Server Feedback Archives</category>
        <dc:creator>sumpftarn44</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">4089@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Once again 29th server admins are creating the law instead of enforcing it.</p>

<ol start="3">
<li>Keep the foul language to a minimum<br />
Our servers are a friendly environment open to players of all ages, genders and races. It may be a war videogame but it is a public server.<br />
Note: This applies to microphone, text chat, and player names.</li>
</ol>

<p>MINIMUM MINIMUM MINIMUM.</p>

<p>minimum- the smallest amount or quantity possible.</p>

<p>Just because your rules are flawed and don't specify the quantity does not mean you can kick me for no cussing.</p>

<p>Cpl. Jansch was kicking players for using cause words. He removed me for saying f***ing and then when i asked why i was kicked he said for swearing. When i told him the server rules he said that my understanding of the rules were flawed. Its in black and white and in simple english. Also obvious was the mis-treatment of players</p>

<p>I'll let you guys handle it</p>

<p>Godspeed, Y2k.</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
