<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Civil Announcements — 29th Infantry Division</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <language>en</language>
            <description>Civil Announcements — 29th Infantry Division</description>
    <atom:link href="https://vanilla.29th.org/categories/civil-announcements/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
        <title>National Liberation Front</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44404/national-liberation-front</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 18:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44404@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>National Liberation Front</b></u></div><br />
<div><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/4/4a/FNL_Flag.svg/1200px-FNL_Flag.svg.png" width="45%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /><br />
The National Liberation Front of Southern Vietnam, nicknamed by their adversaries "Viet Cong", was one of the main combatants of the Vietnam War, making it a unique piece of the conflict through its extensive use of guerilla warfare, nighttime operations, and infiltration. First declared a sovereign group in the later part of 1960 while the war had already been raging for years, the fighting elements of what would eventually become the NLF were already present in South Vietnam years earlier.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/lbiTOPw.png" width="45%" alt="A tour guide showing an entrance to a Viet Cong tunner" /></p>

<p>The Viet Cong's guerrilla tactics, complex tunnel systems, the operations they took part in, and appreciation of nature are often points of discussion when considering their participation in the hostilities. However, there are some aspects of the National Liberation Front which are rarely touched upon; the context of their creation and their fate once the war was over and Vietnam was reunited.</p>

<p><b>Birth of the Liberation Front</b></p>

<p>Failed military coups, peasant uprisings, and armed religious sects in the years leading to 1960 were already doing much to destabilize South Vietnam. While some of these groups were successful in dismantling the presence of the government's police and military within the regions they had surged in, the lack of support and no steady supply line meant it was a matter of time before they had to abandon their newly obtained territory and go underground again to avoid direct conflict with the Army of the Republic.</p>

<p>The National Liberation Front was created to centralize these many insurgent groups within South Vietnam, and not only aid them with the supplies that came from North Vietnam through the Ho Chi Minh Trail but also guide them on military campaigns. These groups were varied in origin, their background, members, the nature of their dissent, their ethnicity, religious beliefs, and even their plans for Vietnam if it were to be once again united. The main groups were those who had suffered direct suppression by South Vietnam's government and some of those who had already supported Vietnam against France during the First Indochina War. <img src="https://i.imgur.com/dFmP8X9.png" width="40%" alt="Ho Chi Minh trail" />Political groups, religious sects, and other social organizations, many of which had already clashed with South Vietnam's secret police force, were the groups that formed the political parties that would, in 1960, form a Central Committee and unite these groups into one organization. The newly formed NLF would soon carry on to join North Vietnam against the Southern forces, now relying on supplies coming from the North through the Ho Chi Minh trail.</p>

<p>Before the First Indochina War, the Ho Chi Minh trail was an unnamed, unrefined trade line that had been in use in the region for centuries, but had since been improved for military use during wartime. By 1959, one year before the proper creation of the NLF, the People's Army of North Vietnam 559th Transportation Group had already been tasked with maintaining and improving the trail to supply insurgents within South Vietnam, turning it into the network of supply lines that would be vital to the NLF's success, transporting tonnes of supplies and thousands of men to the south.<img src="https://i.imgur.com/NwraY62.png" alt="National Liberation Front soldiers" width="35%" /></p>

<p>The National Liberation Front of Southern Vietnam, what had once been a variety of motivated but fickle and undersupplied insurgent groups within South Vietnam's borders, now was a centralized group, with an intricate supply line providing them with much-needed resources coming from North Vietnam. The Viet Cong was now prepared to make their debut on the battlefields of the Vietnam War.</p>

<p><b>Victory and Defeat in the South</b></p>

<p>As the war continued, in June 1969 the political leadership of the NLF formed the Provisional Revolutionary Government of the Republic of South Vietnam, with the intent of helping the Viet Cong obtain international stature. The PRG was formed from the political entities already within the Front, and other south Vietnamese political elements supportive of their cause. Their declared intent was to advance the interests of the South Vietnamese people and provide the Liberation Front with a governmental structure. Settled near the Cambodian border, the PRG initiated organizing its negotiations for eventual reunification. However, after the US and South Vietnamese forces launched the Cambodian campaign, the PRG suffered losses, and the replacements sent from North Vietnam were clashing with the more neutral parties, causing political turmoil within the PRG ranks. When complaints sent to the North Vietnamese government were dismissed, it became clear to NLF and PRG leadership that the nationalists and less revolutionary volunteers who once united to create the Liberation Front were now being cast aside in favor of those determined on advancing North Vietnam's interests.</p>

<p>The military organization of the Front was similar to its political segment, as the NLF forces suffered casualties, they were replenished by North Vietnamese men, steadily replacing the southerners within the military organization. This reached a peak after the Tet Offensive where, by the estimation of the PAVN and Viet Cong, forty thousand Viet Cong were killed, with more than sixty thousand being injured.<img src="https://i.imgur.com/1O7AA9l.png" width="40%" alt="A youth representative of the PRG at the 1973 World Youth Conference in Berlin" /> NLF leaders noted that units that were once dominated by southerners had been replaced by northerners years before the fall of Saigon. This solidifies the loss of unity inside the groups that were created within the borders of South Vietnam, intending to extend the interests of the South Vietnamese people against a government they believed was ruling not for its people.</p>

<p>After the fall of Saigon on the 30th of April 1975, the Provisional Government of the Republic of South Vietnam assumed power in the South and participated in the reunification of Vietnam. The North Vietnamese leadership swiftly decided to dissolve the PRG after the reunification was completed. North and South now merged into the Socialist Republic of Vietnam in July 1976, the PRG was dissolved, and the National Liberation Front soon followed a comparable fate, being merged with the Vietnamese Fatherland Front in February 1977.</p>

<p>The National Liberation Front of Southern Vietnam succeeded in its fight against the South Vietnamese government and their American allies, but the southern nationalists were replaced by men from the north as the war went on. This would eventually be the main cause of North Vietnam having sole authority over the now reunified nation.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> PFC de Freitas<br />
<em>Edited by</em> T5 Evarts and PFC Mrzena</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Merrill's Marauders</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/44132/merrills-marauders</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 19:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">44132@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>5307th Composite Unit</b></u></div>

<p></p><div><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f1/Merrills_Marauders.svg" width="27%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div> "Merrill's Marauders"</div>

<p>5307th Composite Unit, nicknamed "Merrill's Marauders'' after the units commander and referred to in operation by codename “Galahad”, was an all volunteer regiment composed of soldiers and officers from the jungle trained Caribbean Defense Command, Army Ground Forces in continental United States, veterans from South Pacific Command, and even soldiers from military prisons who were offered their freedom in exchange for service. In all, the unit numbered 2,997 men. This unit, on top of their specialized training, received a generous arsenal of various US Army weaponry that favored mobility. The unit also had 700 animals largely composed of horses and mules to transport supplies through the jungle terrain. Finally, unlike other units in the Burma Campaign that were under British command and answered to Admiral Lord Mountbatten, the Deputy Supreme Commander of South East Asia, Merrill's Marauders answered to Deputy Supreme Commander General Stilwell of Northern Combat Area. This specialized unit was tasked with penetrating deep behind Imperial Japanese lines during World War II to conduct guerilla warfare during the Burma Campaign, supporting the Republic of China against Imperial Japan with British and American aid.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/6zNxcVm.png" alt="Brigadier General Frank Merrill (left) and General Joseph Stilwell (Right)" width="48%" />The unit's nickname "Merrill's Marauders" originated when General Stilwell appointed Brigadier General Frank Merrill to lead the unit, and during their tour, Time News correspondent James Shepley was thinking of a catchy name for the unit as 5307th Composite Unit didn't quite captivate the public image. So he came up with "Merrill's Marauders" and the name stuck ever since then. The commander, Brigadier General Merrill, was previously a Staff Sergeant in the Engineering Corp where he was able to get an appointment to West Point. He was also a military attaché in Tokyo where he studied Japanese, before joining General Douglas MacArthur's Staff as an intelligence officer. By the end of the war, Frank Merrill was a Colonel, however, he retired from service as a Major General.Remarkably, Frank Merrill became a Brigadier General only a month before his fortieth birthday, making him one of the youngest generals since the Civil War. His accolades include, Distinguished Service Medal, Legion of Merit, Bronze Star, and a Purple Heart on top of being inducted into the US Army Ranger Hall of Fame.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/oKdMbXh.png" width="55%" alt="Brigadier General Frank Merrill with Japanese-American Interpreters T/Sgt. Herbert Miyasaki (Left) and T/Sgt. Akiji Yoshimura (Right)" />Merrill Marauders' successes came largely from their jungle training, experienced NCO and officer corps, and understanding the limitations of their arsenal. Such as the fact that the unit lacked a heavy weapons company, and thus relied heavily on flexibility and surprise to outfight the Imperial Japanese forces; as every single soldier within the regiment had automatic weapons. However, a little known secret among the unit's success was the integration of Japanese-American soldiers from the Military Intelligence Service who acted as translators for the unit. Many of these translators would go on to become US Army Rangers and get inducted into both the Military Intelligence Hall of Fame and the US Army Ranger Hall of Fame. It should be noted that the conditions these soldiers faced were brutal, as weight was critical for the Marauders; they relied on jungle rations to stay dry, light weight, and give a large pool of calories to the exhausted men. However, because they were discontinued due to cost, the unit relied on K rations as an alternative which was largely unpopular among the men in terms of taste, so would often trade cigarettes with the allied forces for food.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/QsHx1IQ.png" width="40%" alt="Master Sergeant Roy Matsumoto, Former Marauder, Military Intelligence and Army Ranger Hall of Fame. Earned Bronze Star and Legion of Merit" />Despite the limitations that the unit faced with firepower, and the constant struggles of jungle warfare such as sunbathing to fight off fungal skin infections, Merrill's Marauders inflicted heavy casualties against Japanese Imperial Forces- in one battle inflicting 400 casualties while suffering 57 KIA, 302 wounded, and 379 incapacitated due to illness or exhaustion. On their final mission to capture Myitkyina, Marauders suffered 272 KIA, 955 wounded, 980 evacuated due to illness and disease while inflicting over 3,800 KIA and 187 POW of the Imperial Japanese forces on their last mission. The unit would eventually capture Myitkyina, however, only 200 of the original Marauders were present. By the time the unit was disbanded, only 130 combat effective enlisted men and officers out of the original 2,997 men would be present. Out of the entire regiment, only two individuals were never hospitalized for wounds or major illness.</p>

<p>The unit’s dedication and tenacity would leave a long lasting legacy within the United States military, with the 75th Ranger Regiment inheriting their legacy and paying homage to Merrill's Marauders as they set the <img src="https://i.imgur.com/dqalmGs.png" width="30%" alt="The legacy of Merrill's Marauders is carried on through the 75th Ranger Regiment, as their distinctive unit insignia pays homage to Merrill's Marauders" />foundation to how a light infantry unit would operate and is still used to this very day by various special operation units. The Marauders’ actions would not go unnoticed, as the unit holds the rare distinction of every single member having earned the Bronze Star for their actions, and the unit as a whole being awarded Distinguished Unit Citation and the Congressional Gold Medal. Many of the marauders would later be inducted into Army Ranger Hall of Fame and/or Military Intelligence Hall of Fame. Notably, David Richardson, the most decorated soldier-journalist of World War II was a Marauder, having earned two Bronze Stars, Legion of Merit, and was eligible for the Purple Heart but refused treatment in favor of returning to the action. As of December 31, 2020 seven Marauders are still alive.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. Dawdy<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Cpl. Tilley and PFC Mrzena</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>2020 Year in Review</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42879/2020-year-in-review</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 02:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42879@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/b7VShPQ.png" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p>2020 was quite the year for all of us, especially in regards to the 29th.  This was a year filled once again with events and expansion, possibly to a level that has not been seen in quite some time.</p>

<p>As with 2019, we had another great start to the year beginning with one of the better events that a member of the 29th can participate in: OCS Scrims. 2Lt. Stray of CP2, 2Lt. Brenholen of DP3, and 2Lt. Dahl, formerly of EP4, all completed their OCS Scrims and were commissioned to the rank of Second Lieutenant. Additionally, the OCS Scrims provided an opportunity for medals to be earned with one Bronze Star being awarded for actions during these events.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, world events took a negative turn, and the traditional April Fools joke had to be postponed. Taking its place was a unit-wide weapons pass for the month of April, giving members the opportunity to use that extra time on their hands to have a little extra fun on 29th servers.<br />
A big theme in 2020 was the unofficial scrimmages with outside units that Charlie and Easy Company participated in. These events brought the opportunity for competitive gameplay without the intense preparations that scrims bring. Members of many of these events were awarded an Armed Forces Expeditionary Medal.</p>

<p>Easy Company also got busy this year with their Operations Corps planning and hosting many public scrimmages that many outside units attended. These Pub Scrims introduced many other units to 29th-type drills and even led to some of those units being opponents in official scrims.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://imgur.com/iNzNCFk.png" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>2020 was quite the year for official scrims in the unit, with every company deploying a platoon at least once. First was EP3 being deployed to fight the Canadian Forces in what was ultimately a victory. DP1 followed up next with a scrim against the 1st Cavalry in August in what was also a total victory. Next came DP3 in September with their victory over Phoenix Gaming. The fourth scrim of 2020 went to EP4 who tied 1-1 with Squad Ops in a hard fought deployment. The final scrim of the year went to Charlie Company, who participated in a large scale coalition fight in which they won their attack.</p>

<p>1Lt. Nelson had the following to say about 2020 for Charlie Company:</p>

<p><em><b>"Long story short, we had a very eventful year, and 2021 is looking to be even more so. Morale is high, and our mix of old-timers and newer folks makes for a fantastic experience all around. I can't emphasize enough how great "Friday Night Fights" has been for our ability to network with other realism units and how great of an opportunity it provides to train leadership at all levels in combat."</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – 1Lt. Nelson, Charlie Company Commanding Officer</b></em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/MOY5GmJ.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>While fighting other units is exciting and a lot of work, that wasn’t enough for Charlie and Easy Companies. Charlie followed in the footsteps of Dog and Easy Companies with their own Charlie Battle of the Squads in which CP1S3 were the victors. Easy Company changed it up. Rather than doing a Battle of the Squads, they did Battle of the Platoons, where every platoon fought each other and EP3 came out on top as the top platoon of Easy in 2020.</p>

<p>We wrapped up this incredibly busy year the way we began it, with another round of OCS Scrims, again featuring members of each Company. 2Lt. Drake of CP1, 2Lt. Griffin of DP1, 2Lt. Deb of DP2, and 2Lt. Furie of EP2 all completed scrims of their own and were commissioned to Second Lieutenant. Of course these promotions were accompanied with many other promotions to Company and Platoon Headquarters. 1Lt. Nelson, 1Lt. Ochs, and TSgt. Robles were all promoted to Company HQ, and FSgt. Dethfield became Senior NCO of Easy Company. Along with the seven Second Lieutenants commissioned this year, SSgt. Vandewalle of CP2, Sgt. Gibson of EP3, SSgt. Newton of EP4, and SSgt. Crane of EP5 were all promoted to Platoon Sergeant.</p>

<p>One of the primary causes for the promotions of new leadership is due to the expansion of the companies. Dog Company added DP2S4 and DP3S4 while Easy Company opened EP5 in a new time zone for the unit, PST.</p>

<p>Captain Fritz had the following to say about 2020 for Easy Company:</p>

<p><em><b>"While 2020 was an unmitigated disaster, I’ll look back at it with fondness. Easy Company and the 29th as a whole achieved so much during the downtime of the various national and local lockdowns provided. From growing numbers and new platoon expansions; to OCS Scrims, Pub Scrims, and official deployments, and even the first-ever Battle of the Platoons, I can say truthfully that this was by far the most exciting year in my tenure here. 2020 showed me, and I hope to all of you, what we can achieve as a unit. While I hope 2021 is a far more stable year, rest assured that we will keep pushing things to new heights so that we can all enjoy an even better 29th ID. Ever Forward!"</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – Cpt. Fritz, Easy Company Commanding Officer</b></em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Cgr2aWc.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>It goes without saying that 2020 was very busy, and there are no signs of the unit slowing down in 2021. The dedication that everyone shows to attending drills, along with the hard work that staff, SLT, Squad, Platoon, Company, and Battalion leadership put in to the unit make this one of the most, if not the most premier realism units out there.</p>

<p><em><b>"Looking back at 2020, I'm amazed at how full the unit feels. Thanks to the nonstop action of our unit's recruiters, we are pushing very close to the 500 member mark. That is truly historic. In addition to the fullness of our roster, our senior officers have been hard at work fostering numerous Officer Candidate School cadres to develop junior officers allowing for needed expansion. Not only did we have some very nerve-wracking OCS Scrimmages, but the unit also fielded multiple platoons in Official Scrimmages against other units. This, in turn, has led to numerous badges, awards, and bragging rights for many across our ranks. One more "Congratulations!" to those who represented the unit on the ultimate stage, we're proud of the effort and professionalism you achieved.</b></em></p>

<p><em><b>We've had some other members answer the call to higher leadership in 2020 and I want to thank them for their efforts and service to the Battalion and their Companies. Special thanks to 1Lt. Nelson, 1Lt. Ochs, and TSgt. Robles. Your ranks below and this Battalion as a whole would not be the same without you gents and Battalion Headquarters thanks you!</b></em></p>

<p><em><b>Looking ahead to 2021, I hope to see continued growth amongst the ranks, from AIT's to SLT to OCS and beyond. The work each and every one of you put in is truly inspiring and Battalion Headquarters is entirely confident that big things are coming because of those efforts. Keep pushing yourselves, your squad, and those around you, together we embody our motto of "Ever Forward!". Happy New Year and 29th, Let's GO!"</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – Lt. Col. Wheatley , Battalion Commander</b></em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/oLsdT1p.png" width="85%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Sgt. Gibson<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Cpl. J. Lee</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>THE REAL 29TH - THE BATTLE OF SAINT-LÔ</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42705/the-real-29th-the-battle-of-saint-lo</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 22:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42705@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>THE REAL 29th - THE BATTLE OF SAINT-LÔ</b></u></div>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/3P4OVoc.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div>

<p>Most people exposed to Anglophone media know about the Normandy landings (Operation Neptune), in which the 29th Infantry Division (ID) took part. People living in the early 21st century know of the famous movies such as “Saving Private Ryan” which depicted the landings of the 29th at Omaha beach. On June 6, 1944, the 116th "Ever Forward" Regiment of the 29th ID, was indeed assigned to the first wave on four sectors of Omaha, intended to support the 1st Infantry Division “Big Red One”. Of it’s 3100 men, the 116th Regiment took 900 casualties. By the 7th of June, the rest of the 29th had landed and by the 9th, Omaha Beach was secure and the division took Insigny-sur-mer. However, few know of the subsequent battles the 29th fought after Normandy, unless you actually read about it or if you played Company of Heroes 1. This article serves as a brief account of the 29th taking Saint-Lô in July 1944.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/xaHJSWT.png" alt="Disposition of Forces in June 1944. 29th is with the First Army just NE of St.Lo." width="45%" /></p>

<p><b>THE 29th ID AFTER D-DAY IN JUNE 1944</b></p>

<p>In the middle of 1944, the 29th ID was composed of 3 infantry regiments (115th, 116th, 175th), supported by 4 Field Artillery Battalions (105mm guns), and one support battalion each of combat engineers, medical, mechanized reconnaissance, signals, and others. This was the standard organization for non-elite U.S army divisions. By late June, the 29th ID’s effective strength was around 12,000, since it had suffered more than 1000 casualties on D-Day and was considered understrength. However, after two weeks of reorganization and regroup, on July 14th, the 29th Division was reassigned to XIX Corps (also consisting the 30th ID and 35th ID) with the task of leading the assault towards Saint-Lô. Located roughly 25 miles to the Southwest of Omaha, the division began its march along the hedgerow filled terrain to the city.</p>

<p><b>THE STRATEGIC OBJECTIVE OF SAINT-LÔ</b></p>

<p>Saint-Lô was a large strategic objective, chosen alongside Carentan and Caen by SHAEF (Supreme Headquarters, Allied Expeditionary Force) for obvious reasons. With a population of 11,000, Saint-Lô sat on low ground surrounded by hills, with large arterial roads that connected it to other major ports and roads towards Bayeux, an important staging ground for the allied push further into France and Belgium. Since D-Day, St-Lô had already been under heavy allied bombing which destroyed most of the city and dispersed the local population (with an unknown number of civilian casualties). <img src="https://i.imgur.com/oI0gD8K.png" width="55%" alt="29th Division’s position towards St-Lô with 115th and 116th regiments leading the assault" /> This bombing campaign was to prevent German supplies and reinforcements from moving into the allied invasion zone by rail or road. The ground offensive for St. Lô was planned in late June and involved 12 Allied divisions in 4 Corps on a 12 mile front, against a hodgepodge of German troops that retreated from Normandy, as well as fresh elite troops that were stationed deeper in Normandy. The Divisional Commander of the 29th ID, Maj.Gen Gerhardt, was assigned a sector stretching a few miles. Directly facing the 29th and guarding the town and surrounding area were elements of the 352. Infanterie Division and the elite 3. Fallschirmjägerdivision (3. FSJg). In all, an estimated 10-15,000 German troops were in the AO, but the actual number remains unknown.</p>

<p><b>THE 116TH AND THE BOCAGES</b></p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/MLi6iXy.jpg" width="48%" alt="image" /></p>

<p>On July 11th, the 29th was given orders to commence the attack. P-47 Thunderbolts were called to strafe the hedgerows surrounding the city. 1st Battalion of 116th (our unit’s real life counterpart) was surrounded as it had unwittingly crossed too far ahead, and had become encircled for 2 days before being relieved by elements of the 115th. This mishap led to numerous friendly fire incidents from aerial bombardment, resulting in more than 100 casualties for the 116th. Strategic locations such as hills and river crossings were pre-marked by German artillery and continuously bombarded.</p>

<p><b>THE 3. FALLSCHIRMJÄGERDIVISION</b></p>

<p>Both German and American sources indicate clearly that it was the 3.FSJg that inflicted the most casualties on the 29th at St-Lô. 29th Veterans noted that the 3.FSJg preferred to attack suddenly at night and from all sides. 1/115th received a night attack which its commander described as “beautifully executed and planned”; a barrage of precise 88mm, Nebelwerfer and 105mm shells which led to its outposts becoming overrun. This parachute unit was veteran and composed entirely of very young volunteers. They had gone through the most intense training the Luftwaffe had to offer, and had previously fought at Crete in 1941. Moreover, it was much better equipped than the soldiers of the 29th. Along with SS Panzer detachments, it was much more heavily equipped, had more mortars, and was 30% larger than the 29th ID. Each company in the 3.FSJg had 20 machineguns and 43 SMGs, but each company in the 29th ID only had 2 .30 cal guns and 9 BARs. Knowing that St-Lô was being bombarded, it had entrenched itself over the hedgerows in a wide area. They also mined the entirety of the roads facing the 29th and camouflaged StuG IIIs in ditches, making them almost invulnerable to aerial attack. One battalion commander of the 29th said: "Those Germans are the best damned soldiers I ever saw. They're smart and they don't know what 'fear' means. They come in and they keep coming until they get their job done or you kill 'em."</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/VIbJ5xq.png" width="55%" alt="German Fallschrimjager at St-Lô" /></p>

<p>From July 17th, it was clear to XIX Corps HQ that the 29th had become bogged down in the hedgerows due to the terrain of Normandy and the elite German troops, and famously lost one battalion commander from mortar fire; Major Thomas Howie. Major General Gerhardt, the divisional commander, famously put Major Howie’s flag draped body on a jeep and drove into the city, calling the dead Major “the Major of St-Lô”. On the 17th, the 29th entered St-Lô in force and witnessed a destroyed city with Germans entrenched in urban terrain, facing snipers and mines which heavily slowed the advance and resorted the commander to call aerial bombing to level the city. As such, the city was virtually destroyed. By July 19th, the city had been taken by the 29th, but not before the division tallied a very high amount of casualties- twice as much as the 82nd or 101st Airborne Division. At this point, the 116th regiment alone had suffered 2516 casualties since June 7th (the regiment had landed on D-Day with 3100 men), while the total losses of the division amounted to 3706. Due to the incredibly high amount of casualties, on July 20th, the 29th was called back to the reserve line and replaced by the 35th ID.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/qqgvhfa.png" alt="Troops of 29th in St-Lô, 19th July 1944" width="75%" /></div>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Akt8pin.jpeg" width="45%" alt="image" /> <img src="https://i.imgur.com/Q0CJ0Vi.png" alt="St-Lô in 1944." width="45%" /></p>

<p><b>THE 29th AFTER ST-LÔ</b></p>

<p>After St-Lô, the 29th was relieved and redeployed to Vire, capturing the city by August 7th during Operation Cobra (an armor led assault deep into France to encircle the Germans). It was then assigned to Brest, and later took part in the invasion of the Ruhr area of Germany. The 29th ID was famous not only because of the Normandy landings, but also because it had a relatively high casualty rate (20,600 casualties) from June 1944 to May 1945 (more than 200% of its strength in just 242 days of combat). From the episode of St-Lô, it is clear that the 29th was neither ready nor well-equipped to face the elite 3.FSJg, but nevertheless got the job done due to numerous other units in the operation as well as armor and air support. Some historians have blamed the unit’s commander, Gerhardt for recklessness which led to demoralization in the unit, but that shall be covered in another story.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. Tan<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Cpl. Tilley and PFC Mrzena</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues | Holiday Edition #2</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42553/veterans-virtues-holiday-edition-2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 01:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42553@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-EI_Ad5y8UVU?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EI_Ad5y8UVU"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/EI_Ad5y8UVU/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Real 29th: Major Thomas Dry Howie</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/41474/the-real-29th-major-thomas-dry-howie</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 02:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">41474@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>The Real 29th: Major Thomas Dry Howie</b></u></div><br />
<div><b>"The Major of St. Lo"</b></div><br />
<div><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Howie.jpg" alt="Image description" /><br />
</div>

<p>Major Thomas Howie was the Battalion Commander of the 116th Infantry Regiment during the Battle of Normandy in World War II. During his service, he proved to be an exemplary leader and a soldier of the 29th Infantry Division, whom forever would be immortalized as "The Major of St. Lo" in his critical last efforts in capturing the city from German occupation.<br /></p>

<p>Major Howie was born in Abbeville, South Carolina in 1908 as the fifth of seven children. He would later attend The Military College of South Carolina, more popularly known as "The Citadel", where he majored in English. He was assigned to Charlie Cadet Company and obtained the rank of Cadet Corporal. He was also voted "Most Versatile, Popular, and Best All Around" by his class. After graduating, he taught English at Stauton Military Academy, before accepting a commission into the Virginia National Guard in 1932. During his tenure in Stauton, he would meet and marry Elizabeth Payne; together, they had a daughter named Sally in 1938.<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/f5/a6/c3/f5a6c3b1e0645130e0a8685477bf9e5b.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Major Thomas Howie with his wife Elizabeth Payne</div>

<p>Major Howie entered active service when the 29th Infantry Division was federalized in 1941. He received training in Maryland, Florida, and North Carolina, before being moved to the United Kingdom in preparation for D-Day, where his unit also received additional intensive training for Omaha Beach. Major Howie was assigned to command 3rd Battalion in the next coming days. After the initial invasion of Omaha Beach, Major Howie was tasked with rescuing 2nd Battalion, who'd become surrounded with very little food and ammunition. Under his leadership, Major Howie managed to break through the German lines using bayonets and grenades in fewer than two hours despite his battalion being at half strength. Major Howie was also personally credited with eliminating two enemy machine gun nests single handedly. After resupplying 2nd Battalion to defend their position, Major Howie reported to Major General Charles Gerhardt, the Division Commander, that the 2nd were "too cut up" and planned to use his 3rd Battalion to take St. Lo, saying "Yes, we can do it" and "See you in St. Lo!". Unfortunately, moments later in the attack, Major Howie was killed by shrapnel from a mortar attack.<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://www.brooksart.com/Seeyouinstlo.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>"See you in St. Lo!" By Larry Selman</div>

<p>The next day, 3rd Battalion entered St. Lo with Major Howie's body on a hood of a jeep draped over by an American flag. Under orders of Major General Gerhardt, Major Howie was to be the first American to enter town. His body was placed at the rubbles of St. Croix Cathedral, giving both soldiers and civilians the opportunity to pay their respects to the fallen Major. The photo of Major Howie's flag-draped body was widely circulated in the United States by the New York Times, becoming one of the most iconic pictures of the war of American sacrifice in the Western Theater. However, due to wartime security, Major Howie's name couldn't be revealed. It was only announced that the body was a major of the United States Army which led to his immortalization as "The Major of St. Lo". His body was buried in Normandy American Cemetery.<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Howieflagdrapedbody.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>New York Times' Picture of "The Major of St. Lo"</div>

<p>Major Thomas Howie was awarded the Silver Star, Bronze Star, Purple Heart, Presidential Unit Citation, Legion of Honor (Chevalier), and the French Croix de Guerre. Several buildings and a statue were made in his honor at The Citadel, Stauton Military Academy, several ROTC buildings, and Mary Baldwin College. He is also enshrined in the South Carolina Hall of Fame. In his honor, a granite monument at his hometown of Abbeville is escribed "Dead in France, Deathless in Fame".<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://images.findagrave.com/photos/2020/12/55903415_44a13a50-57d7-4c9d-8593-16d5d5fe811f.jpeg" width="300" alt="image" /></div> <div><img src="https://alchetron.com/cdn/thomas-d-howie-982b6e2d-dc76-445d-b95e-d224ce8b880-resize-750.jpeg" alt="Image description" /></div>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. Dawdy<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Sgt. Gibson &amp; Cpl. J. Lee</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues Ep. 21 - Sgt. Deb</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42107/veterans-virtues-ep-21-sgt-deb</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 03:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42107@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-w0k5VGsdtC4?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w0k5VGsdtC4"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/w0k5VGsdtC4/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>EP4 Scrim Summary</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/42078/ep4-scrim-summary</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 22:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">42078@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>EP4 Scrim</b></u></div>

<p><br /><br />
</p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/oglUZmU.png" alt="image" /></div>

<p>I had been working in Signal Corps searching around the Squad community for scrim opponents for about a year, and from day one, I hoped we could arrange a scrim with the SquadOps community. They are by far the longest standing one-life group in Squad besides the 29th, so I saw them as our best chance for a real tough fight. Sadly, I was unable to get anything to come to fruition with them. Fast forward a year later and a few scrims down the line, and Sgt. Furie was able to secure this scrim with them with relative ease. Once I heard the news that EP4 would finally have our scrim and it would be against what I perceived as the toughest challenge out there, and on my favorite map of Gorodok no less, I was pretty ecstatic. The scenario itself reminded me somewhat of the EP3 scenario with large portions of the map open to the defenders as well as a lot of foliage and small villages for the attackers to contend with.<br />
<br /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/9lghkwh.png" width="45%" alt="image" /><br />
The infamous month of scrim prep began shortly after the announcement was made to the company, and EP4 got right to work on picking the area apart and coming up with a plan to overcome the river crossing as well as how to best approach the objectives in the double bunkers area. Initially, we probed each approach individually to see the merits and downfalls of each one. We quickly came to the realization that the north, west, and direct south approaches took us deep into enemy territory where we could get surrounded as the round went on due the forests and hills in those locations giving the defenders plentiful amounts of concealment. This is something EP3 had to deal with as well in their scrim, which they did successfully by taking an approach that eliminated as much unseeable, or untraversable area for the defenders as possible.<br />
<br /><br />
In order for EP4 to implement a similar idea, 2Lt. Dahl and I decided to try and use the large river, marking the movement restrictions for the defenders, as a way to protect our flanks through much of our approach. By attacking from the east and southeast, we were able to protect our sides and rear for much of the round until we approached the objective itself. In our preparation, this plan immediately showed more promise than the other approaches as we could force our enemy to fight us head on. However, as the weeks progressed and our plan became more concrete, we began to run into issues as the opfor 29th members we were practicing against began to find ways to challenge and counter our plan. Initially, this was a benefit as we could see what our plan’s weaknesses were. A few changes needed to be made in order to get around these weaknesses and they were implemented pretty successfully. The first major change came from T/5 Perez-Pantoja, who discovered a wonderful location for the Bradley to fire upon the two northern objectives from a cliff on the NE on our side of the river. This worked beautifully and it meant that we only had to destroy the 2 southern objectives by hand. The second biggest change was that EP4S3 needed to be sent across the river a bit early in the north to clear out a cliffside that looked down the length of the river that the rest of our team needed to cross. Once again, opfor began to find ways to challenge these changes and make our life difficult, which ended up being a double edged sword. With us being mostly satisfied with our attack plan, we began to work on our defense.<br />
<br /><br />
<img src="https://steamuserimages-a.akamaihd.net/ugc/260471325505371539/94EEBD1EB4C4AB58267891E48B283539D04E28CA/" alt="image" /></p>

<p></p><div>River on Gorodok<br />
 </div>

<p><br /><br />
We knew our defense wouldn’t be nearly as challenging, as the area was favorable to the defenders thanks to the large area, thick forests, and hilly/village terrains available to us. A 360 degree initial setup with some quick movements in response to contact is all we needed to keep the objectives reliably safe. S1 and S3 defended the SE and NE respectively to hold off any direct attacks, while S2 spread out across the entirety of our NW, W, and SW sides to scout and cover and potential long flanks the enemy may have tried. In our preparation this worked out very well as the squads were spread out just enough to cover all approaches, but also close enough together to move and respond to support each other if one squad began to get overwhelmed. With our plans in hand, we readied ourselves for gameday.<br />
<br /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/sYKofaT.png" width="55%" alt="image" /><br />
On the day of the scrim, we had some last minute replacements that needed to be called in for S3 to fill out some numbers- thankfully we had Sgt. Mortem, Sgt. Gibson, and PFC Logan on hand to do so. PFC Logan especially would come in very handy for the match itself and all three were a welcome addition to the team. Once that was all settled and the match began, we attacked first as is normally the order of things during 29th scrims. This is where the double edged sword of our preparation began to come into play. Squad Ops has a very different play style to the 29th, and although our rough preparation had gotten us to iron out any kinks or challenges we may face in our path, it took our attention away from the rest of the map on the enemy side of the river. Once we arrived at our staging area on our side of the river and the Bradley began shelling it’s objectives, I took a Kornet missile to the face from the enemy BMP while sitting in my command MRAP from a position on the far north side of the map that none of us thought to use in our preparation. This was quite an embarrassing and shocking moment for me personally, but 2Lt. Dahl did a good job of continuing to keep the team’s morale up and progress with the plan. However, The enemy BMP was not done us. After our Bradley destroyed the north objectives as planned, the BMP relocated to the bottom of the cliff that overlooked the river crossing. Nobody saw the BMP before it began to fire, and as a result S1 lost several players during the crossing before our Bradley was able to quickly dispatch the BMP. The team soldiered on and all squads took their initial areas as planned. This is where our lack of diversity in our preparation bit us again. We paused in our push as we normally did to eliminate any remaining contacts in our direct path, as our enemy was usually stacked there. However, Squad Ops had dispersed themselves far and wide on their side of the river and unbeknownst to us our path to the objectives was actually quite open if we had just taken it. This lead to us giving the enemy a chance to reinforce the objective and get behind us as we made our final push, ultimately resulting in our defeat.<br />
<br /><br />
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/DarpPjb.png" width="55%" alt="image" /><br />
Morale was definitely low after that. Murphy’s Law had come into effect hard and everything that could’ve gone wrong, did. Nonetheless, EP4 showed its heart and determination and everyone collectively decided one thing after we collected ourselves for the next round: We are going to win this round. The squads took their places and awaited the enemy. S3 and parts of S2 took contact first on the south side as a much of the enemy team came from there, while one squad attempted to attack from the direct north. T/5 Evarts and T/5 Perez Pantoja had other ideas though as the two of them stopped the southern attack in its tracks and forced Squad Ops to back off after taking several casualties with none inflicted in return. The T/5 duo began to pressure the enemy and follow them back as they moved east and thinning their numbers even further. Simultaneously, PFC Logan encountered the enemy on the north side and landed a frag rocket on the enemy TL very early in the round. This also encouraged the enemy to break off of their initial attack direction and attempt another push from the northwest. Logan would continue to find enemies to land frag rockets on before eventually being overrun at his position. Between the three of them, these players managed to end up killing about half the enemy and stop their initial pushes. This caused them to not have the strength necessary to really make a dent in any of our held positions and the rest of the team was able to prevent the enemy from even getting close to our bunkers housing the objectives.<br />
<br /><br />
It was unfortunate that EP4 ended up being the first Easy Co. platoon to really drop a round against an enemy unit during a scrim, however there were some silver linings and lessons to be learned from the experience. EP4 showed its ability to take a difficult round on the chin and come back stronger as well as to outperform the enemy in terms of who had the stronger defense, and who made the most progress on their attack. Lessons were also learned for how to prepare next time to really keep our eyes open to all sorts of possible strategies from the enemy team, as the way Easy Co. plays Squad is not necessarily the only way to play Squad well. We also learned to believe in our plan a bit more and to not hesitate when we have the upper hand in the future. All in all the scrim was a mixed bag of course as a draw is not an ideal result with the enemy. However, EP4 did come out on top in terms of overall performance during each round comparatively speaking and we learned valuable lessons for the future. I am proud of fourth platoon and I look forward to seeing what we can accomplish on our next outing. Squad Ops were worthy opponents and they were a pleasure to interact with on and off of the battlefield. Hopefully we will get a chance to run it back against them in particular, and show them what we have learned.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Sgt. Newton<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Cpl. Tilley and PFC Mrzena</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Battle of Malaya and Singapore</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/41572/the-battle-of-malaya-and-singapore</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 03:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">41572@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>THE BATTLE OF MALAYA AND SINGAPORE</b></u></div><br />
<div><b>8 DEC 1941 – 15 FEB 1942</b></div><br />
<div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Esz2xjy.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Japanese troops clearing streets, Kuala Lumpur, January 1942.</div>

<p>My home country, Singapore, was the site of one of the most significant events in the Pacific War. Before World War Two, Singapore was considered the gem of the British Empire, a “Gibraltar of the East”, and an “impregnable fortress”. On 15 February 1942, these ideas were shattered as myths. A total of 120,000 British and Allied troops were defeated by and surrendered to the Imperial Japanese Army (IJA) which numbered only 70,000. In just three months, the IJA forces swept the entire Malayan peninsula of 700 miles, inflicted decisive defeats on the Allied troops in key battles, and captured Singapore. Prime Minister Winston Churchill reacted to this defeat in anguish, describing it as the “worst disaster” in British military history. His close companions noted that the tragic loss of Singapore in 1942 remained in Churchill’s memory for years to come.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>Background</p>

<p>How did this “disaster” happen for the British forces? Before we answer this question, we must first establish the world’s geopolitical situation at the winter of 1941. As the Axis forces in Europe were making huge gains in the Soviet Union, Britain was already at war for two years and in a precarious predicament. It only miraculously avoided disaster at the events of Dunkirk and the Battle of Britain in 1940. Naturally, Home Command was prioritizing Europe and Africa. By December 1941, Southeast Asia had become an increasingly important strategic location for the Japanese; British colonies and dominions in Asia seemed vulnerable due to the changing world situation. Unlike France which capitulated and gave Indochina to the Japanese, in 1941, Britain still owned the colonies in the East – Malaya, Burma, India, and the Gibraltar of the East: Singapore.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, the Japanese in 1941 were bogged down in the war with China since 1937. After taking the vital coastal cities and North China, the Japanese assault could push no further inland, with cumulative casualties. Japan, facing an embargo from the United States and others, needed oil desperately and could only gather it from the Dutch East Indies (today Indonesia), which was still controlled by the Netherlands despite having capitulated. However, weakened British, Dutch and French empires formed opportunities in Southeast Asia.</p>

<p>Malaya and Singapore were strategically important to the Japanese for three reasons. First, Malaya owned half of the world’s rubber plantations and tin mines. Second, the region had a large population of ethnic Chinese people who also formed the majority in Singapore. They were highly supportive of the Kuomintang and contributed significant relief effort to China, additionally boycotting Japanese goods. Capturing the assets of rich overseas Chinese in the region would be beneficial to the Japanese. Third, the geographic location of Singapore, as well as its fortifications, meant possession of it would hold the Straits of Malacca as a springboard to attack the East Indies and defend against British counter attacks from India. Meanwhile, it also meant that the so-called impregnable fortress would be in Japan’s hands, a great boost to the weary civilian population which had seen the country at war since 1937. From a Japanese strategic point of view, Malaya, Singapore, and eventually all of the East Indies were vital lands needed to be taken if the Japanese were to one day win in China.</p>

<p>At the same time, the United States also controlled the Philippines, a large blob in the way of the rich resources of the East Indies. The Japanese military’s perspective was that it was cornered, needing to find a way to solve her suffocating resource and strategic problem, lest it face utter defeat in China and potential loss of its empire. The opportune time came when most of the U.S Pacific Fleet was reported to be docked in Pearl Harbor.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/3nZmlGF.jpeg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Overall Japanese Pacific plan</div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Order of Battle</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/cUmdy10.jpeg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Malaya invasion plan</div>

<p>Unlike popular belief, the Japanese attack on the Pacific was not due to crazed radical militaristic ambition, but was treated as a necessary action for survival. It was a carefully calculated “do or die” step which Imperial Japan had planned for several years. General Headquarters of the Imperial Japanese Army (IJA) made the decision to perform an all-out strike and defeat all opponents in one decisive and planned strike; the U.S Navy would be crippled, out of the way, by losing capital ships in Hawaii. Meanwhile, the Japanese Army would invade key British, Dutch and American-held naval bases and port cities, proceeding onwards to take the rest of the Asian colonies. The “Southern Expeditionary Group” (Nanpogun) was set up with over 1 million personnel for objectives in Southeast Asia. Prior to this, Japanese intelligence had already been active in Malaya and spent years studying the ground. The Japanese set up contacts with local Malays and Indians, whom they attempted to align, foster anti-British sentiments, and, most importantly, gather military information and maps. On 7 December 1941 (8 December in Tokyo), the plan was commenced.</p>

<p>Assigned to invade Malaya and Singapore was the IJA “25th Army”, a total of 70,000 crack troops commanded by General Yamashita Tomoyuki. This included 3 full strength divisions with experience in China, including the elite Imperial Guards Division. Supplementing this was tank regiments which had a total of 400 vehicles, including the Type 95 Ha-Go and Type 97 Chi-ha tanks. The first transports were sent across the sea at night from Saigon and landed on the Northern Malay coast on the morning of 8 December.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/ioyaiFK.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Japanese uniform used in 1941, Malaya</div>

<p>The opponents on the Malay Peninsula was the British “Malaya Command” led by General Arthur Percival. This included two Indian divisions, the Australian 8th Division, as well as the 18th British Division, and volunteers from local ethnic Chinese and Malay population: a total force of 120,000 men. Prior to the battle, the British had called about half of these reinforcements only a few months before. Upon news of the Japanese landing at Thailand, more British troops, including the 18th Infantry Division, were rushed to Singapore. However, the British did not possess tanks other than Bren carriers, as the jungles were deemed unsuitable for tanks.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Ybwb7Qg.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>British uniform worn in 1941, Malaya</div>

<p>A significant part of the Japanese plan was to overwhelm the British Air force and Navy. The Japanese had slightly superior aircraft but only used them sparingly in the campaign due to AA defences. Thus, the first step taken on 8 December was also to cripple any resistance from the air which might slow down an invasion. In one day, only 50 out of the 110 Allied aircraft were destroyed in air strikes. The remainder only consisted of old Brewster and Buffalo aircraft and a few Hurricanes.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Sinking of the HMS Prince of Wales and Repulse</p>

<p>Japanese planners knew that the Royal Navy used Singapore as a giant naval base for its power projection in Asia. Since Japan’s navy was mostly deployed in the Pacific, Japanese forces only had one cruiser and some destroyers to escort the convoys, relying on air power to secure the seas.</p>

<p>A key event which spelled the fate of the battle was the sinking of 2 British battleships, which was the bulk of the British Navy in the far east. Upon hearing news of Japanese landings, this was designated Force Z and sent to intercept Japanese troop ships. Unfortunately for the British, there was no air support available, but the risky decision to send them under the guise of poor weather was still made. On December 10th, the troops were spotted by Japanese submarines in the area. Without any form of air cover, the battleships were quickly destroyed by G4M torpedo bombers.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/JzEX2Vn.jpeg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Japanese pilot’s depiction of the event</div>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/fNHqAzg.jpeg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Torpedo Bomber Mitsubishi G4M1 “Betty”, referred by Japanese as Hamaki/葉巻(Cigar)</div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Malaya</p>

<p>Before the real battles had even started, the British already lost any real chance of air-naval superiority due to a sudden Japanese strike. On the 8th of December, when Japanese troops landed on the beaches of Kota Bharu in Kelantan, northern Malaya, they were met by some Allied ground troops. Although the defenders managed to destroy two Japanese transport ships and bring down the first wave of troops, the overwhelming numbers of Japanese troops forced the Allies to retreat.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/DOwprYs.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Japanese troops cross a river in Malaya</div>

<p>The British had anticipated a Japanese landward attack and developed a first-strike plan known as Operation Matador. Under the plan, Allied forces would intercept the Japanese forces just over the Thai border, giving the main forces in Malaya time to gather and attack. However, the Allies failed to detect the Japanese landings before they happened, and British High Command calculated that the defenses at the beach would be sufficient. As the beach fell, the Allied troops, as per the plan, were ordered to Jitra, Kedah, to form an inland defense line, an elastic defense plan. The problem was that Japanese troops already crossed the Thai border and entered northwest Malaya with little resistance. The Japanese, having acquired the port of Kota Bahru, was able to acquire bicycles and additional supplies to move quickly down the peninsula and could use ports to disembark most of their main force and tanks from Saigon.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/BKDWMLj.jpeg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Japanese troops in Kuala Lumpur, January 1942</div>

<p>The defensive line at Jitra was reached by the Japanese on December 13th, only less than a week after the initial landing. This line was difficult to defend due to it crossing a mountain and very close to the Thai border. Allied forces retreated again inland in the Peninisula to the midpoint of Malaya at the Slim River. The Battle of Slim River on January 7th, 1942 was a disaster for the Allies. Of the 5,000 men from the two Indian brigades who had fought in the battle, only 25% survived. Losing Slim River also resulted in the loss of central Malaya to the Japanese, and Allied troops were quickly encircled and overwhelmed. By the end of January, important Malayan cities Penang and Kuala Lumpur were lost. This meant the Allies had to retreat to Johore and set up a defensive line there, the last before Singapore. At Muar, Johore, 4,000 Allied infantry managed to delay the Japanese advance. A major problem was that most of the allied troops were recruits from India and Malayan volunteers, unlike the more well-trained British and Australian troops. At Muar, there was a casualty rate on the Allies at around 70-75%.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/kQuU825.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Australian 8th Division anti-tank guns destroyed nine tanks in Johor, slowing the Japanese advance by a few days</div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Singapore<br />
Trying to slow the overwhelmingly rapid Japanese advance, the British blew up the causeway linking Malaysia to Singapore on February 8th. The Japanese simply used the fishing boats and rafts from villages in Malaya to cross at night. Australian troops fought off initial landing attempts while inflicting casualties on the Japanese. However, the Australian troops retreated unnecessarily amidst some confusion of battle, allowing the Japanese to gain a strong foothold at the shore defense installations. Subsequent landings by the Japanese were unopposed. The military situation for the British under Percival worsened. With shortage of food and especially water, along with highly demoralized troops, Percival surrendered his army unconditionally on February 15th.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Ln50RTv.jpeg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>British surrender in Singapore</div>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/0Tj0G7p.jpg" alt="Image description" /></div><br />
<div>Overall course of events in Malayan Campaign</div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Concluding Thoughts<br />
The British lost this battle disastrously due to three broad reasons. They suffered from lack of counter-intelligence/preparation, lack of air superiority, and mostly, the Japanese advantage of deploying the first strike. Compounding these three reasons was overconfidence of the High Command and making the assumption that tanks could not be used in jungles. Additionally, because they had strong ground intelligence, the Japanese knew British weak points which allowed a decisive first strike. Once the first strike was successfully done, morale was crippled among the confused defending forces, while morale soared among attacking forces.</p>

<p>It is also likely that the British simply did not have enough air equipment or reliable manpower in the Far East due to overextension; priority was placed on the Home Isles and the intense battle ongoing in North Africa. In Commonwealth countries, it is often remembered that of these 120,000 troops, many were sent to the railways of Burma as workers in near-death or deathly conditions. The gruesome details can be found elsewhere.</p>

<p>As a historian writing this in October 2020, I am without doubt that this campaign has affected this region and the world dramatically. Singapore as an English-speaking former colony often uses this story to explain its contemporary Israel-like defense policy, painting a picture of vulnerability using this battle, and justifying conscription of 2 years which I have served. This Israeli-Singapore model is useful for the defense policies and strategies of other small states.</p>

<p>Timeline</p>

<p>7–8 Dec 1941: Japanese attack Pearl Harbor; Japanese troops land in Northern Malaya.<br />
10 Dec 1941: Japanese sink HMS Repulse and Prince of Wales.<br />
19 Dec 1941: Japanese capture Penang.<br />
7 Jan 1942: Battle of Slim River.<br />
11 Jan 1942: Japanese capture Kuala Lumpur.<br />
31 Jan 1942: Last Allied troops cross the Causeway into Singapore.<br />
15 Feb 1942: Fall of Singapore.</p>

<p>Casualties<br />
Allied Casualties<br />
7,531 killed <br />
10,000 wounded<br />
130,000 captured<br />
Japanese Casualties<br />
3,507 killed<br />
6,150 wounded</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> PFC Tan<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Sgt. Gibson &amp; Cpl. J. Lee</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>29th vs. Real Life: The Combat Engineer</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/40676/29th-vs-real-life-the-combat-engineer</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 02:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">40676@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>29th vs. Real Life: The Combat Engineer</b></u></div><br />

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/8tbh7fP.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div> <div>An explosion in Squad</div><br />

<p>I have been pretty vocal in Easy Co. about saying that the combat engineer is the best AIT. Now personal bias aside from my background as a CE, I think that there is one fundamental argument as to why this is the case. The CE is the only infantry based AIT that can engage and kill any target that the player may come across. All other AITs must be in fear of the enemy tanks or IFVs, but not the combat engineer. While the CE still has to be cautious, those vehicles must instead fear the CE, despite being in a vehicle impervious to 90% of the enemy team. In fact, that is a CE’s primary purpose here in the 29th- to kill enemy vehicles. However, this is just combat engineers in the context of drills within the 29th. Given that the 29th is a realism unit based off of the US military, one may wonder, “What do CE’s do in the US Military today?” As it turns out, there is a bit of overlap. However as one might expect, the role of a CE in the real world is quite a different one to the world of the 29th in other aspects.</p>

<p>The coolest thing about being a combat engineer, in my personal experience, is shooting rockets at enemies and having the enemy vehicles or infantry rage at you over Steam for abruptly ending their life in that round. Here in the 29th, a CE’s primary role in drills is to hit targets with rockets. Although unlike other AITs, the combat engineer has more diversity and depth to its role through the use of the sapper. This role expands the CE’s capabilities by granting them access to mines, IEDs, explosive charges, sandbags and razor wire. Similarly in that regard, combat engineers in the real world are also a very diverse MOS. While combat engineers are trained how to use shoulder fired rockets to engage enemies on the battlefield, they are also taught a plethora of other skills to make them more useful on the battlefield than just combat troops.. Whereas 29th CE’s are more focused on the combat aspect of combat engineering, CE’s in the real world are engineers first and combat troops second.</p>

<p>Combat engineers are trained in several different aspects of construction and destruction that is relevant to combat operations. On the construction side of things, a CE has to know how to, well, be a construction worker. One of their responsibilities is constructing what are known as SEA or SWA huts from lumber and plywood the way any civilian carpenter would. These are rudimentary structures that are used for giving troops at a FOB a roof over their head to get out of the elements.. In addition to wooden construction, CE’s are also versed in concrete for construction purposes and airfield repair. While this may not be as glamorous as blowing up vehicles, it is still a critical part of combat operations.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i2.wp.com/real-leaders.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/Building-Somali-style-huts.jpeg?w=900&amp;ssl=1" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><div>615th Engineer Construction Company, 4th Engineer Battalion, building Somali-style huts for a training area near Dire Dawa, Ethiopia</div> <br />

<p>However, that is not the only type of construction that engineers are trained in. They are COMBAT engineers after all, and that means that combat construction is one of their primary duties. There are much more construction efforts that go on in a battlefield than one might think. Trenches, bunkers, defenses, tank traps, wire obstacles, and whatever needs to be created on the battlefield are all the responsibility of the engineers. It goes without saying that these are some highly important assets to providing safety for friendly forces as well as being a thorn in the side to all types of enemy forces. How these assets are used in real life can be compared to how they are used in Easy Company. While it is the responsibility of the CE’s to create these types of fortifications and obstacles, they work hand in hand with the leadership of the infantry in order to get it done, similar to how the SL’s in Squad are the ones who place the objects down before the rest of the team builds them. It’s more of a tandem effort in the real world as the leadership have a plan and an idea in mind and the CE’s are the ones who make that plan happen, but also advise the leadership on how to best employ said fortifications or obstacles on the specific terrain they may find themselves in. Also much like Squad, the common rifleman is not left out of the loop. Riflemen have shovels, and in the time-sensitive environment of a combat zone the extra e-tools are always needed for assistance. The key difference here though, is that the CE’s are not limited to using the sandbags and wire that we see in-game. Their capabilities in that regard go all the way up to the emplacement level and even in reshaping the earth around them.</p>

<p>There is one construction effort that CE’s in the real world handle that does not exist in the 29th, and that is bridging. Bridging is one of the tasks that combat engineers take care of that is truly independent from aid or overlap from the infantry. Bringing armored vehicles as well as supplies over a gap in the earth is a critical need for any combat operation to succeed. Rivers, canyons, and rough terrain are everywhere on Earth, and they must not stand in the way of the combat troops. To tackle this, the US military has invented an ingenious alloy of aluminum, magnesium, nickel and a few other metals that works as a super lightweight, flexible and strong material that is fabricated into more or less a giant set of legos made for bridging gaps from a friendly near side without needing a presence on the far side. Combat engineers often take pride in being able to bridge any gap they come across in hours with their giant lego sets, and it is quite a sight to see when they do.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://www.army-technology.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2017/09/5l-image-36.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><div>US Soldiers deploying an <i>Improved Ribbon Bridge</i></div> <br />

<p>However. construction is not all that CE’s are capable of. Oh no, in fact, where a combat engineer truly shines is destruction. You need a bridge blown up?Call the engineers. Do you need a building levelled? Engineers got your back. Do you need a 40ft crater blown into a road? Engineers. While infantrymen do use breaching charges and the like to open doors, CE’s are truly the kings of explosives on the battlefield. While in Squad a CE really only has a stick of C4 and maybe an IED at his disposal, the explosive kit of a combat engineer in the real world is vast and versatile. There are quite a number of different types of explosives used. From high explosives like C4 used to cut metal structures or breach into buildings, to low explosives like ANFO for moving earth and creating obstacles, as well as a whole host of other explosives for different purposes. CE’s are also trained to use explosives in some more nefarious ways that you may associate with the irregular factions in-game such as creating booby traps. However, on the flip side of this, CE’s are also trained in recognizing and eliminating booby traps and other types of hidden explosives like IEDs and mines. Some of these techniques are very creative. For example, there are a few ways to clear a minefield ranging from rolling up your sleeves and poking into the ground with a metal stick to locate mines (yes this is real), to using a metal detector to search for mines and IEDs (also real), to using a string of C4 attached like a chain to the back of a rocket to clear a line through a minefield. When it comes to IEDs, combat engineers tend to steer clear, as they are often much more complicated to deal with. Instead, CE’s do the reasonable thing and let those crazy fools in EOD have a crack at getting rid of the IEDs.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C4q_vafVMAArSmz.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><div>Combat Engineers set explosives to breach obstacles during training on the Korean Peninsula</div> <br />

<p>When you look at it in totality, the combat engineers of the real world and of the 29th do share a lot in common. Although, CE’s in the military are a lot more engineer than combat, and CE’s in the 29th are a lot more combat than engineer. However, their overall purposes are similar when applied to their separate worlds. The brave men and women that serve as combat engineers in the U.S. military today are much like ours here in the 29th, only more so, in that 29th CE’s are a bit of a snapshot or microcosm of the ones stationed around the world.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Sgt. Newton<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Cpl. Tilley and PFC Mrzena</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Real Life Counterparts to RS2: Vietnam - ARVN, USAF, &amp; AUS</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/40745/the-real-life-counterparts-to-rs2-vietnam-arvn-usaf-aus</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 01:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">40745@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>The Real Life Counterparts to RS2: Vietnam - ARVN, USAF, &amp; AUS</b></u></div><br /><br />
<div><img src="https://static01.nyt.com/images/2017/08/19/opinion/19vietnam-web/19vietnam-web-videoSixteenByNineJumbo1600.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div> <br />

<p>Despite being represented by three nations, the forces of South Vietnam have a lower weapon variety than that of the North Vietnamese. For the U.S. Armed Forces, Australian Army, and Army of the Republic of Vietnam, a large proportion of the weapons available in RS2 are of American origin. However, there is a juxtaposition found in the American relics from WW2 used by the ARVN with the most modern armaments available to the U.S.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>M14</p>

<p>Replacing the iconic M1 Garand as the standard-issue rifle in 1958, the M14 rifle was the final battle rifle issued in mass service to American forces. While the M1 Garand was among the most advanced rifles in its time, by the waning months of WW2, modifications were already being made to the design. Among these modifications included the implementation of automatic fire, box magazines to include additional bullets, and redesigns of gas ports and regulators for better functionality in extreme conditions.</p>

<p>Seeing service in Vietnam for a period of around eight years, the M14 performed adequately; the weapon’s full-power cartridges provided massive penetration power and range. However several issues, stemming from the environment, were present. The length and weight of the M14 led to its users being frequently impaired by dense undergrowth, and the wooden stock had a tendency to swell in the heavy moisture, affecting accuracy. Fiberglass stocks were produced to alleviate these concerns, but the weapon was soon replaced by the M16.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://arc-anglerfish-arc2-prod-bonnier.s3.amazonaws.com/public/LJOJ6QQG4TGCKNK2BDBX4ZR2IM.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div> <br />

<p>Despite no longer being the standard-issue rifle, the M14 remains in limited service throughout the U.S. military, with civilian variants also used for sport. In its Rising Storm 2: Vietnam representation, the M14 has no concerns with accuracy or ergonomics. Although locked to semi-automatic fire, the weapon is capable of one-shot kills and boasts immense stopping power over its M16 alternative.<br />
<br /><br />
M16 / M16A1</p>

<p>Ordered as a replacement by direction of Robert McNamara, overpowering objections from U.S. Army officers supporting the M14, the M16 first entered service in 1967. Lightweight, produced with aluminum alloy, and chambered with intermediate cartridges in a world where traditional rifles were forged from wood and iron, the M16 – earning monikers such as “Mattel-16” and “poodle shooter” – was greeted with much derision from its users.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://s34193.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/m163-1200x549.jpg.optimal.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div> <br />

<p>Indeed, the M16 had severe reliability concerns that would soon be amended by the subsequent variant, the M16A1. The weapon had a malfunction rate of two per one thousand rounds fired, which was only exacerbated by the harsh conditions and poor logistics found in the Vietnam War. Three factors primarily led to widespread extraction failures and malfunctions: a change in powder type from testing environments resulted in differing pressure curves, models lacking chrome-plated chambers, and lax maintenance founded on the misconception that the weapon was self-cleaning.</p>

<p>With 80% of soldiers reporting stoppages and anti-war protests gaining fervor, the M16A1 was quickly introduced in 1967. Issued alongside cleaning kits, the M16A1 boasted many modifications that addressed its predecessor’s infamous reliability issues. A 1968 Department of Army report found that the M16A1 found widespread acceptance by U.S. troops in Vietnam, with 85% preferring to carry an M16 or its carbine-length variant, the XM177E2.</p>

<p>In RS2:V, the M16A1 variant is available. In real life, out of concerns for magazine feed failures, 20-round magazines used in the M16 were not fully loaded, which is also represented in-game as selected historical accuracy. While the M16A1 comes with 20-round magazines, prior to Late War, the maximum capacity in game is 18+1. Authentic to real-life, the M16A1 features low recoil characteristics and provides the player with more ammunition than is available to a M14 user.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>M60</p>

<p>Adopted in 1957 and issued beginning in 1959, the M60 has served with every branch of the U.S. military. Seeking to address disparities in suppressive firepower from WW2, particularly in those present against German doctrines, post-war America began a search in the late 1940s for a new, lighter machine gun. Partially derived from German machine guns of WW2, early prototypes of the M60 conglomerated many design principles from the firearms available at the time. Incorporating a semi bullpup system from the FG 42 with the belt feed system from the MG 42, the T161 system was born. Tests and revisions – including the demand to adopt the new NATO standard 7.62mm – led to the final T161E3. Both out of a desire to avoid licensing fees and bias towards domestic products, the U.S. Army adopted the T161E3 over foreign competitors, designating it the “M60”.</p>

<p>While versatile, capable of firing shoulder-mounted, vehicle-mounted, on a tripod, or on a bipod, not even the M60 was invulnerable to the harsh climates of Vietnam. Critical parts of the weapon wore out quickly, and the weapon’s light weight rendered it fragile to damage. As a result of the weapon's volume of fire with the humidity and mud of the environment, diligent maintenance was necessitated. Despite the weapon’s weight and ammunition consumption, the M60 boasted a mixed reputation, with many period American forces appreciating the weapon’s capacity to provide overpowering suppressive fire. Alongside the new M16, the M60 became a familiar sight in wartime photography and post-war cinema, owing to the weapon’s distinctive silhouette.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/63/b5/87/63b5878fc75c5a75f8e2ceb7cbbc68a0.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div> <br />

<p>In RS2:V, the M60 is available with a choice between either 100-round box magazines or a 200-round belt. With the weapon’s voracious appetite, many users opt for the 200-round belt to maximize the weapon’s uptime.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>L1A1/L2A1</p>

<p>Widely adopted by many NATO countries, the FN FAL entered service in 1954 with the Australian Army under the designation “L1A1”. To provide common operational and administrative procedures for ease of logistics and communication, the NATO states produced many Standardization Agreements, STANAG for short. As part of the standardization effort, the FAL had select-fire capability, removable magazines, and self-loading function regardless of ammunition. Originally designed to fire intermediate rounds, inspired by the German Strumgewehr, the prime contender was the experimental .280 British, a highly capable caliber balancing weight and rifle-grade ballistics. Early developments of the FAL were forced to abandon this cartridge to appeal to the Americans, who demanded a munition no smaller than .30 calibre. For this reason, the early model T48 rifle, chambered in the 7.62mm NATO cartridge, was developed, although the U.S. eventually dropped the FAL in favor of the M14.</p>

<p>However, from its first production in 1953, the FAL was adopted by over 90 countries and throughout NATO states. The FAL is among the most produced firearms in history. During the Vietnam War, the L1A1 SLR was the standard-issue rifle for the Australian Army. Citing better reliability and higher stopping power, Australian forces greatly preferred their larger caliber weapon over the American M16. With great experience in jungle warfare, owing to earlier conflicts, the Australian forces considered the strengths and weaknesses of the L1A1 and its larger caliber more appropriate with their tactics and doctrine.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/81/a9/85/81a985ed11301a9a2bc952d47e4713b1.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div> <br />

<p>In coordination with Canada, Australia developed the L2A1 as a variant to serve as an automatic rifle in a support role. Differences in the design included a heavy barrel, a different front sight, a handguard that also served as a foldable bipod, and unique 30-round magazines. This variant was only used by Canadian and Australian forces, as Commonwealth states primarily used the Bren light machine gun for the support role. As the Bren had changeable barrels and a greater weight, many considered the Bren to be superior for fire support.</p>

<p>Regardless, towards the end of the 20th century, the benefits of intermediate cartridges became increasingly well-known. In comparison to more modern assault rifles, the FAL was too long, too heavy, and too limiting. As years progressed, this weapon designed for universal use was itself replaced. The Belgians adopted the FNC, the Austrians the AUG, the British the L85 – all of which were chambered in the intermediate 5.56mm NATO.</p>

<p>In RS2:V, a stark contrast to the dichotomy between the M14 and the M16, the L1A1 combines the best of both worlds – superior stopping power alongside very serviceable recoil.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. J. Lee<br />
<em>Edited by</em> T/5 Evarts &amp; Sgt. Gibson</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues Ep. 19 - SSgt. Crane</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/40692/veterans-virtues-ep-19-ssgt-crane</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 22:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">40692@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-v51_iqdrXNc?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v51_iqdrXNc"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/v51_iqdrXNc/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Real 29th: TSgt. Joseph &quot;Lightning&quot; Farinholt</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/39733/the-real-29th-tsgt-joseph-lightning-farinholt</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">39733@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>The Real 29th: TSgt. Joseph "Lightning" Farinholt</b></u></div>

<p></p><div><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/e/e2/Joseph_A._Farinholt.jpg/330px-Joseph_A._Farinholt.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Technical Sergeant Joseph "Lightning" Farinholt</div> <br />

<p>TSgt. Joseph Farinholt, nicknamed “Lightning” by his fellow soldiers, is the only soldier in United States history to have earned the Silver Star four times within the same war. Joseph Farinholt was born in Cantonsville, Maryland in 1922 before he joined the United States Army at the age of sixteen in 1938, lying to the recruiter about his age in order to join Maryland's National Guard. Notably, he told his recruiter that his age was twenty-three, as TSgt. Farinholt elaborated later on in an interview, "My uncle told me if I ever told a lie to tell a big one – so I did". His unit would become activated and re-organized into the 175th Infantry Regiment under the 29th Infantry Division, he would start out his career as an assistant gun crew-chief of a 57mm anti-tank gun.<br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://www.blogs.va.gov/VAntage/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Fariholt-5.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div>Pvt. Farinholt's laid out equipment for inspection prior to D-Day. Tidworth Barracks, England.</div> <br />

<p>TSgt. Joseph Farinholt's first act of heroism happened on July 13, 1944, near the city of Saint Lô in the deadly hedgerow countryside of France. At the time, Cpl. Farinholt was out on a patrol when he encountered a German mortar pit that was hammering on a nearby friendly unit. Cpl. Farinholt would grab an AT rocket launcher and disregard his safety in order to move into a better position to successfully eliminate the mortar team. As soon as Cpl. Farinholt eliminated the mortar team, an anti-armor vehicle started to approach his position. With quick thinking, Cpl. Farinholt dashed into the nearby hedgerow, reloading his weapon before disabling the vehicle once it passed by his position. He would recall this moment, "I spotted a German mortar position, so I picked up a bazooka and ran forward to knock it out. The Germans I didn't kill ran away. Then I looked up and this German tank was headed right for me. I jumped in the brush, reloaded the bazooka, and knocked out the tank as it went by" Once he returned to his position, an officer would pick him up and say "Son, you've just won a Silver Star". For his actions not only would he earn the Silver Star, but he would also get promoted to Staff Sergeant.<br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://www.blogs.va.gov/VAntage/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Farinholt-8.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div>Joeseph Farinholt with his fellow platoon members.</div> <br />

<p>SSgt. Farinholt would earn his second Silver Star only five days later, for his actions during daring night raids in order to recover direly needed anti-tank guns that would assist in destroying a tank column days later. He would recall "Our position was overrun after a counterattack and we had to leave our equipment or be taken prisoner. After dark, we went back and hooked two of our guns to trucks while under heavy fire. We couldn't get a truck to our third gun so we pulled it out by hand. We really baffled the Germans with that move because they thought they had us cornered. The next morning we stopped a column of tanks with those guns. That was my second Silver Star". For his actions, his nickname of "lighting" for his fast initiative would become well known among the unit.<br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://www.blogs.va.gov/VAntage/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Farinholt-2.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div>TSgt. Farinholt with his wife</div> <br />

<p>By the time Farinholt would earn his third Silver Star, he had been promoted to Technical Sergeant and became the senior-NCO of his platoon. His citation would state "T/SGT Joseph A. Farinholt, 20343338, 175th Infantry, US Army for gallantry in action against the enemy in Germany. On 13 October, 1944, during a period of heavy and constant enemy shelling, casualties were sustained in the 1st Battalion, 175th Infantry. Amidst this intense barrage of fire, T Sgt Farinholt left his sheltered position and went to the aid of the wounded where he administered first aid treatment and personally evacuated four casualties to a place of safety. The outstanding courage and unselfish devotion to duty displayed by T Sgt Farinholt while under decimating enemy fire, reflect great credit upon himself and the military service. Entered military service from Maryland."<br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/a6/Lightning_at_Bourheim.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div>"Lighting at Bourheim" from the National Guard Heritage Series</div> <br />

<p>TSgt Farinholt's final Silver Star would be earned in the defense of Bourheim, when his unit's position was attacked by German forces accompanied by a Tiger tank. After one of TSgt. Farinholt's anti-tank crews were killed by a Tiger tank leading a tank column into Boruheim, TSgt. Farinholt would single-handedly man the anti-tank gun and successfully would detrack the Tiger tank, which then blocked the rest of the tank column. However, TSgt. Farinholt would become wounded when the tank returned fire. He sustained 26 bullet wounds, a shattered bone in his right leg, and shrapnel from the tank’s main gun. Even with these severe wounds, TSgt. Farinholt would successfully manage to escape and drive back in a jeep to his company headquarters, allowing for a P-47 airstrike against the German column. His citation would state: <br /><br />
<i>"T/SGT Joseph A. Farinholt 20343338, 175th Infantry US Army for gallantry in action against the enemy in Germany. On 26 November, 1944, while the Third Battalion 175th Infantry was defending the town of Bourheim, enemy Infantryman supported by tanks entered the town and advance against the battalion's thinly held line. Realizing the gravity of the situation , T SGT Farinholt ordered his antitank platoon to remain in position where they delivered such devastating fire upon the enemy that they were forced to divert their attack to another sector of the town. Then, finding all communications severed by enemy artillery fire, T/SGT Farinholt , despite suffering from a broken leg, asked to be placed in a vehicle while he drove under fire to the command post to inform the Staff of the situation. Such courageous actions reflect great credit upon himself and the military service. Entered Military Service from Maryland."</i><br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://www.blogs.va.gov/VAntage/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Farinholt-gravesite-2-730x417.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div>Joseph Farinholt's gravestone</div> <br />

<p>TSgt. Joseph Farinholt would survive the war, recovering in an army hospital for two years from his wounds. During his time in the hospital, he would meet his soon-to-be wife, one of the army nurses who took care of him; They would have four children together. TSgt Joseph Farinholt would also receive the Bronze Star for his contribution for the war effort, a purple heart, and a Belgium Croix de Guerre. He passed away peacefully on June 11, 2002 at the age of 79.<br />
<br /><br />
Ever Forward.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. Dawdy<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Sgt. Gibson &amp; Cpl. Tilley</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Battle of Chosin Reservoir</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/39865/the-battle-of-chosin-reservoir</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 22:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">39865@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>The Battle of Chosin Reservoir</b></u></div>

<p><b>Introduction</b></p>

<p>Some historians call the Korean War, a “forgotten war” due to it being overshadowed by other conflicts involving the United States during the 20th century. As we know, World War Two and the Vietnam War are extensively covered by American movies and games. As gamers, we hardly had the chance to experience the Korean War, a highly dramatic episode in human history which shaped the world we know today. This article is meant to cover a dramatic battle which was probably one of the most important battles of the war: The Battle of Chosin Reservoir in late 1950.<br />
Background (The Korean War)</p>

<p>In June 1950, the Korean People’s Army (KPA) of North Korea (DPRK) crossed the 38th parallel into the Republic of Korea (ROK), with the aim of unifying the country, sparking what is known today as the Korean War. Within a few months, the course of the war took a highly dramatic turn. By August, ROK and United Nations (UN) forces were pushed by KPA to a small perimeter around Pusan, on the Southeastern most coast of South Korea, almost losing Korea entirely to KPA forces.</p>

<p>The total annihilation of ROK was saved by an operation in Mid-October 1950 known as the Incheon landing. Under the orders of General Douglas Macarthur, the UN successfully launched an amphibious attack on Korea’s Western coast at Incheon, near Seoul. This soon resulted in DPRK forces being pushed back all the way toward the Yalu River and close to the border with the People’s Republic of China (PRC). By September 1950, China became increasingly threatened by the UN forces, which did not seem to have any intention of stopping at the 38th parallel, and continued to occupy North Korea. At this point, the UN forces were so close to the Chinese border that Mao Zedong and his colleagues suggested a military intervention. China sent a force of 1 million troops, called the People’s Volunteer Army (PVA), entering Korea in late October of 1950.</p>

<p>However, this intervention was at first unexpected by the UN troops… they had for months, only fought North Korean troops. The U.S high command ,particularly, had little idea of the Chinese military mobilization in Manchuria. In North Korea, allied troops were still assembling with the intention of advancing to the Yalu River, and completely occupying the DPRK, just as the DPRK almost occupied all of the ROK a few months ago.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://imgur.com/i7VxE5h.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Course of the war</div> <br />

<p><b>The Battle of Chosin Reservoir</b></p>

<p>In mid-november of 1950, as U.N troops marched North, they passed the Chosin Reservoir, which became the scene of one of the most dramatic episodes of the war. The Chosin reservoir is located in what is today DPRK territory, in the Northeast of Korea just 100km south from the Chinese border. The Chinese troops, fresh out of the Chinese Civil War, meanwhile, were mobilizing themselves in force of up to 1 million, and reinforced their divisions to cross the North Korean border with Manchuria.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/rLLvusZ.png" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Location of Chosin</div> <br />

<p><b>Order of Battle</b></p>

<p>The 9th and 13th Army from China, totalling around 150,000 troops, and consisted of troops fresh from the Chinese Civil War. Most forces crossed the border almost undetected. This massive force of Chinese volunteers, soon found themselves encircling the UN’s X Corps, a force of 30,000 troops around the lake. It was the Chinese intention to drive the UN forces back to South Korea and possibly off the peninsula entirely. Mao Zedong, the Chinese leader, saw the UN forces as a threat to Chinese security and put his best commander, Peng Dehuai, who had distinguished himself during the Chinese Civil War, in charge of the troops.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.gyazo.com/630137144e19059e4065f4e58951372c.png" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Chinese troops assembling to enter North Korea</div> <br />

<p>The X Corps, comprised of some 30,000 troops, started to assemble in Chosin. The X Corps was mostly comprised of the veteran 1st Marine Division, with some Army battalions and ROK troops. The 1st Marine Division were one of the most elite troops the U.S could offer. They already were famous at the time, renowned for its victories during the Pacific War against the Japanese at key battles such as Guadalcanal, Peleliu and Okinawa. Moreover, the 1st Marine Division had also faced important battles at Pusan and were tasked to lead the amphibious assault at Inchon. The troops were in assault positions expecting to push the North Koreans to the Yalu river, under orders from its commander, General Almond. Under orders from General Macarthur, The U.S troops were not expecting much resistance, after finding themselves victorious on numerous occasions after Inchon. Like Macarthur, Almond was confident in being able to reach the Yalu by Christmas, and spread his forces thin. At the same time, the U.S Eighth army on the Western flank of Korea was forced into full retreat by the numerical superiority of the Chinese, crippling any form of reinforcement. The X Corps was heading into a situation of destruction, with the 1st Marine Division being under threat of encirclement.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/BDKXDfG.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Troops of the 1st Marine Division at Chosin</div> <br />

<p><b>Course of the Battle</b></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://imgur.com/QynGcMN.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Map of the Battle</div> <br />

<p>General Almond however, was unaware of the Chinese intentions and troop sizes. The Chinese knew full well that the 1st Marine Division was operating in the area, and intended to encircle and destroy it to cripple American morale in the war. Destroying a crack unit like the 1st Marines would, as Chinese high command measured, test the American public’s approval of the U.S intervention in the war. Marshal Peng Dehuai dedicated a total of 10 divisions with orders to surround and destroy the single Marine division, attacking on the night of 27th November.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, as winter approached, the temperatures dropped to around -35 degrees Celsius. The Marines, once informed of the attack, fortified their positions. The Chinese attacked throughout the night across all major marine positions. Contrary to popular belief and portrayals in many Western (and ROK) movies, the PVA did not attack in human waves. According to historian Edwin Simmons, the PVA operated in compact groups of 50-100 men, about the same size as an U.S Army company. Chinese historical sources in Mandarin also confirmed this to be true. This in fact gave the Marines time to organize a hasty retreat, since the Chinese attacked in small groups that failed to overwhelm any positions on the night of 27th.</p>

<p>General Almond then made a risky decision; withdraw all the forward positions along with their equipment and heavy weapons toward a better position at Hagaru-ri. Almond, observing the Chinese movements, realized that the main objective was to destroy the 1st Marines, and used other forces in the area to distract the Chinese army. On November 29th, Almond met with President Truman who decided to abandon the idea of a unified Korea, but still wanted to save the ROK. The X Corps’ new objective was to retreat to the nearest port at Hungnam in the Southeast, lest be destroyed by the PVA.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/eplB3i9.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Marines preparing to withdraw</div> <br />

<p>On December 1, the Marines started to withdraw with its rear going to Hungnam first, while the frontline troops at Hagaru-ri held the line. However, the Chinese redirected troops to cut off the convoy route and close the roads. General Oliver Smith, commander of the 1st Marines, was quoted as saying “If You Stopped Moving, You Froze”. Both sides were caught in brutal terrain at severe temperatures, but had no choice but to continue fighting. The Chinese, despite old weapons and inadequate supplies, kept on attacking the Marines to demoralize them. For the Americans, it was a miracle that by December 2nd no units were captured or destroyed, and continued to make their way down the snowy road to Hungnam, with only a single M4A3 Sherman leading the convoy.</p>

<p>Throughout the next two weeks, the U.S and ROK forces organized themselves to retreat in a bounding fashion. The Chinese ultimately failed to cut off any part of the route south of Hagaru-ri. One crucial advantage that the U.N had was the use of F4U Corsairs equipped with night-fighting capability. Dropping napalm and strafing Chinese positions for 24 hours, these sorties were pivotal in saving the 1st Marine positions from being destroyed. By December 7th, some divisions of the PVA 9th Army had been virtually destroyed, unable to counter the U.S in the air.<br />
Finally, the 1st reached Hungnam port on December 11th , after 2 weeks of fighting, with the withdrawal complete. The Chinese had lost their morale and momentum, with both sides suffering severely from the cold. The 1st Marines was able to evacuate via the port at Hungnam.</p>

<p><b>Aftermath of the Battle</b></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://imgur.com/dD8i4jz.png" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />
<div>Map of the Retreat</div> <br />

<p>The Chinese 9th Army, had a total of 37,500 casualties, with other historians estimating the losses at a range of 40,000 to 80,000 troops. Meanwhile, the 1st Marine Division and other units of X Corps had 17,000 casualties, which included those lost to frostbite. Despite the losses, 105,000 soldiers, 98,000 civilians, 17,500 vehicles, made it to Hungnam and evacuated to South Korea.</p>

<p>Subsequently, Hungnam was captured by the Chinese, which had taken massive casualties and failed in their objective to destroy the 1st Marines. The Chinese failure with high casualties meant more time needed to reorganize and reinforce which slowed their advance toward Seoul. With most of North Korea captured by the Chinese and North Koreans, they soon captured Seoul (again) in January 1951. Ultimately the successful retreat of X Corps, was able to reinforce the lines and allow the UN forces to reorganize themselves, with Seoul yet again recaptured by the U.N forces in July 1951. Thereafter, a stalemate ensued, which establish the borders of North and South Korea we recognize today.</p>

<p>The action at the Chosin Reservoir in late 1950, saw the X Corps put up a ferocious defense that ensured their survival, and contributed immensely to the survival of South Korea. Many historians agree that if they had been successfully encircled and fallen, there might not have been enough momentum to defend Seoul and rest of the ROK from being captured by the PVA and KPA.</p>

<p>References:<br />
Appleman, Roy E. Disaster in Korea: The Chinese Confront MacArthur. Vol. 11. Texas A&amp;M University Press, 2008.<br />
Montross, Lynn, and Captain Nicholas A. Canzona USMC. US Marine Operations In Korea 1950-1953: Volume III-The Chosin Reservoir Campaign [Illustrated Edition]. Pickle Partners Publishing, 2015.<br />
Roe, Patrick C. The dragon strikes: China and the Korean war, June-December 1950. Presidio Press, 2000.<br />
Simmons, Edwin H. "Frozen Chosin: The Marines at the Changjin Reservoir" (PDF). p. 48. Retrieved July 2, 2018.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> PFC Tan<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Sgt. Gibson &amp; T/5 Evarts</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues Ep. 18 - Sgt. Gibson</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/39611/veterans-virtues-ep-18-sgt-gibson</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 01:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">39611@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-dgEi8OpznpI?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dgEi8OpznpI"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/dgEi8OpznpI/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Real Life Counterparts to RS2: Vietnam - PAVN &amp; NLF</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/39085/the-real-life-counterparts-to-rs2-vietnam-pavn-nlf</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 18:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">39085@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>The Real Life Counterparts to RS2: Vietnam - PAVN &amp; NLF</b></u></div>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/18/c2/5e/18c25e7488b33594c36f576ae948d64a.jpg" width="55%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<p>Contrary to the common, modern pop culture perception that the North Vietnamese forces were composed of simple farmers equipped with simpler weapons, the conventional army was in actuality a modernized power receiving exorbitant amounts of aid from Communist-aligned countries, while the Viet Cong guerillas were closer to the contemporary symbol. In Rising Storm 2: Vietnam, this munitions disparity is seen in the variety and varying amounts of archaism within the weapons accessible by both the PAVN and NLF factions.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>SKS</p>

<p>One of the first weapons chambered for the 7.62x39mm M43 round, the SKS was designed with lessons learned from World War Two. For example, the Soviets main existing rifle, the Mosin-Nagant, fired a cartridge too powerful in the contexts it was used. While effective at ranges up to 1,000m, most infantry combat was held at distances of 100m to 300m. This meant the 7.62×54mm was rarely used to its full potential. The weight and recoil produced by the full-power cartridge were significant motivators for the Soviet Army to consider intermediate cartridges.<br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/09/66/03/0966031ebe6b2f0a1811d50b7662037d.jpg" width="65%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<p>Designed in 1944, adopted in 1949, and then replaced three years later by the AK-47, the SKS can be considered a stop-gap solution. Featuring a spring-loaded bolt carrier, this self-loading rifle is easily field stripped and reassembled without specialized tools, well-suited for the soggy environments of Vietnam. To this extent, while the SKS found itself quickly obsoleted by the AK-47 in the Soviet military, the former found a second life in other Soviet-aligned countries.</p>

<p>Vast quantities of obsolete and redundant SKS rifles were donated to movements around the world. Serving as one of the primary arms of the NLF, SKS's in Vietnam were gradually phased out and replaced by AK variants as logistics from foreign powers continued. In game, this is abstracted through weapon availability in campaign mode: early war, the SKS is the most modern rifle available to the NLF; and in the late war, the NLF gain access to the Soviet-produced AKM. One advantage that the SKS holds over AK variants is a consequence of its longer length; the SKS fires at a velocity twenty meters per second quicker than the replacing AK variants do.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>AK variants</p>

<p>With much of the same philosophies that drove the development of the SKS, along with inspiration from the German Sturmgewehr 44, the AK-47 was created for the modern world. Often considered one of the first assault rifles, the concept for this iconic weapon was borne from the woes of wounded soldiers lamenting the failures of their issued rifles. Featuring innate usability from simplicity and reliability, the AK-47’s entry into the Soviet military was hampered by production issues, which conveniently allowed the SKS more years of life.</p>

<p>In 1959, these issues were remedied with the introduction of the modernized AKM, equipped with a stamped sheet metal receiver that was lighter and easier to produce. A slanted muzzle break included with the design also aided in recoil control. From this design came all three AK variants featured in RS2:V - the AKM itself alongside the Chinese Type 56 and Type 56-1.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/564x/48/ff/be/48ffbee4bb3787bba37bc74083bcb806.jpg" width="50%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<p>Owing to their vast industrial capability, the Chinese produced millions of the Type 56 and Type 56-1 variants. Early Chinese support for North Vietnam meant that many AKs supplied to North Vietnamese soldiers were of Chinese origin. Indeed, of all AKs captured by American soldiers, most were Type 56 variants. There is a small distinction between the Type 56 and Type 56-1. While both are variants of the AKM, meaning both have replaced milled receivers with stamped receivers, the Type 56-1 has a folding shoulder stock and the bayonet removed for ease of transportation.</p>

<p>In RS2: Vietnam, there are slight differences between these three variants represented in gameplay. The AKM boasts an open iron sight, allowing for easier target acquisition, and is very slightly more accurate. However, the Chinese variants feature lower recoil characteristics, and the stock folding capability of the Type 56-1 hastens ADS time. Although these differences are admittedly minor, their in game stats are different enough that engaging discussions could be held.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>MAS-49</p>

<p>A subsequent step in the long chain of iterations, the MAS-49 was part of the French’s answer to the need for modernized weaponry post World War Two. Capable of enduring harsh service environments, the MAS-49 was introduced with improvements to the intricacies of the design. With the number of bolt moving parts reduced to six, this gun required mere seconds to disassemble and could be easily cleaned.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/0f/a1/9c/0fa19c3234cd89643d8e02637fa8eb5a.jpg" width="50%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<p>Strangely enough, that this gun is featured in RS2:V seems to be an anachronism. The majority of MAS rifles used by North Vietnamese soldiers were MAS-36s captured from raided French supplies abandoned in the First Indochina War. Sources indicate that the MAS-49 was quickly replaced by the later iteration MAS-49/56, which was lighter and could fit an attachable knife bayonet. While only 20,600 MAS-49 rifles were produced, the MAS-49/56 - the final MAS design used prior to the FAMAS - was efficiently mass-produced, attaining a total of 275,240 rifles issued in twenty one years.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>MAT-49</p>

<p>Created with a machine stamping process that allowed efficient mass production, the MAT-49 - chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum - addressed an urgent need for a compact weapon to arm airborne and colonial forces. Designed with a low production cost to alleviate the post-war French military’s recovery, the MAT-49 derived inspiration from the American M3, and much of the latter’s DNA can be seen in the MAT-49’s stamped lower assembly. In its thirty years of production, eventually being obsoleted by the bullpup FAMAS in 1979, about 700,000 were produced. Easy to carry, easy to clean, and easy to fire, the MAT-49 was one of France’s most prized weapons.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/f5/97/d8/f597d89c426161e0ff32fceebba0a54a.jpg" width="50%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<p>The PAVN and NLF both captured scores of these SMGs, from both battlefield scavenging and surrendering French soldiers. The MAT-49 would become one of the two most frequently used SMGs among Northern forces. However, as the 7.62x25mm Tokarev cartridge was ubiquitous, owing to supplies from the Soviets and Chinese, captured MAT-49s were often modified and re-chambered. Converted MAT-49s could be identified by their longer barrels and 50% higher rate of fire.</p>

<p>In game, both variants are available, aptly named the “French Original” and “Viet Modified”. Their performances match the characteristics of their respective historical counterparts. The Viet Modified fires much faster and does slightly more damage than the French Original can match.<br />
<br /></p>

<p>DP-27 | RP-46</p>

<p>The RP-46 is a variant of the Degtyaryov machine gun, more commonly known as the DP-27. A light machine gun chambered in the same full-power 7.62×54mmR that the Mosin-Nagant fired, the DP-27 was the primary light machine gun used by the Soviets throughout World War Two. In addition to being the standard squad LMG, the DP-27 was also, after several modifications, mounted on aircraft and fitted to almost all Soviet tanks. While this weapon was sturdy – capable of being buried under mud, dirt, or sand and still operating consistently – and used the same ammunition as the standard Soviet rifle of the time, the DP-27 had a fire rate at nearly half of those in its wartime rivals, the German MG 34 and MG 42 counterparts.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-zen_doc/241223/pub_5c85340ae064fd00b2671bfa_5c8584b9d399dd00b42ee020/orig" width="50%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<p>While the DP-27 boasted a distinctive silhouette, the weapon’s reliance on pan magazines begot a myriad of issues. The 47-round capacity neutered the DP-27 system as a support weapon. The round shape inconvenienced transport and left the magazine prone to damage. Other issues also emerged from factors outside the magazine shape. The bipod was weak and fragile if poorly handled, and overheating of the barrel led to recoil spring failure. These latter concerns would be addressed with subsequent iterations, but the most crippling weakness – the pan magazine – remained until the advent of the RP-46.</p>

<p>The RP-46 arrived with many boons. Chiefly among them was a successful transition to a belt-fed loading mechanism that finally allowed for sustained fire. Heavier barrels meant more rounds could be fired per barrel, reducing downtime in replacing those overheated. Additionally, the absence of pan magazines greatly reduced the weight of the machine gunner’s full kit – gun and ammunition – by ten kilograms.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://images-wixmp-ed30a86b8c4ca887773594c2.wixmp.com/f/975de00d-9db4-4e39-9e6b-f956007fc851/d9shes2-709083ae-d877-48cc-afa4-b402adc4b66a.jpg/v1/fill/w_600,h_352,q_75,strp/the_company_commander_gun_rp_46_by_thedesertfox1991_d9shes2-fullview.jpg?token=eyJ0eXAiOiJKV1QiLCJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiJ9.eyJzdWIiOiJ1cm46YXBwOiIsImlzcyI6InVybjphcHA6Iiwib2JqIjpbW3siaGVpZ2h0IjoiPD0zNTIiLCJwYXRoIjoiXC9mXC85NzVkZTAwZC05ZGI0LTRlMzktOWU2Yi1mOTU2MDA3ZmM4NTFcL2Q5c2hlczItNzA5MDgzYWUtZDg3Ny00OGNjLWFmYTQtYjQwMmFkYzRiNjZhLmpwZyIsIndpZHRoIjoiPD02MDAifV1dLCJhdWQiOlsidXJuOnNlcnZpY2U6aW1hZ2Uub3BlcmF0aW9ucyJdfQ.3fOut3cSwlI4iFiGMEcKQoJAiPi7OwfjnQdNLAJymTI" width="50%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<p>In RS2:V, the DP-27 and RP-46 are available to NLF and PAVN forces, respectively. As the latter is a variant of the former, both weapons share very similar characteristics. Their damage and fire rate match, while the DP-27 has slightly better recoil statistics. Fortunately, because a Northern player can only either be of the NLF or PAVN factions, one will never have to choose between these two weapons.</p>

<p>True to real life, the volume of weapons available to the NVA is staggering. Boasting access to differing weapons of French, Russian, Chinese, and even American origins, NVA players have no shortage of toys. A rifleman on the South can choose between either the M16A1 or his faction’s battle rifle. In contrast, the opposing NLF rifleman has the choice between three AK variants, the marksman’s SKS, the antiquated Mosin-Nagant, the captured MAS-49, and even the M1 Carbine. While the weapons available to the North may be inferior to their Southern counterparts, NVA players can enjoy greater tactical flexibility, derived from their vast library of arms.</p>

<p>Stay tuned for the next part covering the weapons of the United States, Australia, and South Vietnam!</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. J. Lee<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Sgt. Gibson &amp; T/5 Evarts</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues Ep. 17 - 2Lt. Ochs</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/39042/veterans-virtues-ep-17-2lt-ochs</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 02:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">39042@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-q23KmJccwPE?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q23KmJccwPE"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/q23KmJccwPE/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues Ep. 16 - Sgt. Furie</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/36217/veterans-virtues-ep-16-sgt-furie</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 02:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">36217@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-nIsiaFVCf9Q?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nIsiaFVCf9Q"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/nIsiaFVCf9Q/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues Holiday Edition - Lt. Col. Wheatley and MSgt. Conrad</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/35370/veterans-virtues-holiday-edition-lt-col-wheatley-and-msgt-conrad</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">35370@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><b><i>As we look back on not only the past year but the past decade, there is a lot to discuss and who better to discuss that with than those who have been around for all of it.  This was the first full decade that the 29th has existed which is quite remarkable. Back in 2010, the 29th had three companies, Able, Baker, and Charlie, all deployed in Darkest Hour. The unit saw two massive changes in the decade with expansions to Arma 3 and Rising Storm in 2012, and a move to Rising Storm 2 and Squad in 2017. <br /><br />
On this final day of the year, we bring you the Veteran's Virtues Holiday Special featuring Lt. Col. Wheatley and MSgt. Conrad! They will share with you some of their comments about their time in the unit and where the 29th has been and is going! <br /><br />
Please enjoy this special episode and have a wonderful New Year on behalf of Civil Affairs Corps and Quartermaster Corps! </i></b></div> <br />

<p><span data-youtube="youtube-kZmjoR0PL6Y?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kZmjoR0PL6Y"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/kZmjoR0PL6Y/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>2019 Year in Review</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/35316/2019-year-in-review</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">35316@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/5eonozZ.png" width="85%" alt="image" /></div><br /><br />

<p>Another year is just about in the books. As we embark on this traditional break over the holiday season, it is also time that we reflect upon the year we had in the 29th.</p>

<p>We had a busy start to the year with not one, but two OCS Scrims in the month of February. Easy Company’s Sgt. Willis of EP2 and Sgt. Kelso of EP3 both proved their leadership abilities, and demonstrated them in combat, earning them both the rank of Second Lieutenant. These events being the first scrims of any sort since the formation of Easy Company in 2017, it was also the first experience in a scrim environment for many members of Easy Company.</p>

<p>In March, we saw Dog Company grow by opening their Third Platoon under the command of WO1 Bruneau.</p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/J7oqAQG.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><em>Rising Storm 2; Courtesy of Sgt. Dahl</em></div> <br />

<p>March also saw members of Charlie Company participate twice in the ArmA Tactical Combat (ATC) with the 2MRB. This earned those members the Armed Forces Expeditionary Medal.</p>

<p>As is tradition, the unit was fooled with an April Fools joke. This year, the benevolent 2Lt. Ochs bought the unit for a mere $5000, granting him the rank of Lieutenant Colonel! While we all would have enjoyed what Lt. Col. Ochs had to offer, I think we breathed a sigh of relief when we learned that Lt. Col. Wheatley would continue guiding the unit.</p>

<p>Immediately after this prank, we got some real news with the announcement of Battalion Drills, which took place for several weeks during late spring and into summer.</p>

<p>Summer was a very busy time in the unit. At the Battalion Level, a Donation Rewards Overhaul went into effect with new recognition for those who donate, along with several interesting jacket updates.</p>

<p>Charlie Company hosted a D-Day anniversary event that turned into a weekly WW2 special event hosted by SSgt. Butler.<br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/8c1Ox1p.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><em>Arma 3; Courtesy of T/4 Burg</em></div><br />
<br />

<p>In Easy Company, the second rendition of Easy Company Battle of the Squads was fought. This was a long and intense tournament, lasting almost three months. It was bigger and better than the first EBOTS with the introduction of a double elimination bracket. It also included a squad comprised of members from Dog Company, helping to build cooperation between companies. In the end, EP2S2 was victorious and was awarded the Meritorious Unit Citation.</p>

<p>Following in Easy Company’s footsteps, Dog Company hosted their own Dog Company Battle of the Squads which also featured great fighting and excitement that can only be found in special events. DP2S2 came away with the gold and also received the Meritorious Unit Citation.</p>

<p>TSgt. Dethfield had the following to say about the impact and importance of special events and scrims:</p>

<p><em><b>"Events and scrims give squads and platoon a sudden, significant focus as well as a sense of completion after it is over. The year-round training in weekly drills finally pays off, the reasons for why we do things the way we do are made very clear, and everyone comes together to work towards a common goal. These events then become part of our unit history as people tell their stories and the lessons learned, making the unit that much more effective as time goes on."</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – TSgt. Dethfield, Easy Company Company Sergeant</b></em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Continuing on from the busy summer, Easy Company saw two of her platoons get deployed to fight in their first scrims. EP1 deployed on November 2nd against the 508th PIR and the 3rd Rangers. EP1 won both rounds of the scrim, many members seeing their first scrim action. A month later, EP2 got the same opportunity; fighting against the 7th Cavalry Regiment and the 3rd Rangers. EP2 had a decisive victory in their attack and closed out the year on a high note.<br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/zk5nAN9.png" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><em>Squad; Courtesy of SSgt. Robles</em></div><br />
<br />

<p>Over the course of the year we also saw several staff projects and overhauls come into effect:</p>

<ul>
<li>SSgt. Robles and Cpl. Mellinger guided a significant revitalization of Quartermaster Corps and our YouTube channel. </li>
<li>2Lt. Willis and T/5 Evarts began streaming many 29th events on our Twitch Channel as well.</li>
<li>TSgt. Dethfield worked to get Medical Corps going again providing much assistance to the unit’s technical difficulties. </li>
<li>1Lt. Fritz and T/5 Perez-Pantoja worked diligently to release great content to Easy Company in the form of mods in Engineer Corps</li>
<li>Sgt. Gibson and Sgt. Crane reintroduced the Veteran’s Virtues series through Civil Affairs Corps.</li>
</ul>

<p><br /><br />
Finally, in the year of 2019, we saw several SLT scrims and many promotions past the rank of PFCs. In total, there were 33 promotions to Cpl. and T/5, 10 promotions to Sgt. and T/4, 3 promotions to SSgt., 1 promotion to TSgt., 2 promotions to WO1, 2 commissions to 2Lt., 2 promotions to 1Lt., and 1 promotion to Cpt.</p>

<p>Additionally, T/5 Enser was awarded the prestigious recruiters badge for recruiting 160 recruits, all within 1 year. This recruitment single-handedly helped to expand Easy Company and bring it her Fourth Platoon under the command of SSgt. Robles, who had this to say about the creation of EP4:</p>

<p><em><b>"The thing about a freshly created platoon is that people have a chance for a fresh start. It's a new platoon, a new culture to be experienced -- it really is fun...especially when you are in a position to influence the said culture. The real cool thing, however, is that EP4 is made out of people from EP2 and EP3, a melting pot of two different, but similar, platoon cultures. It's been fun being the leader of this new platoon. If someone is in a position where they can do this, I would truly recommend."</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – SSgt. Robles, EP4 Platoon Sergeant</b></em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>2019 was a busy year for the unit and a year of growth and change. As always, we will finish with a message from Lt. Col. Wheatley. <br />
<br /><br />
<em><b>It's always fun to look back at the year and all that we have accomplished as a unit. Most years seem to fly by then the review post always opens our eyes to how much was actually completed. Looking forward to next year, I'm not sure exactly where we'll be, but I am sure we're going to be at the top! 29th, Ever Forward!</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – Lt. Col. Wheatley , Battalion Commander</b></em></div>

<p><br /><br />
</p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/oLsdT1p.png" width="85%" alt="image" /></div><br />

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Sgt. Gibson<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Cpl. Tilley</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues 11 - SSgt. Dethfield</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/32924/veterans-virtues-11-ssgt-dethfield</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 02:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Barclay</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">32924@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-FfwYGq__epQ?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FfwYGq__epQ"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/FfwYGq__epQ/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues 15 - SSgt. Bagge</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/35037/veterans-virtues-15-ssgt-bagge</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">35037@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-LlpIZtvrsu0?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LlpIZtvrsu0"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/LlpIZtvrsu0/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues 14 - SSgt. Robles</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/34626/veterans-virtues-14-ssgt-robles</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 10:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">34626@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-O2dQZXhAAFM?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O2dQZXhAAFM"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/O2dQZXhAAFM/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues 13 - WO1 Bruneau</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/34433/veterans-virtues-13-wo1-bruneau</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 02:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>SSgt. Gibson</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">34433@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-_GiwFTLKz3k?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_GiwFTLKz3k"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/_GiwFTLKz3k/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Veterans Virtues 12 - Sgt. Runing</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/33689/veterans-virtues-12-sgt-runing</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 17:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Barclay</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">33689@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-4kYeY76oCyw?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4kYeY76oCyw"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/4kYeY76oCyw/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Tết: Year of the Dog</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/32766/t%E1%BA%BFt-year-of-the-dog</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 13:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Barclay</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">32766@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><span data-youtube="youtube-GPrEMMXltB8?autoplay=1"><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GPrEMMXltB8"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/GPrEMMXltB8/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" alt="image" /></a></span></p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Guesting: The Universal Benefactor</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/31162/guesting-the-universal-benefactor</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 18:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Barclay</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">31162@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>Guesting: The Universal Benefactor</b></u></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>One of the core aspects to anyone's experience in the 29th is the mandatory drills they attend. These drills all have many benefits, from improving communication and teamwork, to honing in-game skills and even just socializing with others in the unit. They are mandatory for a good reason, as we could not function as a unit if our members did not show up on a regular basis. The events that we prepare for and the goals that we have as a unit depend on a consistent roster of well-trained members ready to go at a moment's notice, yet there is one thing that many people in the 29th still do not engage with in drills. This one thing provides numerous benefits to everyone involved and enhances everything we do both in and out of game; that thing is guesting drills.</p>

<p>The phrase "guesting drills", sometimes simply referred to as "guesting", is when a member of the 29th attends a drill that they are not expected to attend. Whether it is a mandatory drill of another squad or a non-mandatory company drill, 29th members are allowed to ask permission to participate in drills they are not required to. Most of the time the permission is granted as long as the person making the request follows the rules, behaves themselves, and does not disrupt the drill. Many people, however, actively choose not to do this for one reason or another. To put it bluntly, if you are not guesting often, you are doing yourself a huge disservice. It does not matter who you are, your rank, your position, or what your goals are in the unit. Guesting drills on a regular basis benefits literally everyone, especially you. Some people do not have as much time as others, but if you are actively choosing not to participate outside your mandatory two hours, that is a mistake.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/2ajev4P.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>For members of the 29th who have just graduated BCT, guesting other drills allows you to get accustomed to the 29th way of doing things much more quickly. You will easily pick up on the standard procedures and traditions we have, the tactics we often use, the different purposes for weapons and personnel, and even the unofficial rules that each unit sets up naturally. As a fresh private, it's your role to carry out orders to the best of your ability and to continue learning all you can about the 29th. This process takes time but there is no better way to speed this up than guesting.</p>

<p>Perhaps you are interested in getting more involved in the 29th? You want to be noticed for an AIT, or get more into the administrative side of things? You need to get your name out there and what better way to do so then to be someone regularly seen throughout the week. Being a regular sight at multiple drills means those who often make those kind of decisions above you can easily see you are serious about sticking around. You will learn things about the 29th that are not exactly written down, learn who are the ones to talk to about certain topics, and even who the experts are regarding certain AITs. With the amount of guesting that can be done in the 29th, you will easily pick up many of the tricks and odd issues regarding the game itself, as well.</p>

<p>Maybe you want to be considered for SLT, or you are currently in SLT and need to practice your in-game leadership? There is no easier way to do this then to take command of a team of guests. You will quickly learn the basics of leadership as well as seeing what works and what does not; especially when it comes to your own personal style of leadership. The nervousness that many have when they first start leading teams fades much faster when guesting regularly and getting into the routine of taking command of a squad.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/vHXsYIv.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Even current leadership at all levels can benefit from guesting. Squad leaders attending other squad's drills can see what others are working on, look for good ideas to "borrow", and sometimes even see what does not work. You can even help out other squads by sharing a different point of view or contributing information they may not be aware which goes towards improving your entire platoon - the unit size we just so happen to deploy in the most. This also applies to platoon and company leadership, providing a good chance to get to the know the other leadership in the unit. It also lets you interact with other members who you normally would not have a chance to.</p>

<p>Of all the habits that we encourage in the 29th, there is no better habit I can think of than guesting. From helping one's personal skill, to practising the essential skills of leadership, to just having a good time with fellow 29th members; guesting has a huge impact on everyone involved. If you currently do not guest drills regularly, fix that.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> SSgt. Dethfield<br />
<em>Edited by</em> Cpl. Furie &amp; T/4 Laird</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Easy Company Battle of the Squads: In Review</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/30863/easy-company-battle-of-the-squads-in-review</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 19:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Barclay</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">30863@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>Easy Company Battle of the Squads: In Review</b></u></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>In late 2018, Easy Company embarked on a journey to see what her squads were made of. Nine squads, some as old as Easy Company itself, some only weeks old, would all compete for the title of best squad. While this is determined every six months or so, with the coveted Superior Unit Citation, this competition was for a much greater prize: the prestigious Meritorious Unit Citation. The Superior Unit Citation is nice, as are all medals and awards, but it goes away as the ever changing landscapes of platoons shift. The Meritorious Unit Citation however, stays with a member and their squad, enshrining themselves in the 29th’s great history.</p>

<p>Under the organization and leadership of SSgt. Dethfield, and with the help of SSgt. Robles, a schedule, rules, and bracket were all created and announced. There were measures put in place to ensure fairness for each squad, along with rewards for the squads that recently were awarded the Superior Unit Citation, ensuring each of them a first round bye and a place in their platoon championship. Matches were fierce, often including close range engagements consisting of four Attack/Defense rounds and an Attack/Attack tiebreaker if necessary. This set the stage for an exciting competition, one that would reveal interesting tactics, exciting gameplay, and even heroic acts by some.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><em><b>"This is an exciting time for Easy Company! We hope to see some really heated and intense fights in the matches ahead and above all, remember that you guys are here to prove your squad is the best squad in the company and can be victorious regardless of the circumstances! Train hard and keep your morale high and give every match 100%!"</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – SSgt. Dethfield, EP2 Platoon Sergeant</b></em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Train hard the company did, with every squad drill being based around preparation for Easy Company Battle of the Squads. Every squad put in the effort, time, and excellence that define the 29th Infantry Division, and while there was only one winner, eight squads left the competition knowing that they represented their platoons, company, and the unit well.</p>

<p>Easy Company, Second Platoon, First Squad, while no longer having the same roster, still carries pride in what they accomplished by winning this competition. In the process of getting through the competition, they competed against three squads, two of those being the best the other platoons had to offer, and still came out victorious. Not only did they earn this victory, they did it without leaving a doubt as to which squad was superior, winning not just every match, but every single round thanks to the heroic acts of now Cpl Greene. Without his acts of bravery and a lack of self preservation in the final minute of the round, the final defender would have been able to go undetected and win the round for the other team. He ran through the objective with little regard to anything but victory, managing to locate the enemy behind a door, and kill him. Unfortunately, his wounds proved fatal and he fell. For this, he was awarded the Purple Heart. While Cpl. Greene's action were vital to his squad, it was thanks to all members that they were able to win this competition and show their excellence.<br />
<br /></p>

<p><em><b>"It has been an exemplary display of skill, team, dedication and sportsmanship on the part of the squad and there is no doubt that they have earned their overwhelming victories and title as champion of the EBOTS competition.”</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – SSgt. Dethfield, EP2 Platoon Sergeant</b></em></div>

<p><br /><br />
<br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/LijA6rs.png" width="30%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><b>The roster of the EBOTS Champions - EP2S1:</b><br />
Sgt. Willis – Squad Leader<br />
Cpl. Maciel – Assistant Squad Leader<br />
T/5 C. Garrett – Combat Engineer<br />
PFC Harmon – Platoon Sniper<br />
PFC Moreno – Rifleman<br />
PFC Greene – Grenadier<br />
PFC Strickland – Automatic Rifleman<br />
PFC McDonough – Rifleman<br />
Pvt. York - Rifleman<br />
Pvt. Assis – Rifleman</div>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><b>On behalf of the entire unit, congratulations once again EP2S1, and Easy Company as a whole, on a job well done!</b></div>

<p><br /></p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. Gibson<br />
<em>Edited by</em> PFC Tilley &amp; T/4 Laird</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>29th Infantry Division: 2018 Year in Review</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/29853/29th-infantry-division-2018-year-in-review</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 14:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Barclay</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">29853@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/qIzrg98.png" width="70%" alt="image" /></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>As 2018 comes to a conclusion, it's time once again to look back at the year we have had in the 29th.</p>

<p>We started off the year with the long-overdue OCS scrim of Charlie Company’s CW3 Hill, who after two intense battles was commissioned to the rank of Captain.</p>

<p>Also in February we saw the 29th’s departure from Darkest Hour and the unfortunate closure of Baker Company. Soon after in April, we saw the 1000th training platoon of Basic Combat Training.</p>

<p>April Fool's Day came around and 'in order to better reflect the importance of paternal heritage', the names of each member of the unit was appended with the Scandinavian '-son' suffix on the forums for the day.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/9Rwa0rI.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><em>Arma 3; Courtesy of Sgt. Butler</em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>August and September brought us the OCS scrims of Dog Company’s Sgt. Ochs who was commissioned to the rank of Second Lieutenant.</p>

<p>The next few months saw such events as the continuation of MSgt.’s ‘ZeuSaturday’ campaign, Sgt. Butler’s Arma 3 WWII campaign, and of course the annual 29th Halloween Arma 3 Zombies event.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><em><b>"OCS scrims are one of my favourite parts of what the 29th does. OCS scrims are always entertaining and rewarding and I always look forward to participating in them. When I was first told I'd be doing OCS I hadn't given much thought to the scrim in any complex way until the date of the first scrim was announced; then it became real. If you were to ask I don't think I could remember the number of OCS scrims I have been part of in my time in the 29th but, I can tell you, when the OCS scrim is your own it takes on a new meaning.</b></em></p>

<p><em><b>I would describe the feelings as anxiety, excitement, pressure. Anxiety about performing well and not letting my team or Bn. down, excitement at the opportunity and the event in general, and pressure because that is the point of it. That last one, pressure, really is the point. I've seen Bn. design OCS scrims that put pressure on the candidate, I've seen candidates almost crack. I though I was fully prepared but when it's you and not someone else who is being tested, it's very different.</b></em></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/7qyZlxX.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><em>Squad; Courtesy of PFC McDonough</em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p><em><b>The results of the OCS scrims were good overall. After the fact I saw many ways I could have performed better or done something differently. I learned some things about my leadership style and had to make some adjustments as a result. All in all a thoroughly wonderful experience and Bn. really should be commended for all the effort that is put into the OCS program.</b></em></p>

<p><em><b>Since I became CO, Charlie Company has had many changes. Most notably, we switched how we managed a mod list with our members and servers and moved those servers onto a dedicated server box. The mods we use offer us many toys to play with and an ever increasing sandbox to play in.</b></em></p>

<p><em><b>I endeavor to see that the coming year is eventful and entertaining and I am thankful to have such a wonderful group of guys to be part of."</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – Cpt. Hill, Charlie Company CO</b></em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>The closure of Able Company and the 29th's departure from Red Orchestra 2/Rising Storm came in November and with it another large segment of the unit’s history stretching back almost a decade came to an illustrious conclusion.</p>

<p>In July we were hit by the deeply tragic news that fellow 29th member T/4 Jeffrey Hauser had passed away. So soon after, the 29th was shook once more in August with news of the passing of T/5 Samuel V. Morse. An abundance of tributes flooded in for the pair as the 29th as a whole mourned their loss.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.imgur.com/xX8bxEm.jpg" width="85%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><em>Rising Storm 2: Vietnam; Courtesy of 2Lt. Fritz</em></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>We end 2018 with over 300 members across the now three companies based in Arma 3, Rising Storm 2: Vietnam, and Squad. While we did unfortunately see the closure of two companies that had been such an integral part of the 29th, we saw the first full year of Dog and Easy Company as they prepared to house their own history.</p>

<p>There were a total of 5 SLT (Squad Leadership Training) scrims in 2018 bringing with them the promotions of PFC Laird, PFC Vos, PFC Vogel, T/5 Vonk, PFC Furie, and PFC Maciel as they all became Non-Commissioned Officers.</p>

<p>Bringing this year in review to a conclusion, we can only anticipate what is to come for the unit in 2019. We’ll see a barrage of fresh members ready to start their 29th careers as well as the usual assortment of scrims, changes, events, and who knows what else, only the year will tell.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><em><b>"When I look back at the unit in 2018, Battalion’s first impression is that a lot has changed. Just looking at the roster, we started the year with five companies and ended with three. While a reduction in companies could be indicative of a decline in the health of the unit, downsizing allowed for a redistribution of leadership that helped to fill gaps that existed which led to a strengthening of the unit as a whole. Thanks to the efforts of multiple recruiters, our membership is sitting strong at approximately 350 members, a brotherhood that stretches around the globe.</b></em></p>

<p><em><b>Looking back at the effectiveness of Officer Candidate School as we traditionally do in these posts, Battalion Headquarters was able to successfully complete the OCS’s of three new Second Lieutenants (2Lt. Barclay, 2Lt. Brewer, and 2Lt. Ochs), as well as the didactic portion of two candidates (Sgt. Kelso and Sgt. Willis), and, for the first time ever, successfully commissioned a CW3 Company Commander into a Captain. These leaders have already made profound impacts on those under their command and Battalion Headquarters is optimistic greater things will be accomplished in 2019.</b></em></p>

<p><em><b>Looking forward, Battalion will be working with Company Headquarters to review and update many policies to ensure that they are still relevant and applied equally across each Company in the Battalion for the sake of consistency."</b></em></p>

<div><em><b> – Lt. Col. Wheatley, Battalion Commander</b></em></div>

<hr />

<p>Written by T/4 Laird</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>How To: Morale</title>
        <link>https://vanilla.29th.org/discussion/29344/how-to-morale</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 20:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <category>Civil Announcements</category>
        <dc:creator>Cpt. Barclay</dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">29344@/discussions</guid>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><div><u><b>How To: Morale</b></u></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p><em>“And should we win the day, the 4th of July will no longer be known as an American holiday, but as a day when the world declared with one voice: We will not go quietly into the night! We will not vanish without a fight! We’re going to live on! We’re going to survive! Today we celebrate our independence day!”</em></p>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Do you feel that? That sensation of pride, enthusiasm, and confidence that just surged through you like a jolt of caffeinated electricity? That’s your morale being raised by the rousing speech given by American President Thomas J. Whitmore, played by the highly skilled character actor Bill Pullman in the blockbuster film Independence Day (1996). With a speech like that you’ll be able to do anything from clearing a building to destroying a massive alien mothership. That is the power of morale.</p>

<p>So, you want to know How To: Morale like renowned American actor Bill Pullman. Morale, of course, has a long history. In English, the term entered our language in the 18th century from the French word moral. The Merriam-Webster dictionary provides one definition of morale as being “the level of individual psychological well-being based on such factors as a sense of purpose and confidence in the future.” At the same time, Encyclopedia.com provides the definition of morale specifically regarding soldiers as being “a state of mind that either encourages or impedes action.” From these definitions we can surmise the utmost importance of morale.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/d9/f4/e2/d9f4e2cd72176bde70e780f4cbfe4bd8.jpg" width="70%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><b>Renowned American Actor Bill Pullman.</b></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>With your morale soaring from that initial speech provided by renowned American actor Bill Pullman, I can only imagine you are biting at the bit to learn how best to provide this same exact feeling of elation to your fellow members of the unit. And don’t worry Private Fresh, you don’t need to be Sergeant Oldtimer to have a positive effect. So, with that in mind, let’s talk about the benefits of high morale, the consequences of low morale, and the best methods to maintain high morale.</p>

<p>First and foremost, let’s come to the agreement that most people want to feel belonging. According to Maslow’s Hierarchy of Needs, a theory in the field of psychology proposed by the aforenamed Abraham Maslow in 1943, the human desire for belonging is the third sought after need, following physical safety and physiological needs. What this means is that once someone is getting all their physiological needs met, such as needs for sustenance and sleep, and then when they feel appropriately protected from harm, they immediately seek belonging from their social group. In questions of morale, this directly translates to a need to feel apart of the unit in which they belong to.</p>

<p>In this light we can determine that high morale directly relates to increased unit cohesion and effectiveness. But, the benefits of high morale can go well beyond statistics and numbers; high morale often results in creating better gameplay results as squadmates pay more attention, communicate more often, and work together more easily. Maintaining high morale, then, can decide the difference between failing to save the human race or instilling suicidal bravery in a lone pilot to bring down the alien mothership single-handedly. In the same way, within the confines of the 29th this can inspire one squad member to play more effectively, committing to actions like defending an objective that may put their own life at risk in favor of the team’s victory. In addition to suicidal bravery, high morale can instill other, just as important behaviors in a squadmate. When morale is high, attendance goes up; no doubt, a squad member who feels belonging with their unit will be more inclined to show up in the first place. Additionally, members who have high morale are more likely to be inspired to take part in non-combat related jobs or to further recruit to bolster the ranks. Moreover, there are numerous benefits beyond those listed here that can affect members in individual and unique ways that can’t even be expected.</p>

<p>Of course, high morale is but one side of the 1939 minted silver dollar coin that is Morale. Low morale, just as high morale, can be devastating. As said by the not-as-renowned-as-Bill-Pullman Chiang Kai-Shek, “War is not only a matter of equipment, artillery, group troops or air force; it is largely a matter of spirit, or morale.” Despite his non-actor status, the non-fictional President of the Republic of China speaks true; no matter how many AITs you’ve been provided, how many vehicles are assigned to you, and how great the defensive position to be held, a force with cripplingly low morale will fail to achieve victory and not just due to things you might expect. Imagine, if you will, a scrim day where the platoon in question, suffering from CLM (Chronic Low Morale) Syndrome, meets an enemy ready and willing to fight with their high morale visible in the very pixels of the game. Where the enemy has deployed at full strength, the squads of each platoon raggedly arrived in poor order and undermanned. Months of training were wasted on disinterested and uncommunicative platoon members with many having missed some or all of the trainings due to being offline in War Thunder during drills. Missing spots in the ranks weren’t filled because no one was inspired to recruit, and jobs weren’t filled because even the lowliest private couldn’t be bothered to accept a position practically handed to them. In this potential dark future, as horrendous as it is, we see the threat of low morale as plain as day.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://gohighbrow.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/4.0..png" width="70%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><b>Not-as-renowned Chiang Kai-Shek.</b></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Does this vile vision of a possible future shock, disturb, and sicken you? If not, stop reading; you have already fallen too deep into your CLM Syndrome and there is little that renowned American actor Bill Pullman or I can do for you. But, if you fear that possible future and see the wisdom in what Pill Pullman and Chiang Kai-Shek have to say, read onward. Morale can be brought up and maintained at all time highs by active action by even the lowest, newest, freshest members around. That’s right, Private Fresh, this is your time to shine.</p>

<p>The easiest way to increase and maintain high morale is through the tried and true way of being friendly with your fellow 29thers; with as little as three muscles moving to press your talk key and only some expended oxygen, anyone from Sergeant Oldtimer to PFC D. Rainbow can make Private Fresh feel welcome to their new environment. Friendliness can range from something as simple as talking to others to pubbing or even playing in non-29th games with each other. Developing a repertoire with other members of the unit will increase the likelihood that more members will stay longer and become more active in the unit due to friendships generated over their time present. Being able to keep a level of banter going without threatening the cohesion of the unit during combat can go farther in this; squadmates who joke in the foxhole stay in the foxhole, so to speak.</p>

<p>In the confines of leadership, morale can be instilled through being present, visible, and open; Bill Pullman’s speech would’ve been useless if he made it to no one and didn’t broadcast it around the world for all to hear. It is up to members of leadership to be the anchor by which other members of the unit might take part in increasing overall morale. Without a present and active leader efforts to increase morale not only grind to a halt but begin to take not just small steps, but great leaps backwards towards a tailspin of low morale. Individuals in leadership worried about low morale in their respective units should seek to make their presence more known, to increase camaraderie among their units by example, and take an active role in the 29th that inspires others to do the same. In addition, keeping up with paperwork despite how laborious it can be will give motivation to members through promotions and awards to continue excelling and striving for new goals. Even taking the time out to talk with a member over steam, asking what their goals are, and offering to help facilitate it can go a long way. Above all, showing a level of knowledge about your unit through genuine quotes that come off as actually knowing the person rather than being some hackneyed munitions-grade sentence of vague approval can make the difference between Private Fresh becoming PFC D. Rainbow or becoming Bored [29th Ret.].</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p></p><div><img src="https://gallery.commandoveterans.org/cdoGallery/d/4037-13/Commandos+and+Rangers+on+the+road+from+Anzio+to+Rome_.jpg" width="70%" alt="image" /></div>

<p></p><div><b>Camraderie; No. 9 Commandos and American Rangers in Anzio, Italy.</b></div>

<p><br /></p>

<p>All of the above and more all lead to the creation of Unit Identity, the core of creating a self-sustaining high morale high. Unit identity is the ultimate way of maintaining high morale within a unit and can take a newly formed squad in a whole new platoon made up of new, fresh faced Privates and forge it into a highly effective, incredibly cohesive, and particularly friendly squad loaded to the brim with veteran PFCs. This can be further strengthened with mottos that all agree on, so-called extracurricular events outside of scheduled drill times, and a killer badge that everyone can point to with pride.</p>

<p>It is with all this knowledge that renowned American actor Bill Pullman, Chiang Kai-Shek, and I leave you ready to take to your squads, platoons, companies, and the 29th at large, so armed with the skills to increase morale. All three of us solemnly hope that your efforts to better the unit are further increased by what you have read today and that you have indeed learned How To: Morale.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><b>Sources</b></p>

<p><a href="https://americanrhetoric.com/MovieSpeeches/moviespeechindependenceday.html" rel="nofollow">https://americanrhetoric.com/MovieSpeeches/moviespeechindependenceday.html</a><br />
<a href="https://merriam-webster.com/dictionary/morale" rel="nofollow">https://merriam-webster.com/dictionary/morale</a><br />
<a href="https://encyclopedia.com/history/encyclopedias-almanacs-transcripts-and-maps/morale-troop" rel="nofollow">https://encyclopedia.com/history/encyclopedias-almanacs-transcripts-and-maps/morale-troop</a><br />
<a href="https://brainyquote.com/quotes/chiang_kaishek_539294?src=t_morale" rel="nofollow">https://brainyquote.com/quotes/chiang_kaishek_539294?src=t_morale</a></p>

<hr />

<p><em>Written by</em> Cpl. Crane<br />
<em>Edited by</em> T/4 Laird</p>
]]>
        </description>
    </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
